<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adam&#39;s Blog</title>
    <description>A blog about whatever is on Adam&#39;s mind.</description>
    <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/Adams-Blog/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/Adams-Blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 08:31:09 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 08:31:09 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Climate Change and Snow - The Real Story</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
#inhofe {
	float: right;
	padding: 20px;
}

.axis path,
.axis line {
  fill: none;
  stroke: #000;
  shape-rendering: crispEdges;
}


.pdxLine {
  fill: none;
  stroke: steelblue;
  stroke-width: 2px;
}

.pdxLine:hover {
	stroke-width: 4px;
}

.nycLine {
	fill: none;
	stroke: green;
	stroke-width: 2px;
}

.nycLine:hover {
	stroke-width: 4px;
}
svg {
	display: block;
	margin-left: auto;
	margin-right: auto;
	background-color: white;
	font: 10px sans-serif;
}

.key {
    padding: 10px;
    border-radius: 50%;
    display: inline-block;
}


&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Climate change is real.  97% of all scientists believe the Earth is getting abnormally hotter than usual because of greenhouse gases polluting the Earth.  But there are some people who believe it&#39;s a hoax.  Most likely it&#39;s to protect their greenhouse gas producing fuels and chemicals.  Others are religious nuts who hate science as it counters religion.  They&#39;ll find any excuse to discredit global warming and climate change as to protect their profit, and gain the support of those who disapprove man-made climate change, mostly members of the Republican Party.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;inhofe.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Jim Inhofe&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; id=&quot;inhofe&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;In Washington D.C., it snows virtually every winter.  Doesn&#39;t prove a thing.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;Enter Jim Inhofe, the senior Republican Senator of Oklahoma and for some reason, the chair of the Senate Committee on Environment and Public Works.  Senator Inhofe has long been a denier of climate change, and a cold winter day on February 26, 2015, Senator Inhofe blasted global warming as a hoax.  His reasoning: It was snowing outside.  He even brought in a snowball to a Congressional Hearing to back up his claim, because according to him, how can we have global warming when it&#39;s so cold outside.  So despite average temperatures trending upward since the 1970s, does Inhofe&#39;s snow theory hold up?&lt;/p&gt;
		
		&lt;p&gt;Anyone with half a brain knows it doesn&#39;t get hot in our Winter. Since the Earth&#39;s rotated at 24.5 degrees, we have different seasons and when our axis is away from the sun, it gets colder as opposed to the axis being towards the sun, when it gets hotter.  Yet Senator Inhofe thinks Global Warming only makes things hotter.  A native Portlander, I have seen many winters come and go in Portland with little to no snow, despite a decently cold temperature.  When I was younger, I saw a lot more snowy days in Portland.  Now, we&#39;ve had just a few years with any major snowstorms.  As you can see from the graph below, I&#39;ve compared snowfall levels of both Portland and New York City (where it is more likely to snow), and looking at the data, doesn&#39;t prove that Global Warming doesn&#39;t exist.&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;p&gt;As the data below shows, there is no reason to believe that snow has anything to do with global warming.  In fact, Portland shows a drop in snowfall over the years.  The snowstorm of 2008-2009 was a freak snowstorm for us here in Portland; we had not seen that much snow in that year.  But as the data shows, we in Portland saw little to no snow during the rest of that decade.  It&#39;s true that Portland doesn&#39;t represent the United States as a whole, but by Inhofe&#39;s thinking, there would be little to no variation in the yearly data.  Looking at the data for New York City, there&#39;s no variation in snow levels, varying year to year.  But this has nothing to do with temperature.  On the flipside is Phoenix, where it rarely, if ever, snows.  Senator Inhofe&#39;s snow argument wouldn&#39;t get much muster in Phoenix.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;I can&#39;t tell you where Senator Inhofe gets his ideas from.  But as someone who gets plenty of campaign money from the oil and gas industries, it would come as no shock if his opinions are being paid for.  After all, these companies are polluting the air with little regard to the environment.  But while that factor will always be there, it&#39;s Inhofe&#39;s religious stance that may be a greater cause of concern.  In 2012, Inhofe cited the Bible as irrefutable proof that climate change isn&#39;t man-made.  His quote: &lt;em&gt;&quot;[T]he Genesis 8:22 that I use in there is that &#39;as long as the earth remains there will be seed time and harvest, cold and heat, winter and summer, day and night.&#39; My point is, God&#39;s still up there. The arrogance of people to think that we, human beings, would be able to change what He is doing in the climate is to me outrageous.&quot;&lt;/em&gt; But really, why would God choose 2014 to become the hottest average temperature on the existence of Earth since they started measuring, and then break that record the following year.  Some things are easier to identify and prove than with God&#39;s will.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;h3 id=&quot;title&quot;&gt;Snowfall from 1871-2009 in New York City and Portland&lt;/h3&gt;
	&lt;div id=&quot;info&quot; style=&quot;width: 1100px;&quot;&gt;
   	&lt;div id=&quot;keys&quot;&gt;
      	&lt;p&gt;
            &lt;span class=&quot;key&quot; style=&quot;background: steelblue;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
            &lt;span class=&quot;key-text&quot;&gt;Portland&lt;/span&gt;
         &lt;/p&gt;
         &lt;p&gt;
         	&lt;span class=&quot;key&quot; style=&quot;background: green;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
         	&lt;span class=&quot;key-text&quot;&gt;New York&lt;/span&gt;
         &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;	
	&lt;script src=&quot;//d3js.org/d3.v3.min.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
	&lt;script&gt;

var margin = {top: 20, right: 20, bottom: 30, left: 50},
    width = 960 - margin.left - margin.right,
    height = 500 - margin.top - margin.bottom;

var formatDate = d3.time.format(&quot;%Y&quot;);

var x = d3.time.scale()
    .range([0, width]);

var y = d3.scale.linear()
    .range([height, 0]);

var xAxis = d3.svg.axis()
    .scale(x)
    .orient(&quot;bottom&quot;);

var yAxis = d3.svg.axis()
    .scale(y)
    .orient(&quot;left&quot;);

var pdxLine = d3.svg.line()
    .x(function(d) { return x(d.date); })
    .y(function(d) { return y(d.pdx); });
    
var nycLine = d3.svg.line()
    .x(function(d) { return x(d.date); })
    .y(function(d) { return y(d.nyc); });    
				
var svg = d3.select(&quot;body&quot;)
	 .append(&quot;svg&quot;)
    .attr(&quot;width&quot;, width + margin.left + margin.right)
    .attr(&quot;height&quot;, height + margin.top + margin.bottom)
  	 .append(&quot;g&quot;)
    .attr(&quot;transform&quot;, &quot;translate(&quot; + margin.left + &quot;,&quot; + margin.top + &quot;)&quot;);


d3.tsv(&quot;data/data.tsv&quot;, type, function(error, data) {
  if (error) throw error;
  
  x.domain(d3.extent(data, function(d) { return d.date; }));
  y.domain(d3.extent(data, function(d) { return d.nyc; }));

  svg.append(&quot;g&quot;)
      .attr(&quot;class&quot;, &quot;x axis&quot;)
      .attr(&quot;transform&quot;, &quot;translate(0,&quot; + height + &quot;)&quot;)
      .call(xAxis);

  svg.append(&quot;g&quot;)
      .attr(&quot;class&quot;, &quot;y axis&quot;)
      .call(yAxis)
    .append(&quot;text&quot;)
      .attr(&quot;transform&quot;, &quot;rotate(-90)&quot;)
      .attr(&quot;y&quot;, 10)
      .attr(&quot;dy&quot;, &quot;.71em&quot;)
      .style(&quot;text-anchor&quot;, &quot;end&quot;)
      .text(&quot;Snowfall (inches)&quot;);
  		
  svg.append(&quot;path&quot;)
      .datum(data)
      .attr(&quot;class&quot;, &quot;pdxLine&quot;)
      .attr(&quot;d&quot;, pdxLine);
 
 	svg.append(&quot;path&quot;)
 		.datum(data)
 		.attr(&quot;class&quot;, &quot;nycLine&quot;)
 		.attr(&quot;d&quot;, nycLine);
 
});

function type(d) {
  d.date = formatDate.parse(d.date);
  d.pdx = +d.pdx;
  d.nyc = +d.nyc;
  return d;
}

&lt;/script&gt;
	
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/Adams-Blog/climate-change-and-snow</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/Adams-Blog/climate-change-and-snow</guid>
        
        
        <category>politics,</category>
        
        <category>environmnent</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why I Voted for Hillary Clinton</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
	&lt;p&gt; At the end of this year, the United States is going to elect a new President, as Obama’s two terms reaches its end.  With that said, it’s important to me that we continue to make progress in building our country&#39;s economy, security and social progression.  The Republican’s presumptive candidate is Donald Trump, billionaire entrepreneur and reality TV star.  I will never vote for Donald Trump; he attracts the worst kind of attention and has led the most hateful campaign ever.  But it was much more difficult to choose between Hillary Clinton and Bernie Sanders, her Democrat competition for the Democratic nominee.  Though both candidates have their strengths and weaknesses, in the end I am throwing my support behind Mrs. Hillary Clinton.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Neither Hillary nor Bernie excite me as a candidate in the same way Barack Obama did back in 2008.  When Hillary Clinton announced her candidacy, most people assumed she was easily win, but Bernie surprised many by mounting an amazing grassroots style campaign that would make Obama envious.  I salute Bernie Sanders for bringing up many of the issues I consider the biggest detriments to a successful country; corruption of the Elite class, Citizens United allowing unlimited cash flow to candidates, and a power structure that favors money over the people.  Our problems are bigger than the issues themselves, with the structure of Congress and its ridiculous rules preventing any progress from happening.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float:left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/hillary.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Hillary Clinton&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Hillary Clinton isn’t perfect, but no candidate is&lt;/h4&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;But when it comes to ideas, Bernie Sanders’ ideas sound too good to be true and unrealistic, and to me, ideas are important.  As Comedian Dave Chappelle once said on his hit sketch show Chappelle’s Show, “Complex problems require complex solutions.”  And it’s true, it’s not as simple as ‘Free education for all’ or ‘Medicare for all’ as Bernie Sanders has suggested as solutions to raising the middle class.  While these things sound nice, they’re unattainable and unrealistic.  It’s for this reason that I didn’t vote for Bernie Sanders in the Democratic Primary.&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;blockquote class=&quot;blockquote-reverse&quot; style=&quot;font-size: 24px; border:none&quot;&gt;
Complex problems require complex solutions
		&lt;footer&gt;Dave Chappelle&lt;/footer&gt;
	&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the flip side, Hillary Clinton isn’t perfect as a candidate, and there are characteristics I certainly don’t like about her, but yet many of the issues the Republicans keep talking about are mere distractions and unimportant to the Presidential race.  The obvious issue the Republicans keep trying to convince us is the worst attack in our lifetime (nevermind 9/11) is the Benghazi attack.  Though it was tragic to see four men die in the attack, including our Ambassador to Libya, Chris Stevens, to hear Republicans say it, Hillary all but invited the terrorists involved to make the attack, and even though they have held numerous wasteful hearings trying to find out ‘the truth’, they’ve accomplished nothing but proven what a political witch-hunt this has become.  As House Majority leader Kevin McCarthy infamous stated, “Everybody thought Hillary Clinton was unbeatable, right? But we put together a Benghazi special committee, a select committee. What are her numbers today? Her numbers are dropping. Why? Because she’s untrustable. But no one would have known any of that had happened, had we not fought.”  Clearly, the issue is political partisanship at its worst, and yet, Hillary Clinton has held her own against United States House Select Committee on Benghazi chairman Trey Gowdy, never buckling down from hours of pointless and repetitive questions.  Republicans know she’s strong and know she’s a threat to taking over the Presidency chair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote style=&quot;font-size: 24px; border:none&quot;&gt;
Everybody thought Hillary Clinton was unbeatable, right? But we put together a Benghazi special committee, a select committee. What are her numbers today? Her numbers are dropping. Why? Because she’s untrustable. But no one would have known any of that had happened, had we not fought.
&lt;footer&gt;Kevin McCarthy, House Majority leader&lt;/footer&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second issue which Republicans keep talking about is the e-mail issue.  Hillary Clinton may have used a private server for using her personal e-mail address for official government uses, which sounds naive and irresponsible at best, but with laws on e-mails and record keeping were evolving at the time, it’s unclear whether Hillary broke any actual laws.  That’s not to say other politicians have done similar, whether it’s Condoleeza Rice, Colin Powell or Jeb Bush.  Yet no one cares ever bothered to investigate them like Hillary has been by the Republicans.  Same with Benghazi.  Thousands of people died on 9/11; if Al Gore were president, the Republicans would have spent eight years investigating him.  It’s their only recourse against a woman who’s not only strong but has the balls to take them on head-on.  Republicans claim this is a major trust issue, as many who don’t like Hillary don’t trust her, but Politicians on the whole are untrustworthy.  Every politician lies, and Hillary Clinton is no less untrustworthy than her opponents or friends, so as Bernie Sanders said during the first Democrat debate, “The american people are sick and tired of hearing about her [Hillary&#39;s] damn emails.”  Please, give me a break.&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;blockquote class=&quot;blockquote-reverse&quot; style=&quot;font-size: 24px; border:none&quot;&gt;
The american people are sick and tired of hearing about her damn emails!
		&lt;footer&gt;Bernie Sanders, regarding Hillary Clinton&#39;s email use&lt;/footer&gt;
	&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bill Clinton was the best president of my lifetime.  He did great wonders for the United States, and his centrist Liberal views were a plus for me.  Being married to Bill Clinton for many years, I would hope that Hillary has learned a thing or two from Bill on how to get things done.  To me, that is one of her biggest strengths; her unrelentless approach.  But unlike Bill, Hillary seems more willing to shift her views to make herself appeal to the Progressive left.  This would be fine for a Progressive, but I don’t consider myself that Liberal.  Bernie Sanders has pushed her towards his direction for better or worse.  And yes, Hillary has a goofy personality, kind of like Joe Biden but with a stronger aggressive side, which kind of turns me off.  However, with that aggressive personality is the ability to get things done, which she has accomplished throughout the years as Senator and Secretary of State.  Her experience with National Security issues is a plus, which is something the Republican candidate can’t say.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/trump3.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Donald Trump&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Infinite Thumbs Down - Anyone But Trump&lt;/h4&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best reason to vote for Hillary Clinton, is that despite all her faults with her personality and trustworthiness, she’s not Donald Trump.  Donald Trump would be a complete disaster as President of the United States.  Virtually everyone around the world can’t stand the guy; the only person who seems to like him is our supposed #1 geopolitical foe, Vladimir Putin of Russia, who like Trump is a bully incapable of listening to anybody.  Trump would make our country a joke, with other countries unwilling to work with a chauvinistic greedy xenophobic divisive putz.  We need someone who is serious about fixing our problems, rather than someone who thinks this is all a joke, like Trump has proven over and over again.  Having an unpredictable loose cannon that acts like a five year old when being criticized is a poor quality and completely unpresidential.  It’s not as easy as making mindless chants and gimmicks; being President requires intelligence and great decision making, something Donald Trump does not have.  Although Hillary Clinton is not the most mature person out there, anyone is better than a spoiled child who expects everyone to say ‘Yes’ to him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump is a poor businessman at best, lame reality TV star at best, and a horrible Presidential candidate who has completely destroyed the Republican party’s credibility.  America deserves better than this.  Truth be told, we’re screwed no matter who’s President; we still have incompetent Senators, Congressmen and Congresswomen who bicker like babies and refuse to work with each other in an attempt to win the game.  But we’ve made progress with Obama despite the Republicans obstructionist ways, despite the Recession left over from George W Bush’s Presidency.  We can’t replace Obama with an idiot who doesn’t know where Obama was born, thinks the Chinese invented global warming to improve their economy, acts like non-white foreigners are the root of all our nations problems, and most important, an idiot who has never given a damn about anyone else in his life other than himself.  Vote Hillary Clinton for President.  Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/Adams-Blog/why-i-voted-for-hillary-clinton</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/Adams-Blog/why-i-voted-for-hillary-clinton</guid>
        
        
        <category>politics</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to Adam&#39;s Blog 2.0 - The Rise of Jekyll</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;img/mthood.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Mt. Hood&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Mt. Hood&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learning new ways to make blog posts or any developing tools in general is something I have always enjoyed.  It&#39;s something encouraged by IBM, the parent company I work for.  With that said, I am revamping my blog post as its own entity, rather than part of the Express framework I&#39;m using for Bodie Web Design.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are the advantages of doing this, you ask?  Let me explain the ways to you in the most simplistic ways.  This new blog engine is powered by Jekyll, a static website generator powered by Ruby.  With it, I have more flexibility as to how I can layout my blog.  Gone are the days of sticking to one layout as I have been doing with my Jade-JSON backed blog posts.  Now I can use markdown files, which translates raw text to HTML.  For example, I would have to make parse my blogs with JSON, like in the first example below, then would retrieve those values with the Jade templating language, as seen in the second example below to convert them into html.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-javascript&quot; data-lang=&quot;javascript&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Example&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;err&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;title&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;err&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Example&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;date&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;err&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;May 4, 2016&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;description&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;err&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[{&lt;/span&gt;
                &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;paragraph&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hello World, I&#39;m a paragraph in JSON!&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
            &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;},&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
                &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;paragraph&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi Foobar, I&#39;m another paragraph in JSON!&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
            &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;],&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;image&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;err&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[{&lt;/span&gt;
                &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;name&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;img/image.jpg&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
                &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;caption&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;I&#39;m a caption!&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
            &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;}]&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-jade&quot; data-lang=&quot;jade&quot;&gt;.article
	- for (var x = 0; x &amp;lt; post.description.length; x++)
   - var y = x / 3       
   	if post.description[x].paragraph !== undefined
      	p #{post.description[x].paragraph}
      	p I&#39;m Jade!
         &lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Though this got me thinking code and algorithms, it also limited my flexibility, having to follow a set pattern for each post I made.  Not to mention the quotation marks for each piece of JSON code.  Enough to drive you mad.  JSON is easier to read than XML, but the quotation marks are maddening.  But with Jekyll, I can make my posts with pure raw text in markdown files, which are converted to HTML.  Now I can have the freedom to add additional content in my posts without having to write code in the html files being outputed from the markdown files.  Want to add a random h4 header?  All I got to do is this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt; I&#39;m an H4 header &lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Want to make an H4 header green, I can do this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 style=&quot;color: green&quot;&gt; Now I&#39;m a green H4 header&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt; And all I did was add html to my markdown file, rather than make some funky rule in my Jade Template to apply for one instance, check this out:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-html&quot; data-lang=&quot;html&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;h4&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;style=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;color: green&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; Now I&#39;m a green H4 header&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;/h4&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;   &lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another big change you&#39;ll see right off the bat is that my blog is now paginated.  Instead of everything on one page, it is now broken off to 10 posts per page.  At the time of this post, that&#39;s 4 pages of blog posts.  Much easier to navigate, less code to load, and a better, faster experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The possibilites are endless with Jekyll, and expect to see more power with my blogs and posts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/Adams-Blog/welcome-to-adams-blog-2</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/Adams-Blog/welcome-to-adams-blog-2</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ted Cruz - The Definition of Pathetic</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; I&#39;ve seen and read about many bad politicians in my lifetime.  Former Senator Trent Lott, who in 2002 claimed we’d be better off had we voted for racist Senator Strom Thurmond is one.  Former Illinois Governor Rod Blagojevich attempts to sell Obama’s Senate seat and other criminal activities is another.  Former Florida Congressman Mark Foley and his sexually explicit texts to teenage boys was also disturbing, along with the many congressmen and politicians who’ve cheated on their spouses, i.e. Newt Gingrich, Eliot Spitzer and Anthony Weiner.  But despite all those with questionable ethics, criminal policies and downright slanderous misgivings, no politician has or ever will be more pathetic, manipulative, uncooperative or untrustworthy than Senator Ted Cruz.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;img/booger.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Ted Cruz ate a booger.  Thanks sis for the reminder.&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Ted Cruz ate a booger.  Thanks sis for the reminder.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ted Cruz was elected as Senator for the ‘great’ state of Texas in 2012, part of the Tea Party’s wave of extremist anti-Obama candidates who think working for him and the Democrats is ‘part of the problem’.  Yet in short time, Ted Cruz has proven that he is self-centered, uncaring for anyone except his followers (though in reality he only cares about himself) and willing to destroy anything in his path just to get his way, alienating virtually all of his fellow Senators and Congressmen and Congresswomen in the process.  His extreme hatred for Obamacare was the main culprit, as Ted Cruz became popular amongst extremists and despised by everyone with a brain by partially shutting down the Government in a pathetic attempt to get rid of Obamacare.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Democrats controlling the Senate and Obama the President, there was no way they would agree to Ted Cruz’s demands to fund the Government without Obamacare.  Ted Cruz surely knew this, as a graduate cum laude at Princeton.  Yet to hear him say it, it was all the Democrats fault for shutting down the Government for two plus weeks, and would have done it again if he could.  Why?  Because they wouldn’t go along with his demands.  As if the Democrats would blindly do something he likes and get nothing in return.  But that is the Republican’s mantra these days, and Ted Cruz is the King of the Obstructionists in congress, the public face of the Tea Party extremists who think all Liberals have to do as they say or else, and should do everything according to the Bible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like any politician willing to do whatever to get people on his/her side, Ted Cruz frequently lies about just about everything.  He repeats the same lie over and over again and his fellow supporters will assume it&#39;s true, even though anyone who actually researches the topic at hand knows it&#39;s completely bogus.  The supporters WANT these things to be true, even when it&#39;s clearly the opposite that is true, so they’ll just assume it’s true.  Cruz plays into their fears and into their hands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;img/trust.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Trust: the last word anyone should associate with Ted Cruz.&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive pull-right&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Trust: the last word anyone should associate with Ted Cruz&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;p&gt;One of Cruz’s favorite lies is about Obamacare, which he believes is a catastrophic bill that has done nothing but kill jobs. Problem is, we’ve seen more jobs created since the inception of Obamacare than we’ve lost jobs.  Though the economy was quite bad when Obamacare first passed due to the Recession, it&#39;s ridiculous to claim it&#39;s killing jobs when the economy has grown since then. Yet Ted Cruz, on a personal mission to do anything to get rid of Obamacare, makes up reasons it&#39;s bad, repeating false claims and furthering using his manipulative ways to misinform his followers on what Obamacare actually is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ted Cruz can easily criticize just about every other politician or wannabe politician, saying ridiculous and often bogus claims, pointing out others flaws, whether true or not and shows little remorse for his words.  But when someone attacks him, my god, someone call the police! Cruz attacks Obama almost daily yet when Obama disagrees with something he suggests, such as the US-Iran deal, Ted Cruz suggests it’s outrageous for Obama to criticize him behind his back, and quote-unquote, should say it to his face, threatening to fight him in the process.  And being locked into a battle with Donald Trump, has managed to take mudslinging to a whole new level.  We need mature candidates, not those who act like fifth graders.  It&#39;s unfortunate that we live in the age of trash-talk TV and controversy sells, as Cruz takes advantage of the times by acting childish and idiotic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But despite all of these characteristics, the thing that is most irritating about Ted Cruz is his narcissistic intolerant attitudes towards others, waging war on those who stand in his way, making false claims about those he doesn&#39;t like, and his sincere belief that everything must be done according to the Bible.  These characteristics are more fitting for a terrorist than a politician, yet Ted Cruz continues to attack his enemies as Un-American, wrong on everything and somehow not deserving the same rights as Christians.  Cruz bashes any idea that’s Liberal, claiming most criminals are registered Democrats, which isn’t remotely true.  He claims Muslims are trying to take over the country with Sharia law, and that we need constant surveillance on all Muslim neighborhoods.  Cruz’s answer for this; make everything Christian-like.  But Ted Cruz’s biggest war is against the LGBT community, whom Cruz feels shouldn&#39;t have the same rights as Christians, that it&#39;s okay for them to be denied services and marriage while claiming Christians are the ones suffering by not being able to deny services to the LGBT community.  Despite the law being against his side and same-sex marriage being legalized, Cruz will try to convince you it&#39;s a states right issue and rewrite the Constitution in the process.  Too bad the Supreme Court overruled a ban on interracial marriage back in the day.  Maybe Cruz needs to read up in history rather than try to redefine it.  And now with the battle waging against transsexual bathroom use, Cruz claims keeping them out of their preferred bathrooms will keep little girls safe from grown men.  Too bad this isn&#39;t about grown men, it&#39;s about transgendered women who will look out of place in a men’s bathroom, as if it’s okay to tell them;  ‘Hey, I’m only in here because of what’s underneath my underwear, come and get me.’ ALL people have rights to live their lives freely, not just Christians. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;img/zodiac.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Ted Cruz isn&#39;t the Zodiac Killer...he&#39;s worse than the Zodiac Killer!&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Ted Cruz isn&#39;t the Zodiac Killer...he&#39;s worse than the Zodiac Killer!&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ted Cruz has all the qualities of at worst, a terrorist and at best, a controlling husband.  Would he treat his wife the way he treats his fellow congressmen and congresswomen?  It doesn&#39;t work in a marriage, why would it work in the Senate?  He thinks he can do whatever he wants and expects everyone to follow him.  People can appreciate him for standing up to their values, but we live in a world that wants results.  Ted Cruz accomplished NOTHING.  All he did was make himself look better, and that’s the only thing Ted Cruz has ever cared about, the man in the mirror.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I am writing this blog, news broke that Ted Cruz officially dropped out of the race, having been beaten pretty badly in Indiana.  My first two words were: Good Riddance.  My next three words, pardon my language, is: Good Fuckin’ Riddance.  Ted Cruz has been nothing but a complete disaster as a Senator, Presidential candidate, and as a person.  And even though we are left with Donald Trump as the Republican candidate, whose racist comments and ridiculous lies are just as bad if not even worse than Ted Cruz’s, I can truly say that Ted Cruz is far worse than Donald Trump, mainly for being such a religious extremist.  Whether Donald Trump is genuinely pathetic or pretending is in question; it’s not a question for Ted Cruz.  I never thought Ted Cruz would even make it this far, but the result was as predicted, Americans have rejected Ted Cruz the same way his fellow Senators and Congressmen have.  So here’s to you Congressman Peter King, who can get rid of the cyanide he jokingly claimed would take if Cruz won the nomination.  Here’s to you Senator Lindsey Graham, who could very well now shoot Ted Cruz and not get convicted.  Here’s to you Satanists who roundly reject Ted Cruz as a Satanist even though John Boehner referred to him as ‘Lucifer in the Flesh,’ proving that perhaps Ted Cruz is even more evil than Satan himself.  Here’s to those who think Ted Cruz is the Zodiac Killer, you can move on and live your lives freely and in peace.  And of course, to all the American’s who are open to other people’s opinions and respect people who aren’t like them, this one’s for you.  Good bye Ted Cruz.  The fight to completely remove him from public office and out of our lives begins today!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/Adams-Blog/ted-cruz-the-definition-of-pathetic</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/Adams-Blog/ted-cruz-the-definition-of-pathetic</guid>
        
        
        <category>politics</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Don&#39;t Be Stupid on the Internet</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last night was the first round of the NFL Draft, a time for the best ranked prospects to join the NFL, a joyous time for those to hear their name called. Yet in this day and age, being stupid sells, and being stupid on the Internet never goes away no matter how hard you try. That&#39;s why all the buzz today is around Laremy Tunsil, a highly ranked offensive tackle who ended up falling to the 13th pick to the Miami Dolphins, as someone allegedly hacked into his Twitter account and posted a video of him smoking a bong through a gas mask earlier in the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;img/tunsil.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;This should have been the highlight of Laremy Tunsil&#39;s night, but everyone&#39;s talking about the bong.&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;h4&gt;This should have been the highlight of Laremy Tunsil&#39;s night, but everyone&#39;s talking about the bong.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;p&gt;People are going to be stupid, you can&#39;t stop that.  But being stupid on the Internet is a big mistake.  Once something gets posted online, it never goes away, it exists in some form of data and will follow you for the rest of your life, like a bad tattoo.  For Laremy Tunsil’s case, his Twitter account was closed just minutes after the video hit the web, yet anyone reading about the NFL Draft or the news in general has already seen an image of said video, knowing it exists.  That never goes away no matter how hard you try.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s true that people have the right to post things they think are cool, like smoking pot through a bong.  That doesn&#39;t mean people should post things like that, especially if it&#39;s illegal.  Unfortunately for Tunsil, his Instagram was hacked later that night, posting a cell conversation with an Ole Miss staff member about payments, which as anyone knows, is a major violation in college football.  Tunsil manned up and admitted what he did, but the fallout will be far worse than that, with investigations at Ole Miss likely to start because of this.  Why anyone would ever save a text message talking about rule-breaking is also stupid, as any smart person knows not to leave a trail of any kind.  Digital trails are especially easy to track in this day and age.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This doesn&#39;t just apply to athletes and celebrities, who are more likely to be targeted for their fame, but anyone can say something stupid online, often controversial, sometimes illegal suggestions.  Miles away from the NFL Draft, John Martin Ross, a 61 year old man from Medford, Oregon was arrested for threatening President Obama.  Among the evidence found, online rants complaining about Obama and suggesting Obama should be shot and killed.  This dumb gentleman has a right to complain about Obama, but that doesn&#39;t mean he should use such strong language.  Anyone can read it and call the cops if violence is implied.   A search warrant to his house led to the discovery of pipe bombs, setting this dumb gentleman up for even more harsh punishment, and as the owner of the words he said online, they can be used against him in the court of law.  Mr. Ross wrote on his Facebook: “I guess you can’t tell the world you hate Obama so much you will shoot him.”  And it’s true, you can’t.  Why?  Because threatening to shoot someone is not only immoral but illegal.  The First Amendment doesn’t protect you from it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Social media posts tell a lot about people, probably more info than needed.  If you&#39;re willing to share your thoughts publicly, anyone can access them, from strangers to employers, so on.  You own your thoughts, and sharing them comes with consequences if not handled properly.  Of course, it comes with great responsibility as well.  Don’t want people to see you smoking a bong but want to show your friends?  Make it private, or better yet, show them in person.  Be smart.  Thinking about harming someone? Only an idiot would share their thoughts with someone else, especially online.  The more that people know, the less successful you&#39;ll be at pulling it off.  And it&#39;s definitely not the way to get attention.  Texts come at face value, no sarcasm or emotion appears with said text.  So please, next time you want to put something stupid on the Internet, don&#39;t do it.  It could cost you dearly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, people like Laremy Tunsil and John Martin Ross are becoming more common these days than not.  These days, news spread like wildfire and anyone can say something that can become viral in seconds.  For people of a certain celebrity like Tunsil, there’s always a price to pay for being famous, and that is that people will find anything against you to humiliate you because of fame and jealousy.  It’s up to them at the end of the day to find a balance between living life freely and avoiding missteps.  As for common people like John Martin Ross, it all comes down to knowing that you’re not invincible.  People often post negative stuff online to avoid physical confrontation with other people, thinking they can’t be caught without a care in the world.  But when stupid people bring up violence, chances are the good people will do the right thing and report you.  Sadly, in these days, when children are learning to swear at younger ages and adults are voting for Presidential candidates who often say derogatory things, social media brings out the worst in people and the stupidest thoughts.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/Adams-Blog/dont-be-stupid-on-the-internet</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/Adams-Blog/dont-be-stupid-on-the-internet</guid>
        
        
        <category>technology</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Curse of Donald Sterling Lives</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Growing up, I didn&#39;t think much of the Los Angeles Clippers. Why should I have? They were a complete joke, a bumbling group of losers who couldn&#39;t win squat, couldn&#39;t put together a decent roster and worst of all had an incompetent owner who wouldn&#39;t spend any money to keep what little talent they had. It wasn&#39;t until the other owners handed them Chris Paul in an effort to keep him from being traded to the Laker did the Clippers finally start to look like a real basketball team. But as the Lakers sunk to the floor, have the Clippers overtaken them? Not even close. No matter how talented the Clippers are, they’ll always be in second place, and incapable of winning the title. Whether they like it or not, they are defined by their disgraceful former owner Donald Sterling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;img/sterling.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Everything Clippers related is tied to Donald Sterling, the joke.&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;h4&gt;Everything Clippers related is tied to Donald Sterling, the joke.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The Clippers had an obvious crisis two years ago when Donald Sterling was recorded making numerous racist remarks about his fans, bringing the Clippers to national headlines, as people were disgusted with their idiotic owner and the players angry over the comments as well.  Even after kicking Sterling to the curb and being bought by Microsoft billionaire Steven Ballmer with his own money, the Clippers are still losers compared to the Lakers, even if they’re winning more than the Lakers.  They haven&#39;t completely shaken the bad aura of Donald Sterling, affecting their attitude and play in the process, often finding themselves on the wrong end of disappointment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Clippers have never made it to the Western Conference finals, let alone the NBA finals in their history, from their foundings as the Buffalo Braves to their unnoticeable years as the San Diego Clippers and of course, as the ‘Donald Sterling joined L.A. because he couldn’t beat the Lakers, so he joined them‘ Los Angeles Clippers. They had a chance last year but blew a 3-1 lead against Houston.  Typical Clippers blunders, one joke after another, and had home court advantage to boot after 4 games.  This despite having a talented roster led by Chris Paul and Blake Griffin, who rank as two of the most talented players in the NBA.  And this year, with a possible chance to play Golden State without Steph Curry, they manage to lose both Blake Griffin and Chris Paul for the season in the same game. Beating Portland just became a lot tougher, if they can even do that at all.  But one has to wonder how the Clippers keep messing things up?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They have a great coach in Doc Rivers; the only coach with NBA title winning pedigree, maturity and understanding of the Donald Sterling mess, really the only coach capable of bringing the team together and sympathizing with their plight as well.  Chris Paul is an elite point guard, great leader and the heart and soul of the team.  You’d think those two would bring the character the Clippers need.  Instead, they have obnoxious, selfish players who gloat like Blake Griffin and DeAndre Jordan.  Blake Griffin, the guy who broke his hand punching an assistant trainer in a stupid fight, costing him a month of action. DeAndre Jordan, who waffled between leaving for Dallas and staying with the Clippers, loving every minute of the attention he got via the so-called Emoji Wars.  Unfortunately, it&#39;s these two who carry the team&#39;s me-first Lob City gloating attitude that makes the Clippers the underachieving team they are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Lakers never acted like that during any of their prime years.  Yet the Clippers seem to casually stroll into games like it doesn&#39;t care, lacking the instinct to perform to its potential.  They wouldn&#39;t even be a playoff team without Chris Paul; he’s the only player with heart, which goes without saying.  Is it because of Donald Sterling’s past influence? The feeling they’ll never pass the Lakers in prestige?  Maybe their key players are immature cry baby&#39;s with questionable character flaws.  Whatever the case, it&#39;s apparent that while Steve Ballmer can throw a whole bunch of money to try to make the Clippers a serious team, they&#39;ll never get rid of the curse that is Donald Sterling. So while Laker fans are saddened by their team&#39;s recent struggles, it compares nothing to being the sad joke that is the Los Angeles Clippers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/Adams-Blog/the-curse-of-donald-sterling-lives</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/Adams-Blog/the-curse-of-donald-sterling-lives</guid>
        
        
        <category>basketball</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Oregon Primaries - Ted Cruz need not apply</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As we&#39;re weeks away from Oregon’s Primary election, May 17th, it has become clear that for the first time in ages, Oregonians everywhere will actually have a say for the primaries. As one of the last states, the candidate has typically been decided before April, but this year we’re in a dead heat on both sides of the puzzle. With Kentucky the only other state with their primary the same day, Oregon at last will get the attention it needs for determining each party&#39;s nominee for President.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;img/donkey.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Don&#39;t we all wish we could do that to Ted Cruz.&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;h4&gt;Don&#39;t we all wish we could do that to Ted Cruz.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Obviously, Oregon is a Liberal state; it&#39;s going to vote Democrat for the Presidential election no matter who wins the race.  Hillary Clinton and Bernie Sanders are the two choices to pick from.  Hillary Clinton stands out as a former Senator, First Lady and Secretary of State, yet her campaign isn&#39;t as strong as it should be, with issues of trustworthiness being a big concern.  Bernie Sanders, an Independent Senator from Vermont and admitted Socialist, has come seemingly out of nowhere to pick up support from the Progressives who hate the fact that the system is rigged to favor the millionaires and billionaires.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet there are conservatives in Oregon as well, and they have their candidates.  Donald Trump leads the way with his big mouth and frequent racist divisive comments, yet Republicans are trying anything they can to keep him out of office. Ted Cruz, the religious nutcase Senator from Texas who hates to compromise, shows no appreciation for non-conservative thoughts and seems to hate everyone that&#39;s not Christian is also in the running. John Kasich, the Governor of Ohio, hangs on by a thread, hoping for a contested convention as he’s only won his home state, despite being the most traditional candidate left and the most reasonable of the bunch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can&#39;t say I&#39;m excited about any of the candidates, but I know one thing I am determined to see: that neither Donald Trump nor Ted Cruz get elected as President.  Both of these men (if we can even call them men, they act like a bunch of babies) are ridiculously unqualified and share absolutely pathetic views on the world, not to mention their hate filled speech.  I&#39;m not crazy about either Hillary or Bernie but either one would be an easy choice over those two dweebs. John Kasich is a decent man but is lucky to be where he is and lacks charisma to get people to vote for him.  With the Republicans being so angry, I would be shocked if they settled on Kasich since he’s actually willing to compromise to get things done, an apparent no-no with Republicans these days.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;img/bernie.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Millionaires and Billionaires hate Bernie Sanders.&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;h4&gt;Millionaires and Billionaires hate Bernie Sanders.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;As a native Oregonian, I can tell you proudly that Ted Cruz would not like our state at all, at least the Portland area.  So as news rolled last night that the Kasich and Cruz campaigns have apparently agreed to coordinate primaries to best keep Trump from gaining the magic number of delegates, it was no surprise that Cruz agreed to let Kasich have Oregon and New Mexico in exchange for Indiana.  Whether Cruz actually follows through or stabs Kasich in the back as he does with everyone else remains to be seen, but Cruz has no chance to win Oregon’s Republican primary.  With the largest percentage on non-religious people per capita in the state and a largely Progressive population, Ted Cruz would have a better chance convincing Oregonians he’s actually a woman than he does of convincing them to vote for him.  For once, I’ll thank Ted Cruz for not even bothering showing up to my home state.  It’s embarrassing enough to have him living in the same country as I do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our system for electing politicians, creating rules and regulations and basically everything tied to the government is broken, corrupt and filled with greed.  Bernie Sanders has emphatically made that the centerpiece of his campaign, and I have much respect for Bernie for mentioning this as the big problem.  With the passing of Citizens United in 2010 allowing unlimited cash flow to campaigns, it’s easy for those without money to get any say at all, having their voices drowned out by money and big corporations.  Gerrymandering congressional districts designed to drown out minority voters, prejudice tactics to keep people from voting and congressional rules that prevent bills from even reaching the floor have turned our system into a cesspool for corruption.  Bernie Sanders inspires people to understand the voice for the common man, which is why people are enthusiastic for him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the downside to Bernie Sanders is his ideas of fixing the broken system.  I wish we could live in a Utopia like he offers, with free healthcare, free college tuition, $15.00 plus minimum wage, and a total dismantling of the millionaires and billionaires of Wall Street.  But it’s never going to happen.  We’re always going to have Republicans on the other side who find these ideas too expensive and burdensome for the wealthy.  Like it or not, some Republicans have decent ideas and fiscally speaking, they’re worth at least exploring as a compromise; unfortunately, their voices are drowned out by the extremists unwilling to negotiate and expecting their way.  This is where Bernie Sanders ultimately fails to me.  I don’t see him having the balls to be aggressive and standing up to these Republicans if leading the way.  Another issue I have with Bernie is my appreciation for moderation.  Nothing about Bernie economically says moderation.  It’s all about attacking Wall Street and their rich snobs.  While it’s true they are driven by greed and power, I also find it necessary for us to work together, not pit sides against another.  We need to find ways to work with them for more business friendly ideas to improve the economy.  Like anything, being in the middle represents the best of both worlds, and the only realistic way to get anything done.  To me, Hillary Clinton would be an easy choice for this except for her sometimes brash personality and somewhat goofy immature attitude she displays.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;img/hillary.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Republicans REALLY hate Hillary Clinton.&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;h4&gt;Republicans REALLY hate Hillary Clinton.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Hillary Clinton, unlike Bernie Sanders, is more well-rounded with experience on all sides of the issues, from economic to foreign policy issues, and clearly has the personality to get things done, never afraid to fight.  But yet her ideas are average at best, as she’s being drawn further to the left to fend off Bernie Sanders’ obvious charismatic ways.  I know Hillary Clinton would be better handled to tackle on foreign policy issues, a big concern of mine with her experience as Secretary of State, and she has more balls to tackle on the Republicans across the aisle, but Republicans have an extreme hatred for Hillary Clinton and would treat her as they have Obama for the past seven years.  Unfortunately, I’m not convinced Hillary would be any more willing to reason with them than they would with her.  During the first Democratic debate, Hillary declared Republicans as her favorite enemy, kind of an immature thing to say to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But in terms of ideas, her beliefs are more reasonable, such as improving Obamacare to be more cost friendly rather than completely revamp it as a single-payer system with Medicare for all, which again, sounds nice, but isn’t realistic.  They aren’t nearly as far-fetched as Bernie Sanders extreme ideas.  But yet, Hillary doesn’t excite me at all.  Her personality is a turnoff for me, and I do consider her somewhat of an opportunist, changing beliefs to better fit her electorate rather than being the more centrist Democrat her husband Bill was, which made him the best President of my lifetime, in my opinion (keep in mind I was born in the Reagan days).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m confident both races in Oregon will be one-sided.  Oregon is ripe with Progressives who love Bernie.  Most bumper stickers I see are for Bernie Sanders, and it’s no surprise for me.  Bernie will beat Hillary easily, with the young white electorate far outweighing the minority support which Oregon doesn&#39;t have much of.  The Republicans are less clear but Donald Trump fits the angry Republicans better than Ted Cruz the religious nutcase.  The fact he would let John Kasich have a better opportunity says that Ted Cruz could never win our state, he could only win the state if he was the only candidate, and even then he would barely beat ‘Other’. So Donald Trump is the likely winner on the Republican side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the end, while my heart says Bernie Sanders is the best choice, for understanding people’s frustrations with the system the best, my brain says Hillary Clinton for providing the most realistic approach to solving problems and being the most experienced person to handle our problems.  Whether I should follow my heart or my brain is the big issue I haven&#39;t settled completely on yet.  The rest of me says anyone but Donald Trump or Ted Cruz, as those two imbeciles would turn our country into a joke.  In the end, that&#39;s the most important thing to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/Adams-Blog/the-oregon-primaries-ted-cruz-need-not-apply</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/Adams-Blog/the-oregon-primaries-ted-cruz-need-not-apply</guid>
        
        
        <category>politics</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Day the Music Died Part 3</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When people refer to “The Day the Music Died,” they are referring to the tragic death of Buddy Holly, Ritchie Valens and the Big Bopper when they perished in a plane crash outside of Clear Lake, Iowa on February 3, 1959. Yet years later, we’ve lost many musicians with a far bigger influence. With apologies to Elvis Presley, John Lennon, everyone in the “27 Club” (Jim Morrison, Janis Joplin, Jimi Hendrix and more recently, Amy Winehouse), we’ve seen two deaths in the music world truly crushing since that day. The second was of course, Michael Jackson’s tragic death on June 25, 2009, and the third was today, as Prince passed away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;img/prince.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Prince embodied sexiness for men.&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive pull-right&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;h4&gt;Prince embodied sexiness for men.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those who have followed Prince’s music, know him as the definition of eclectic, reaching all aisles of the music spectrum blended perfectly to a sound known simply as the ‘Minneapolis Sound.’  Whether it was rock, R&amp;amp;B, pop, whatever it was, Prince knew just how to make the perfect harmony with a mesh of styles.  As a music enthusiast and a well-known perfectionist, Prince was and is the defining artist for those aiming to reach all aisles of the map.  Many artists today, including Andre 3000 from Outkast and Janelle Monae are often compared to Prince for their various stylings of music.  But none of them can be Prince.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prince also had an extreme flair for fashion and performances, well known for his overtly sexually charged performances and somewhat raunchy live-shows.  But yet Prince always knew the appropriate way to reach his platform.  His performance at the Super Bowl halftime show in 2007 was the best performance I’ve ever seen.  Many others including Billboard Magazine agree, as Prince showcased his electric styling of his songs and covers of other songs, which concluded with Purple Pain while it was actually raining, creating the perfect purple glow from the lighting.  But Prince also had more intimate surprise shows perfect for the smaller crowd.  Prince had everything covered when it came to performance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first song I ever purchased on iTunes was ‘When Doves Cry,’ a classic example of Prince’s Minneapolis Sound and one of his biggest hits, from the album that pushed him to superstardom, Purple Rain.  A soundtrack of a movie of the same name starring Prince as ‘The Kid,’ though I thought the movie was somewhat corny, based somewhat on his life, it’s the music that people most remember about Prince.  Though Prince’s acting career didn’t last too long, his music never stopped, spanning from 1978 till today, featuring classic hits including ‘When Doves Cry,’ ‘Purple Rain,’ ‘1999,’ ‘Raspberry Beret’ and many more.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;img/prince2.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Prince knew how to rock it!&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive pull-right&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;h4&gt;Prince knew how to rock it!&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Another one of Prince’s well-known qualities was his quest for musician ownership rights and creative freedom.  He famously squabbled with his record label Warner Bros. for ownership and control of his music, changing his name to an unpronounceable symbol (people referred to him as ‘The Artist formerly known as Prince’).  To many, Prince was an idol in the music industry for standing up to his bosses and demanding creativity and freedom.  Of course, the flip side of this was that Prince did everything he could to keep his music off the Internet, demanding fansites taken down and performances removed from sites like youTube as Prince wanted compensation for his works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet despite all of this, virtually everyone is saddened by Prince’s passing.  From musicians, entertainers, athletes and even the politicians, chances are people right now are sad to see Prince go, probably listening to his past hits, wondering what the heck happened.  I always considered it my dream Halloween costume to dress up like Prince, complete with the purple suit, guitar and wild hair.  That would have been the dream for me, but I could never pull it off, sadly.  It would have been mind-blowing.  As an adopted Minnesotan, having gone to school at the University of Minnesota, I remember seeing First Avenue, driving by Paisley Park in Chanhassen, all while blasting his music.  He will be missed.  Heaven just got a lot funkier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/Adams-Blog/the-day-the-music-died-part-3</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/Adams-Blog/the-day-the-music-died-part-3</guid>
        
        
        <category>music</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mamba Out - The Aftermath</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s true what they say, Kobe always know how to put on a show. The second half of his final game was no exception. As I watched Kobe take shot after shot after shot, I wondered if he was really trying to reach 50 points. The announcers mentioned that could be the case in the first quarter. I would have been happy with 40 points. The plan was to sit Kobe the first half of the fourth quarter. That didn’t happen. Suddenly, the race to 50 was on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;img/kobe9.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Kobe&#39;s the man, fighting to the very end.&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;h4&gt;Kobe&#39;s the man, fighting to the very end&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a man who was always told to pass the ball, in this game, everyone was passing the ball to him and telling him to shoot.  And he did, repeatedly.  No wonder I mentioned Marcelo Huertas in the first part of the blog multiple times.  As the game drew closer to the end, Kobe kept making shots, and with some nice dunks from Larry Nance Jr. and some other great plays, the crowd was going nuts.  Then Kobe reached 51 point with a layup with under two minutes left.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Miraculously, the game was close and the Lakers actually had a chance to win it.  Down by 6, I jokingly thought to myself, ‘Kobe is aiming for 60 points, not 50.’  A couple of shots made later, he actually had a shot at that goal.  I was shocked, he looked tired, playing 42 minutes at 37 years old, but Kobe has made a career of playing with lots of pain.  A few shots later and with Utah missing a bunch of shots, Kobe reached the free throw line with two free throws needed for 60.  He made them both easy-peasy, giving them a three point lead.  After a steal from Kobe on the next play, he threw it down court to Jordan Clarkson for the slam, putting the icing on the cake.  Kobe left the game for the last time with 4 seconds left as the Lakers won 101-96 in a thrilling game, finishing an incredible 60 point game.  Sure, Kobe took 50 shots, but it was his last game, so who cares.  Haters can hate.  A Nike commercial starring Kobe made that clear, he loves the hate, he feeds off the hate.  When it was all said and done, I stood up and applauded a fitting farewell for Kobe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the game, Kobe gave hugs to multiple former players (even the obscure former players from the past, Devean George, Chris Mihm, Ronni Turiaf and a plethora of others long forgotten, along with the big stars and his family).  After the balloons went down, Kobe got to address the fans one last time, thanking the fans, his journey playing twenty years for his favorite childhood dream, and honoring the bad years as his favorite for all the hard work and never giving up.  He ended his speech simply put ‘Mamba out.’  Close to how I ended my blog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;img/kobe10.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;All the stars out to watch, for a great reason.&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;h4&gt;All the stars out to watch, for a great reason.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;p&gt;As I sit back and reflect on it all, it amazes me just how competitive Kobe was.  There was no other like him, he drove off the pain, the bad games, the fans jeering, it just made Kobe more determined.  The NBA will miss that for sure.  Too many players now want Super Teams to make it easy on themselves.  LeBron ran from the hard times, ran from home to play in Miami, only to realize it was a mistake despite winning two Championships and went back to Cleveland.  But instead of fighting through it, he complains.  No wonder Kobe’s had more success.  But that’s another subject to debate.  And of course, on the same night the Golden State Warriors won their 73rd win to break the single-season record, it’s Kobe who proved again who the real star was.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where do the Lakers go from here?  How will it be for me rooting for them without the one constant they’ve had since I was 11?  This season was nothing more than the Kobe Farewell show, and they knew it.  They had their lowest wins in a season ever, even less than last year&#39;s worst season ever.  They have young talent, lots of cap room and hopefully a top three pick in the NBA Draft (here’s hoping they get the Number 1 pick).  But getting a high class free-agent will be almost impossible since there’s no one ready to be a superstar now.  They will need to build through the draft.  D’Angelo Russell showed potential to be a star; hopefully not having Kobe around will let him blossom.  He needs to mature both on and off the court, but Kobe wasn’t exactly great at 19 years old.  Jordan Clarkson is a solid player worth keeping, with both the heart and talent to succeed.  Julius Randle has some freakish talents but like Russell is quite young and not yet mature.  The rest of the team is give and take; Roy Hibbert is useless and off the books, won’t be back.  Nick Young is terrible for Byron Scott’s style of play (if Scott even remains as coach, not a given), and being secretly recorded by Russell for no good reason left him hurt.  Lou Williams is a nice bench player but would probably want a better team to play for.  Larry Nance Jr. showed nice energy and has great dunking abilities (like his dad).  No one else stands out in any way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now for a quick review of the NBA Season, from the highlights to the lowlights.  Here are my picks for MVP, Defensive Player of the Year, Rookie of the Year, Coach of the Year, Sixth Man of the Year, Most Improved, Surprising Team and Disappointing Team of this season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;img/kobe11.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Kobe took many jumpers.  The ones he made got the crowd rowdy.&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;h4&gt;Kobe took many jumpers.  The ones he made got the crowd rowdy.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The Rookie of the Year goes to the #1 pick Karl Anthony Towns of the Minnesota Timberwolves.  I admit, I was wrong about him.  He’s been a much better player than I thought.  He’s got potential with Andrew Wiggins and Zach LaVine to make the Minnesota Timberwolves relevant.  Also considered: Kristaps Porzingis of the New York Knicks, Devin Booker of the Phoenix Suns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Coach of the Year goes to Terry Stotts of the Portland Trail Blazers.  No one thought Portland would be any good after losing most of their key players, but with Damian Lillard leading the way and the rapid rise of CJ McCollum, Terry Stotts proved his worth as a coach, leading Portland to the #5 seed in the West with lesser talent than last year.  Also considered: Steve Kerr/Luke Walton of the Golden State Warriors (Walton of course filled in half of the season while Kerr was recovering from surgery), Brad Stevens of the Boston Celtics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sixth Man of the Year goes to Jamal Crawford of the Los Angeles Clippers.  Not a particularly strong year for sixth man, but Crawford has always filled the role quite well.  Also considered: Andre Iguadola of the Golden State Warriors, Will Barton of the Denver Nuggets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;img/curry.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Steph Curry&#39;s offensive game looks like Kobe&#39;s game ten years ago.  His time is now.&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive pull-right&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;h4&gt;Steph Curry&#39;s offensive game looks like Kobe&#39;s game ten years ago.  His time is now.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Most Improved Player of the Year goes to CJ McCollum of the Portland Trail Blazers.  Loaded with lots of potential but not getting much of a chance, McCollum stepped into the role of Damian Lillard’s sidekick, exploding with a 20.8 points per game average, and keeping the Blazers out of rebuilding mode.  Also considered: Isaiah Thomas of the Boston Celtics, Draymond Green of the Golden State Warriors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Defensive Player of the Year goes to Kawhi Leonard of the San Antonio Spurs.  A defensive freak of nature and capable of guarding just about everyone, Kawhi Leonard knows how to lock players down.  The Spurs struck gold with him, go figure.  Also considered: Draymond Green of the Golden State Warriors, Hassan Whiteside of the Miami Heat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Surprising Team of the Year goes to the Portland Trail Blazers.  Considered an afterthought losing most of its core, Portland stayed afloat with the sudden rise of CJ McCollum.  Especially difficult in the Western Conference.  Also considered: Boston Celtics, Charlotte Hornets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disappointing Team of the Year goes to the Chicago Bulls.  Loaded with talent but seemingly missing something, they fired Tom Thibodeau and hired young coach Fred Hoiberg, hoping to improve.  Instead, the Chicago Bulls fell flat on their face and missed the playoffs all together.  A major shakeup needs to occur for the Bulls to be title contenders.  Also considered: New Orleans Pelicans, Washington Wizards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MVP goes to Steph Curry. 30 points a game, 50% field goals made, 40% three pointers made (400 for the whole season), 90% free throws made and 73 wins.  Enough said.  Can anyone stop this guy?  He makes the craziest shots look so damn easy.  Can anyone else really be considered for MVP?  For the sake of being consistent, also considered: LeBron James of the Cleveland Cavaliers and Russell Westbrook of the Oklahoma City Thunder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/Adams-Blog/mamba-out-the-aftermath</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/Adams-Blog/mamba-out-the-aftermath</guid>
        
        
        <category>basketball</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mamba Day and Everyone&#39;s Celebrating</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Never thought this day would come, but all good things must come to an end. For Kobe Bryant, his final day is today at home, against the Utah Jazz. Here are my thoughts watching the finale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;img/kobe6.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;One last time...it&#39;s Kobe&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;h4&gt;One last time...it&#39;s Kobe&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s 7:26 PM and the video tribute just started.  Reliving all the great memories Kobe has had, from his alley-oop to Shaq in Game 7 of the 2000 Western Conference Finals to his 81 point game against Toronto in 2006.  Kobe has had plenty of great moments, after 20 years it’s hard to remember all of them.  Some forgotten I had to re-remember still look glorious to this day, game-winners against Miami, Portland and Phoenix, among others, still look amazing and surreal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now Magic Johnson’s speaking.  One Laker great speaking about another, and well spoken as usual.  It’s true, Kobe is the best celebrity LA has had in the past 20 years, and everything Kobe has accomplish, he deserves the title of Mr. Laker, truth be told.  Put it simply, he’s the best to wear the Purple and Gold.  I’ve never seen Kobe smile as much as I’ve seen now.  And for Magic Johnson’s proclamation of Kobe’s 81 point night, I was in living in Eugene at my apartment.  My Dad had come to visit that night, and we had sushi for dinner.  My Dad’s no Laker fan but he always rooted for them in the NBA Finals when they won 5 Championships (and lost 2), so I’ll take that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now the official video starts with Shaq speaking.  After everything they went through, it’s great to see Shaq and Kobe on good terms.  Derek Fisher, Kevin Durant, Dwyane Wade, Dirk Nowitzki, Gregg Popovich, Kevin Garnett, Carmelo Anthony, Steph Curry, LeBron James, Pau Gasol, Lamar Odom, Phil Jackson, Jack Nicholson all had great things to say about Kobe.  It about brings me to tears.  It’s true what they say, you can’t really appreciate something until it’s gone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;img/kobe2.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;All the great legends know how great Kobe is&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;h4&gt;All the great legends know how great Kobe is&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And at 7:34 PM, Kobe enters the court with everyone chanting ‘Kobe, Kobe, Kobe!’  A great thing to hear, from the past, everyone chanted ‘MVP, MVP, MVP!’ even when he didn’t deserve it.  But Kobe’s the Laker’s MVP, the all-time leading scorer, owner of multiple records, both team and league records.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, at 7:40 PM, the announcer starts his usual announcement.  Unfortunately, this game will be boring and pointless, especially since Utah was just eliminated from the last playoff spot.  But first, Laker fan Flea plays the National Anthem on the guitar.  Sounds like a weird rendition of Jimi Hendrix’s National Anthem.  Obviously, Flea can’t sing (nor be an effective Nihilist, thanks Coen Brothers for The Big Lebowski), but I would have preferred someone singing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At 7:43 PM, the visitors get announced, yawn!  I was really hoping Houston would miss the playoffs, dang Houston.  Now Laker teammates are talking on video, Julius Randle, D’Angelo Russell, Metta World Peace, Jordan Clarkson and the others, along with coach Byron Scott.  It’s a shame the Lakers have been so bad the past few years, and here comes Kobe on the floor for the last time.  The biggest cheers from an otherwise unenthusiastic announcer.  And now, we can begin an otherwise forgettable game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;img/kobe4.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Kobe&#39;s killer instinct was lethal to those who tried to stop him&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;h4&gt;Kobe&#39;s killer instinct was lethal to those who tried to stop him&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Game just started at 7:48 PM, and a minute later, Kobe missed his first shot of the game.  Meanwhile, this has been a crazy season for the NBA.  At this time, on ESPN, compared to this game on ESPN, the Golden State Warriors are seeking an NBA record 73 wins!  They are one scary team; if they can keep their core of Steph Curry, Klay Thompson, Draymond Green and Andre Iguadola, they can be the NBA’s next dynasty.  Watching the Lakers now, they suck, and suck for a reason.  Now Kobe’s 0-3, despite a nice cutting of the lane, he missed the layup.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At 7:54 PM, the Lakers finally scored with 7:05 remaining, with a Roy Hibbert dunk.  Remember a few years ago when Roy Hibbert nearly led the Pacers to beat the Miami Heat in the Eastern Conference Finals?  That was such a distant memory.  Now Hibbert’s as useful as tits on a boar, especially with the game becoming so guard-oriented.  But he has four points, with the Lakers down 6-4 with an ugly start to a game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At 8:01 PM, I return to my room from the bathroom.  Of course, Kobe hit three of a row in 58 seconds while I was in the bathroom taking care of my bathroom needs.  Now Kobe just hit a long two, and the crowd goes wild, and just hit a three just about 20 seconds later.  By the way, Jay-Z’s in the house, can he at least try to smile?  Next possession, Marcelo Huertas gives the ball the Kobe like he’s supposed to and took an impossible three pointer, which almost went in.  Kobe just wants to shot and put on a show.  He should, he won’t get another chance.  Also, Golden State’s up 27-16 at this point as they seek history, and Steph Curry has 17 already.  He’s a special player to say the least.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;img/kobe7.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Kobe&#39;s come a long way from 20 years&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive pull-right&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;h4&gt;Kobe&#39;s killer instinct was lethal to those who tried to stop him&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At 8:06 PM, we see a video of Kobe announcing coming to the NBA and getting selected in the 1996 Draft by the Hornets.  Thank god the Lakers traded for him.  20 years later, here we are.  No player has spent more years with one team than Kobe; that’s what make Kobe the best Laker of all time, even with all the elite players they’ve had; Magic, Kareem, Wilt, Shaq, James Worthy, Jerry West, Elgin Baylor, etc.  Kobe reaches the free throw line for the first time, hitting three free-throws.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And with the first quarter over, Kobe already has more points (15) than he did in his last road game a couple nights ago against Oklahoma City.  He’s scored the team&#39;s last 15 points.  And a perfect opportunity to show his new AppleTV commercial with actor Michael B. Jordan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second quarter starts at 8:14 PM with buckets from Larry Nance Jr. and Tarik Black(?!?).  Kobe’s on the bench, as the plan is to apparently to play him the whole 1st and 3rd, and half the 2nd and 4th.  Larry Nance Jr. was a decent surprise, high energy guy.  A nice finish by Jordan Clarkson for his first points makes it a 26-25 game. Golden State’s up 44-29 at this point.  Only a miracle would prevent them from losing this game.  I wouldn’t be surprised if they sweep the playoffs.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;img/kobe3.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Young, old, Kobe could do it all&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;h4&gt;Young, old, Kobe could do it all&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;At 8:22 PM, an interview from the Number 1 Laker Fan of all time: Jack Nicholson, rockin’ the red sunglasses.  One of the few games he missed, the 81 point game!  And the crowd nearly erupted from Larry Nance nearly making a posterizing slam, but he reached the free throw line, but that would have been sweet if he made the dunk.  Nice layup from Marcelo Huertas, and now Kobe goes to the bleachers to get ready to enter the game.  Cheers!  8:26 PM, with 6:14 seconds in the second quarter, after a Utah air-ball, Kobe is back in the game, and quickly chucks a bad three pointer.  He could make those in his prime, but unfortunately, not now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back to the action at 8:30PM, with the Lakers down 38-31, and video shows Kobe slapping hands with Shaq.  It’s great to see them two together.  Those were the best times ever in Laker history.  And Kobe with the bucket driving by Gordon Hayward for what would’ve been a slam dunk in his prime, but just a layup.  It’s a shame Kobe tore his achilles in 2013, everything went downhill after that.  Now Kobe has 21 points with the second quarter winding down at 2:45 left in the quarter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At 8:38PM, a list of people in attendance is mentioned by the announcers; Snoop Dogg, Gary Payton, Baron Davis are the names I remember, all to see Kobe, along with Shaq, Frank Robinson, George Lopez and Jay-Z, along with Jack.  And a sweet behind the back pass from Kobe to Jordan Clarkson leading to a Julius Randle slam was just what the Lakers needed before the half.  And at 8:42PM, the first half comes to an end, with Kobe at 22 points, 8-20 from the field, and the Lakers predictably down 57-42.  At least we get to celebrate something.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;img/kobe8.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Thanks for the Memories!&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive pull-right&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;h4&gt;Thanks for the Memories!&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;And with that, I’m closing up the Live Blog shop for the night.  It’s been a long day for me, and I need to relax for another day of work.  But part two of my season ending Mamba Fest will be here in due time.  Black Mamba and out!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/Adams-Blog/mamba-day-and-everyones-celebrating</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/Adams-Blog/mamba-day-and-everyones-celebrating</guid>
        
        
        <category>basketball</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
