<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adam's Blog</title>
    <description>A blog about whatever is on Adam's mind.</description>
    <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 16:52:36 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 16:52:36 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Skittles - A Poor Analogy to Describe Humanity</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Today, Donald Trump Jr., son of the racist bigot Idiot whom he's named after, again proved that racism is learned, much like his racist father and grandfather, by making this ridiculous analogy about Syrian refugees: &quot;If I had a bowl of Skittles and I told you just three would kill you.  Would you take a handful?&quot;  Aside from being moronic and overly simplistic, statements like this are a perfect example of why racial profiling is flat out wrong.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/Skittles.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Skittles&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Skittles, just candy&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As Mars, Incorporated, the makers of Skittles pointed out, &quot;Skittles are candy; refugees are people.&quot;  Anyone who wants to treat human beings as candy is purely stupid and ignorant.  Skittles are all made the same way, have the same ingredients, the only difference is their color and taste.  But even amongst those flavors, each flavor is made the same and are supposed to be the same.  Two yellow Skittles are the same.  Two red Skittles are the same as well.  Human beings on the other hand, are complex individuals with unique DNA, personality and other characteristics that makes them one unique human being (twins aside, but that's an exception to the rule, not a commonality).  A human being with brown hair, white skin and green eyes is always going to be different from another human being with brown hair, white skin and green eyes due to the complexity of human beings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Treating people like candy is the perfect metaphor for racial profiling.  By definition, racial profiling is judging people based on characteristics.  Most times, it's a person's negative characteristics that's used for racial profiling.  It doesn't matter how good a person is, to some, it's better to assume they might be bad to catch the bad ones than it is to treat them all as good and let a bad one get through.  This might work with candy; if a bad batch is made, you can simply throw it out and make a new batch, but this doesn't work with human beings.  You can't simply recycle or throw away human beings like you would with candy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The actions of a few cannot be used to judge an entire group of people.  It's not true about candy nor is it excuse to discriminate against other human beings.  Yet some claim it's the only way to stop terrorism.  A better way is to do what we currently do, judge each person individually, not judge them based on perceived characteristics which may or may not be true about said individual. That way, a person can be judge by all of their characteristics, not just their appearance.  Unfortunately, some people will often harbor negative feelings towards someone solely based on the color of their skin.  In the case of Syrian refugees, it's based solely on their Islamic faith, which some people make their decision primarily based on skin color.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There's always the chance someone falls through the cracks; there's nothing we can do to stop that.  But that doesn't mean we can't deny rights to the many that are good hard-working human beings.  After all, the defining characteristic of a person with the intent to commit a crime is not their skin color, nationality nor religion, it's their intent to commit a crime.  Racial profiling does nothing but lead people to only be on the lookout for a certain group of people.  Any person is capable of committing a crime.  But while racists will judge a terrorist like Ahmad Rahami of being representative of all Muslims, these same people will not make the same comparison for terrorists like Dylann Roof to all white people.  To them, a good Muslim is worse than a bad Christian.  But that is simply not true.  The people these racists will assume as Muslims may not be even Muslim as all, the gentleman who spotted Ahmad Rahami shares a similar skin complexion, but is a Sikh, whom share no connection with Muslims whatsoever.  Racial profiling is not only wrong but ineffective, since skin color doesn't define a person's religion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next time you want to eat some Skittles, just remember they're just candy.  Mars Incorporated does the best it can to ensure the quality of their product.  It's entirely possible a stale Skittle makes it in the pile, but it isn't likely to happen.  That doesn't mean you should never eat Skittles again or throw out every bag of Skittles in your cabinet because one might make you sick in your stomach.  This wouldn't be acceptable with candy, and this is not the way Syrian refugees should be treated to, as they are human beings with far more complexities than your average piece of candy.  So while Donald Trump Jr. should probably stay away from Skittles as he will likely be paranoid that someone will give him poisoned candy over his stupid and ignorant comments, the rest of us can enjoy candy and know it's just that, candy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/09/20/skittles-a-poor-analogy-to-describe-humanity</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/09/20/skittles-a-poor-analogy-to-describe-humanity</guid>
        
        
        <category>politics</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Football Week Three Thoughts</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.basket h4 {
    text-align: center;
    border-bottom: 1px solid black;
}
.basket h3 {
    text-align: center;
}
&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Week 3, unlike the week before, featured a lot of challenging match-ups, and for the first time ever, the Top 3 ranked teams in the AP poll play on the road against other ranked teams.  Alabama at Ole Miss, Florida State at Louisville and Ohio State at Oklahoma.  Safe to say, champions are made here.  Other plenty of entertaining games abound.  So what happened on Week 3?  Here are my thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/buffaloes.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Colorado Buffaloes&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Gotta love the Colorado Buffaloes&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The action started early on Saturday, with Lamar Jackson and Louisville hosting Florida State in a Top Ten match-up.  But by halftime, this game was anything but, as Louisville completely obliterated Florida State at home with a 63-20 romp.  Lamar Jackson proved to be the real deal, with five touchdowns (four rushing) against the Seminoles, as they made Florida State look just as bad as Charlotte and Syracuse.  Safe to say Lamar Jackson will now be the favorite to win the Heisman Trophy (with apologies to Christian McCaffrey).  Florida State made an impressive comeback against Ole Miss the first week but Louisville never stopped.  Very impressive.  The only thing I didn't like were their chrome helmets.  Aside from the butterfly on the back to honor hometown legend Muhammad Ali, I didn't like their helmets especially the white logo.  But at the end of the day, Florida State lost ugly, just like they did at the Rose Bowl against Marcus Mariota and the Oregon Ducks.  Ouch!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float:left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/bison.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;North Dakota State Bison&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;North Dakota State Bison quarter Easton Stick.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another great match-up was Iowa vs. North Dakota State.  It's rare to call an FBS-FCS match-up exciting but as five time defending FCS champs, North Dakota State is not your typical FCS team.  It was certainly a big gamble for them to play at Top 15 team like Iowa, but North Dakota State played like a Big Ten team, pulling off the upset 23-21, with a field goal as time expired to win it.  North Dakota State played a bruising style of game, wearing Iowa out in the end, scoring the last nine points of the game.  North Dakota State became the first FCS team since Eastern Washington upset Oregon State in 2010 to beat a ranked FBS team.   Especially impressive against a team that made the Rose Bowl last year.  I'e always been impressed with the Bison from my time at Minnesota, and they could easily contend in the FBS if they wanted to.  They've won 6 straight against the FBS which says a lot, and they certainly aren't afraid of anybody.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Appreciate it &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/WinTheDay&quot;&gt;@WinTheDay&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;✊ &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/SF27?src=hash&quot;&gt;#SF27&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/po22PweKtf&quot;&gt;pic.twitter.com/po22PweKtf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Nebraska Football (@HuskerFBNation) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/HuskerFBNation/status/777206703267786752&quot;&gt;September 17, 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Great match-up for Oregon as they faced Nebraska on the road in their first real test of the year, as well as Dakota Prukop's first challenge as FBS QB.  Before the game, Oregon laid some flowers at the 27 yard line in honor of their late punter Sam Foltz (who wore #27).  Very classy.  Way to go Oregon.  As for the game itself, it was a back and forth battle, but unfortunately, Nebraska won by 3.  Oregon had their chances, and their decision to go for 2 after each touchdown (they went 1-5 overall) was definitely puzzling to say the least, but you win some and lose some.  Oregon certainly plays bold as Mike Riley put it, but those types of missed opportunities along with a lot of penalties tilted the game in Nebraska's favor.  Dakota Prukop played well given the circumstances, but Royce Freeman got hurt on the first drive and didn't come back.  Despite the loss of Freeman, they didn't miss a beat with their running game.  Good game, but not the result Oregon wanted.  Up next, their conference opener against a much improved Colorado team.  Speaking of the Buffaloes...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Michigan played Colorado in a game that would've had no hype if not for the back and forth banter between the two schools.  Jim Harbaugh, hard-ass coach of Michigan with no sense of humor, refused to release his teams depth chart, believing in secrecy.  Colorado, in a humorous attempt to combat Michigan's lack of depth chart, released their own depth chart, with the likes of Elmer Fudd, Austin Powers and The Dude, which can only be described as hilarious and clever.  Possibly the funniest thing I've seen a team do, who cares if Jim Harbaugh found it unfunny.  In fact, their twitter feed as a whole was quite hilarious.  As for the game itself, Colorado played fairly well considering their recent past and playing Michigan at home.  They jumped out to a lead, but Michigan stormed back, winning 45-28.  They're not the joke they were when they entered the Pac-12, and Oregon shouldn't take them lightly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float:left; max-width: 450px&quot;&gt;
		&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;In case you haven&amp;#39;t seen this week&amp;#39;s depth chart.  What and who is in your favorite position? &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/GoBuffs?src=hash&quot;&gt;#GoBuffs&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/19qUmVyO6P&quot;&gt;pic.twitter.com/19qUmVyO6P&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Colorado Football (@RunRalphieRun) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/RunRalphieRun/status/775718135315980288&quot;&gt;September 13, 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
        &lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Penn State did the inappropriate thing and honored Joe Paterno, fifty years after his first game, or forty years after he was first allegedly told that disgraced assistant Jerry Sandusky was molesting little boys.  Coaching aside, Joe Paterno did nothing and many suffered.  Some Penn State fans obsession with honoring Joe Paterno is absolutely sickening. --- Speaking of inappropriate, in last night's match-up between Rice and Baylor, the Rice marching band 'honored' Baylor's recent controversy by forming IX, a reference to Title IX.  Seems Rice is known for parody marches.  They certainly need something since Baylor easily won 38-10 ---  This week, Clemson was on the right side of a boneheaded play as South Carolina State kick returner Ahmaad Harris inexplicably handed the ball to a referee without taking a knee.  Clemson pounced on the ball to score a touchdown.  Clemson won the game 59-0 in a game that was shortened by six minutes as the two agreed to a mercy rule (to shorten said game) --- Alabama finally solved its Ole Miss problem, needing a 21-point comeback to win 48-43.  I hate Nick Saban.  I hate Lane Kiffin.  And now that Steve Sarkisian joined the staff, I hate him too.  --- Western Michigan got paid $210,000 to play Illinois and subsequently won 34-10.  They're 2-0 against the Big Ten this year, that's what I call highway robbery.  Double salute to the departed John Saunders.  --- USC is 1-2 for the first time since Pete Carroll's first year.  Another reason why USC is stupid and pathetic.  Every year it's the same story of what great talent they have all because they're USC.  And they never live up to the expectations and lose.  With that said, here are my picks for Top Ten:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alabama&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ohio State (+2)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Louisville (NR)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michigan (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clemson (-2)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stanford (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Houston (-1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michigan State (NR)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Washington (NR)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Florida State (-8)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And now as a bonus, in honor of Colorado's fake depth chart, here is my fake depth chart consisting of some of the pathetic people out there, for a team I call &quot;The Basket of Deplorables.&quot;  Starring who else but the Republican Presidential Candidate as starting Quarterback, his biggest ass kisser Chris Christie as fullback and handing the ball off to his favorite dictator in Vladimir Putin as running back, you'll be completed disgusted with this depth chart.  Thanks Colorado for the fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row basket&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h3&gt;The Most Pathetic Football Team Ever:&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;h3&gt;The Basket of Deplorables&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
        &lt;h4&gt;Offense&lt;/h4&gt;
        
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wide Receiver&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;6 Drake&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;9 Future&lt;/p&gt;
        
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Left Tackle&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;65 Rush Limbaugh&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;52 Glenn Beck&lt;/p&gt;
        
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Left Guard&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;68 Wayne LaPierre&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;76 Roger Ailes&lt;/p&gt;
        
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Center&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;33 Kim Jong Un&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;54 Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi&lt;/p&gt;
        
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Right Guard&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;41 Ammon Bundy&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;43 Ryan Bundy&lt;/p&gt;
        
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Right Tackle&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;75 David Koch&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;80 Charles Koch&lt;/p&gt;
        
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tight End&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;23 LeBron James&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;0 Kevin Love&lt;/p&gt;
        
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wide Receiver&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;22 Justin Bieber&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;27 Chris Brown&lt;/p&gt;
        
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Quarterback&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;11 Donald Trump&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;12 Mike Pence&lt;/p&gt;
        
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Running Back&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;28 Vladimir Putin&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;24 Bashar al-Asaad&lt;/p&gt;
        
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fullback&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;54 Chris Christie&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;72 Rudy Giuliani&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
        &lt;h4&gt;Defense&lt;/h4&gt;
        
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Defensive End (L)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;50 Suge Knight&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;47 Birdman&lt;/p&gt;
        
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Defensive Tackle (L)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;77 Frazier Glenn Miller Jr.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;66 David Duke&lt;/p&gt;
        
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Defensive Tackle (R)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;84 Joe Arpaio&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;31 George Zimmerman&lt;/p&gt;
        
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Defensive End (R)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;32 OJ Simpson&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;85 Roger Goodell&lt;/p&gt;
        
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weakside Linebacker&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;5 Kim Davis&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;22 Pat McCrory&lt;/p&gt;
        
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Middle Linebacker&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;17 Sarah Palin&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;15 Michele Bachmann&lt;/p&gt;
        
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strongside Linebacker&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;63 Mel Gibson&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;33 Tom Cruise&lt;/p&gt;
        
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sweet Cake Cornerback&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;45 Aaron Klein&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;43 Melissa Klein&lt;/p&gt;
        
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Not Really Free Safety&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;44 Ted Cruz&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;10 Rick Santorum&lt;/p&gt;
        
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spoiled Strong Safety&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;20 Brock Turner&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;19 Ethan Couch&lt;/p&gt;
        
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steal'em Cornerback&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;77 Bernie Madoff&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;30 Martin Shkreli&lt;/p&gt;    
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h4&gt;Special Teams&lt;/h4&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kicker&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;64 Terri Horman&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Punter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;1 'El Chapo'&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kick Returner&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;8 Ted Nugent&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Punt Returner&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;3 Dzhokar Tsarnaev&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Long Snapper&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;98 Jerry Sandusky&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Holder&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;2 Johnny Manziel&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;h4&gt;Coaches&lt;/h4&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Head Coach&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Pete Carroll&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Offensive Coordinator&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Lane Kiffin&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Defensive Coordinator&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Nick Saban&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/09/17/college-football-week-three</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/09/17/college-football-week-three</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Worst Politicians Currently in Office</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
    .row {
        border-bottom: none;
        margin-bottom: 0px;
        padding-bottom: 0px;
    }
&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Let's be honest, politics is dumb at its core and politicians are terrible.  Currently, Congress has an approval rating of about 10% or so.  Plenty of our current politicians couldn't figure their way out of a paper bag, much less pass meaningful, bipartisan legislation.  No matter who's elected President, Congress will always find ways to screw things up and stop real progress from happening.  With that said, here are the 15 worst members of Congress, and as an added bonus, the 5 worst Governors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h1&gt;Worst Congressmen (and Congresswomen)&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/joe-wilson.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Joe Wilson&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Joe Wilson&lt;/h4&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;h3&gt;15. Joe Wilson - South Carolina House of Representative - 2nd District&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;A rude and racist congressman who once yelled at Obama &quot;You lie!&quot; while Obama gave a speech on health care, Joe Wilson proved what a bozo he really is. Of course, Joe Wilson's racist approach to Obama was filled with hate and lies, as contrary to what Joe Wilson claimed, Obamacare does not provide healthcare to undocumented immigrants.  Democrats rebuked him, but Republicans protected him for something they'd complain about if a Democrat did the same thing to a Republican President.  Hypocrisy strikes again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/mike-lee.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Mike Lee&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Mike Lee&lt;/h4&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;h3&gt;14. Mike Lee - Utah Senator&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;All you need to know about Mike Lee is that he's Ted Cruz's sidekick.  Plus he single handedly stopped a bill giving financial relief to Flint, Michigan by claiming &quot;They have plenty of money.&quot;  If there's anyone willing to follow Ted Cruz, it's Mike Lee.  Despite lacking major recognition, that alone gets Mike Lee on the list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/mark-sanford.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Mark Sanford&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Mark Sanford&lt;/h4&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;h3&gt;13. Mark Sanford - South Carolina House of Representative - 1st District&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;As former Governor, Sanford lied to his people by claiming he wanted to take a hike on the Appalachians, only to go legally missing for six days in 2009 before turning up in Argentina with his mistress.  Yet years later, after his time as Governor ended, South Carolinians in the first district forgave him by electing him back into political office.  Surely, they wouldn't feel the same way about Bill Clinton's affair…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/lindsey-graham.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Lindsey Graham&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Lindsey Graham&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;12. Lindsey Graham - South Carolina Senator&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A man John McCain once called his illegitimate son due to their military based similarities, Lindsey Graham is far less likeable and hasn't accomplished nearly as much as John McCain. If it were up to people like Graham and McCain, we'd spend all eternity in the Middle East fighting their wars, we don't have a clue of how to make things stable without our intervention.  It's no wonder Lindsey Graham couldn't even get 1% Republican support in the Presidential race.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/marco-rubio.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Marco Rubio&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Marco Rubio&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;11. Marco Rubio - Florida Senator&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His values are decent but Marco Rubio is as untrustworthy and unreliable as they come.  He barely showed up to work as Senator, didn't want to run for re-election, but was pushed back in by external forces wanting to keep his seat and the Senate Majority Red.  His Presidential candidacy was predictable and uninspiring, going as far to insult Donald Trump's hand size.  Not the right message from someone who actually has Presidential material, but blew it acting like a child and ultimately lost his home state badly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/steve-scalise.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Steve Scalise&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Steve Scalise&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;10. Steve Scalise - Louisiana House of Representative - 1st District&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Steve Scalise, one of the highest ranking members in Congress, once spoke to a white supremacist group looking for support, claiming he didn't know he was speaking to a white supremacist group founded by the infamous David Duke.  He should've known better than associating himself with David Duke.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/jim-jordan.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Jim Jordan&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Jim Jordan&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;9. Jim Jordan - Ohio House of Representative - 4th District&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of two ultra conservative voices on the Benghazi committee, who didn't think their wasteful investigation into Hillary Clinton for the third time did enough to blame her, so he and fellow extremist Freedom Caucus member Mike Pompeo added to the Republican report nonsense blaming Hillary for something she didn't do.  Jim Jordan makes this list as the Chairman of the ultra-conservative Freedom Caucus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/rand-paul.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Rand Paul&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Rand Paul&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;8. Rand Paul - Kentucky Senator&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Good old Aqua Buddha, the pretend Libertarian, who fights for privacy rights yet thinks the Government can force a woman to remain pregnant, Rand Paul is a fake Libertarian wannabe who once called Obama gay for supporting gay marriage (obviously a homophobic slur meaning 'stupid,' not a belief Obama is actually gay).  Rand Paul had such little confidence of winning the Presidential election that he forced Kentucky to change its rules to allow him to run for Senate as a backup plan.  He obviously didn't make it past Iowa, as not surprisingly, Rand Paul couldn't convince his Dad's followers to support him like they did Ron Paul since he's a phony.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/joni-ernst.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Joni Ernst&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Joni Ernst&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;7. Joni Ernst - Iowa Senator&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Joni Ernst, just elected Senator, scares the crap out of me.  Her looks, her actions and goofy smile makes her creepy.  Anyone who thinks Obama is a dictator but ignores Donald Trump's love for dictators and desire to be a dictator doesn't know what the word dictator means.  As someone who claims her experience castrating pigs would make her perfect for cutting &quot;pork&quot; (wasteful spending), I have no clue why the fair-minded people in Iowa voted for her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/trey-gowdy.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Trey Gowdy&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Trey Gowdy&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;6. Trey Gowdy - South Carolina House of Representative - 4th District&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The current head of the United States House Select Committee on Benghazi, also known as the Hillary Clinton Witch Hunt, Trey Gowdy, who looks like a ghost, accomplished nothing with the Republican witch hunt, wasting millions of dollars to find absolutely nothing new, creating a report all by themselves so the Democrats couldn't say anything nice.  Even worse, he awkwardly questioned Martin Shkreli for his purchase of the secret Wu-Tang Clan album which led to a bizarre back-and-forth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/jim-inhofe.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Jim Inhofe&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Jim Inhofe&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;5. Jim Inhofe - Oklahoma Senator&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A man whose brain must be made of snowballs, as Jim Inhofe, who infamously brought a snowball to a congressional meeting on climate change to make the claim that the existence of snow disproves climate change altogether.  Only an idiot like him would come to that conclusion, clearly there are 4 seasons throughout the year due to the Earth's axis tilt, and it's going to be summer somewhere on planet Earth.  Even worse, Inhofe claims religion as the sole reason it's a hoax.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/steve-king.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Steve King&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Steve King&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;4. Steve King - Iowa House of Representative - 4th District&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Steve King, King of the Anti-Hispanics claiming to be the King of Anti-Illegal Immigration, is a hateful scumbag who recently claimed that only white people have contributed to Western Society.  For someone like Steve King, immigrants aren't livestock but human beings, and treating them like animals is inhumane.  Steve King is the worst member of the House of Representatives, frequently making racist and homophobic remarks, as well as inflammatory remarks about President Obama, claiming he's a Muslim savior.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/tom-cotton.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Tom Cotton&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Tom Cotton&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;3. Tom Cotton - Arkansas Senator&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Barely in his first term as Senator, Tom Cotton, the youngest member in the Senate, led the way to trying to interfere with the Iran deal by sending a letter to the Supreme Leader of Iran with 46 other Republican senators telling Iran any deal made with Obama can be taken away and that he had no authority to make such a deal.  This type of action is illegal and should be criminal to interfere with a deal they aren't negotiating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/mitch-mcconnell.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Mitch McConnell&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Mitch McConnell&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;2. Mitch McConnell - Kentucky Senator&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Senate Majority leader who promised Republicans would accomplish more with control yet has accomplished nothing but play games and rewrite the rules.  For a man who once made it his mission to make Obama a one-term President, Mitch McConnell refuses to hold a vote on a replacement for Justice Scalia, inventing rules of 'the American people need to vote for a new justice' (not their choice) while blaming Obama for his actions (not accepting Justice Alito in 2006 is not the same as not holding a vote on Justice Alito in 2006).  A terrible Senate Leader, the Democrats need to take majority back.  Even worse, he takes credit for something he had no involvement in (a rising economy which Republicans have consistently fought against).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/ted-cruz.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Ted Cruz&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Ted Cruz&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;1. Ted Cruz - Texas Senator&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Without a doubt the worst Senator of modern times, rivaling the infamous Joseph McCarthy as the worst of all time, a selfish degenerate who only thinks of himself and would have no problem destroying the very fabric of this nation just to get his way, as shown with his Government shutdown.  It's very clear that Ted Cruz lives to oppose everything Obama has done, he even voted against a bill once Obama supported it.  This man is the most hateful person ever, believing everything should be about Christianity, trampling over everyone who's not Christian.  Ted Cruz is well disliked by both parties and after his speech at the RNC, will have the biggest target on his back in 2018 when he's up for reelection.  This man is a cancer and needs to go now!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h1&gt;Worst Governors&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/chris-christie.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Chris Christie&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Chris Christie&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;5. Chris Christie - New Jersey&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chris Christie, the biggest opportunistic blowhard of them all, first doing the right thing by working with Obama for assistance with Hurricane Sandy, then complaining about Democrats after receiving negative comments from fellow Republicans, all to further his Presidential ambitions.  Chris Christie only cares about himself and will do anything, bashing Donald Trump during his own campaign but became Trump's biggest ass-kisser after he dropped out, desperate to be Vice President (which he didn't get). His mock trial of Hillary at the RNC was stupid and childish.  It's no wonder the people of New Jersey were so angry that they asked him to resign after endorsing Trump, in addition to their floundering economy.  And with the Bridgegate scandal hurting him despite his claims he knew nothing about it, chances are that's probably a lie based on his bullying ways.  Guilty of Not Guilty of being involved in Bridgegate?  Guilty!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/rick-snyder.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Rick Snyder&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Rick Snyder&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;4. Rick Snyder - Michigan&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rick Snyder, the Governor of Michigan, has led the city of Flint into a complete hell-hole thanks to his decision to change their water source for cost-cutting measures, all while refusing to spend a few extra bucks to treat lead-tainted water.  If that isn't bad enough, two years later, he has refused to do anything about it, ignoring the problem until the media started complaining.  He has refused to accept any responsibility for any of this, blaming Democrats for targeting him.  He even challenged himself to drink their lead-tainted water for 30 days straight, but never followed through, instead traveling overseas in an obvious attempt to appear reasonable.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/mike-pence.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Mike Pence&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Mike Pence&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;3. Mike Pence - Indiana&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Governor of Indiana, an abortion hating religious freedom law passing homophobe, is the only person stupid enough to accept an offer to be Donald Trump's running mate.  He even made this following quote about Donald Trump: &quot;Not since Ronald Reagan in my lifetime has there been a man or woman at the national level who has heard the frustrations and the aspirations of the American people the way (Trump) does.&quot;   Despite this, he gave the worst endorsement in the history of endorsements to Ted Cruz, which helped lead to Ted Cruz's demise in his home state of Indiana, instead spending more time praising Donald Trump.  His handling of Indiana's religious freedom bill, which got scrapped, is a prime example of how stupid he truly is, unaware of what the word 'discrimination' means.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/sam-brownback.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Sam Brownback&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Sam Brownback&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;2. Sam Brownback - Kansas&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sam Brownback presided over some of the most extreme tax cuts in history, costing Kansas millions of jobs and destroying their economy, in the name of Tea Party based experiments that have clearly failed.  Despite Kansas Republicans favoring a moderate Democrat to defeat him in the last election, the voters of Kansas re-elected this economy wrecking bozo.  Turns out the great experiment has been a complete catastrophe to everyone except for Brownback himself.  He also removed gay rights in the public sector, claiming it would help military veterans somehow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/pat-mccrory.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Pat McCrory&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Pat McCrory&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;1. Pat McCrory - North Carolina&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pat McCrory is a lunatic who thinks bathroom use is the most important thing needing to be fixed in North Carolina, as he has waged war against all the LGBT, believing no city in his state can give them the human rights they deserve while claiming transgenders don't exist, don't have any rights, and are likely to be sexual predators targeting women in bathrooms. If that's not bad enough, he blames it on Charlotte for giving the LGBT the rights they deserve.  He doesn't care how much money he's costing the state, especially after the NBA yanked the All-Star game from Charlotte, instead continuing his war in the bathroom.  Instead, he's willing to sue the Government for protecting basic human rights.  It's not common sense, it's discriminatory.  Pat McCrory, who clearly is using this war to get Republican support during an Election year, needs to be voted out.  The state of North Carolina deserves better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/09/15/worst-politicians-currently-in-office</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/09/15/worst-politicians-currently-in-office</guid>
        
        
        <category>politics</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Football Week Two Thoughts</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; On paper, Week Two looked to be the worst weekend of college football ever.  No ranked teams facing each other, more ranked teams playing FCS weaklings than fellow Power 5 teams, and just one ranked team on the road, #13 Louisville playing at Syracuse in an ACC Showdown.  But life has plenty of surprises, as Week 2 provided more entertainment than on paper.  Week 3 promises to be better in terms of quality matchups, but here are my thoughts on what happened in Week 2.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/lamar-jackson.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Lamar Jackson&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Lamar Jackson makes it look easy hurdling over a Syracuse defender.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As previously mentioned, Louisville had the toughest game scheduled for a ranked team, by virtue of being on the road against Syracuse.  Although Louisville's first two opponents, Marshall and Syracuse, don't exactly bring fear in anyone's eyes, sophomore Quarterback Lamar Jackson has put on quite the show, with 7 passing touchdowns and 6 rushing touchdowns in just two games.  He had 411 passing yards along with 199 rushing yards against Syracuse, putting on a dazzling performance and could very well join the Heisman conversation.  Next week, they play Florida State at home, which would be huge for Lamar Jackson.  A win and great offense production would likely shoot him up to the top of the Heisman conversation.  Louisville also plays Clemson and Houston.  It's too early to but into the hype on Lamar Jackson, but as a sophomore, he's definitely worthy of the talk right now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Minnesota had a gimme game against FCS Indiana State, and easily won 58-28, which was Minnesota's highest scoring game since 2006 when they dropped 63 against Indiana.  Hard to believe it's been ten years since I was a student at the University of Minnesota; I was at that game.  Time has certainly flown since then.  Not much to say about playing an FCS team, but since Minnesota has struggled against them in years past, a blowout is great to hear.  Speaking of FCS teams, four time defending FCS champion North Dakota State plays next week at Iowa.  That should be an interesting game.  As for Minnesota, they have a bye next week before playing Colorado State.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oregon played Virginia, who became the first ACC team to set foot in Autzen Stadium.  Virginia is not that good of a football team, but played as well as they could, but Oregon easily won, 44-26.  The offense looked more in sync than last week, as Royce Freeman went wild, rushing for 207 yds, while Dakota Prukop had three touchdowns to three different receivers, including Pharaoh Brown (his first since 2014) and Devon Allen (back from Rio, complete with a hurdle celebration).  Still, their defense has plenty of questions as they gave up quite a few big rushing gains.  Thankfully, the yellow jerseys look a lot better than last week's gray jerseys.  That's a plus.  Up next week, a trip to Nebraska, where of course, they will face former nemesis Mike Riley in a different uniform.  A far more challenging test than Virginia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/fumble.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Fumble&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Ray-Ray McCloud (left) and Kaelin Clay from two seasons ago (right) dropping the ball just before reaching the end zone.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clemson might be #2 in the polls, but didn't play like one against Troy.  Even worse, punt returner Ray-Ray McCloud managed to pull a Kaelin Clay by dropping the ball just short of the end zone.  Thankfully for the Tigers, Troy didn't catch onto this and return it for a touchdown like Oregon did against Utah in that infamous play two years ago. But a 30-24 victory isn't satisfying against Troy. --- Central Michigan completed the best play of the season so far with an incredible Hail Mary and lateral to upset #22 Oklahoma State.  Oklahoma State always manages to wind up on the wrong side of great stories, at least that's the way it seems to me.  Of course, an admitted official error gave the Chippewas of Central Michigan a chance but OK State has no one to blame but themselves for a poor defensive performance.  ---  USC LT Chuma Edoga shoved a ref and got thrown out.  Did he seriously think that wasn't going to happen?  Only at USC, right? --- Northwestern lost again, this time to FCS Illinois State.  Yikes!  --- Pittsburgh Running Back James Conner, back this year after battling Hodgkin's Lymphoma, has played well in his comeback so far.  I'm not sure whose comeback is greater, his or Pharaoh Brown's.  Both are winners in my books.  Congrats to James Conner.  -- Thrilling game between TCU and Arkansas, as TCU came back from a 20-7 deficit to take a 28-20 lead only for Arkansas to get a touchdown in the last minute and a double reverse pass for the two-point conversion, only for KaVontae Turpin (tine) to get a great kickoff return to put TCU in field goal range, which even crazier, got blocked.  Arkansas won 41-38 in Double OT-- Virginia Tech played Tennessee at the Bristol Motor Speedway, setting an FBS record with an attendance of 156,990.  That's a lot of people, I never knew NASCAR had stadiums that held that many people, crazy!  With that said, here are my picks for Top Ten:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/central-michigan.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Central Michigan&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Central Michigan stunned Oklahoma State with the Hail-and-Lateral play.  Wow!&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alabama&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Florida State (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clemson (-1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ohio State&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michigan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Houston&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stanford&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oklahoma&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wisconsin (NR)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Texas (NR)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/09/10/college-football-week-two</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/09/10/college-football-week-two</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nature Deserves Respect Too</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; On August 29th, a group of idiots, believing they can do whatever they want without any repercussions, destroyed a famous rock at Cape Kiwanda known as Duckbill.  Fortunately, someone recorded them committing the act and confronted them over it.  But the damage was done, all because some idiots couldn’t read a sign and blamed everyone but themselves for something that was obviously avoidable.  Too many people take nature for granted, and it deserves every bit of respect it gets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/kiwanda.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Cape Kiwanda&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Cape Kiwanda&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have been to Cape Kiwanda a few times and it is to me, one of the most beautiful areas along the Oregon Coast.  But I also know the risks of being close to the edge and I will respect signs that say 'Do Not Enter.'  For this reason, I never saw or heard of the Duckbill before it was destroyed, but it looked pretty, just like the whole area.  I admit, I have crossed signs I was told not to, but I always take the highest precautions and never stray too far from the trail, usually not more than a few steps beyond the path.  Safety is important.  Unfortunately, these Idiots crossed the Do Not Enter sign, and even worse, took it upon themselves to destroy a popular spot, for incredibly stupid reasons.  These idiots excuse?  They were doing the world a favor by preventing anyone else from getting hurt because one of these idiots broke his leg standing on top the Duckbill.  It was not for them to take matters for themselves, especially when they shouldn’t have been there in the first place.  That is a complete disregard for nature and selfishness on their behalf.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Living in Oregon, it’s not surprising that people like me love nature and cherish it for its beauty and mystique.  And not surprisingly, I have seen many stories of idiots not giving a damn about nature.  Last year, some dweebs etched their names in a railing at Tumalo Falls, and felt entitled to do so after being confronted by someone who took a picture of them showcasing their 'art.'  It’s reasons like this that make me disgusted with entitled pricks, and more reasons to appreciate nature for what it is.  Nature is alive and energetic, just like humans, animals and plants.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/duckbill.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Duckbill&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;If the idiots who destroyed Duckbill want to do the world a favor, they should turn themselves in and face punishment&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are plenty of things to love about nature, yet others would love to destroy it for profit.  Just like the pathetic Bundy clan and their anti-government militiamen.  If it were up to them, they would completely destroy nature just so they could make money.  That’s what their stupid mantra is all about.  They can claim the government has no right to land ownership, but some land is worth cherishing for its beauty.  Can you imagine if the Grand Canyon was owned by corporations and built all the properties they could?  That would completely devalue the natural beauty the Grand Canyon has to offer.  It's the same with those who pollute the Earth and all the land they are near in the name of profit.  I’ve never been to Glacier National Park, but reading its history and seeing the pictures, one can clearly see how global warming has damaged the very fabric the park has to offer, its Glaciers.  I would love to go there before they’re completely melted away by outside interests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes, you don't truly appreciate something until it's gone.  This is no exception with nature.  Humans aren't necessarily the root of all the destroying of nature, some of it is natural.  The famous Old Man of the Mountain, which was arguably one of New Hampshire's most famous attractions, collapsed in 2003 to much disappointment, but it 'died' of natural causes.  With events like this, you never really know how long nature will last.  It certainly doesn't help when humans take it for granted and outright trash and destroy parts of it.  Earlier this year, a group of frat boy punks had too much fun on Lake Shasta and when they were done, completely disregarded it, leaving all their trash there, acting as if nature is nothing more than a toilet.  But it's not, because believe it or not, some people actually value nature.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/kiwanda2.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Cape Kiwanda&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Another great picture of Cape Kiwanda.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be the first person to admit I haven't been completely perfect with nature.  As a young'un, I thought it would be cool to take a piece of lava from Lava Butte, and when I was older, a little piece of the Painted Hills, but in retrospect, was it really worth it?  Not really.  It seemed like good sentimental value, but it doesn't beat the memories itself, the pictures I've taken and seen, nor the experience itself.  Some dweebs take things for granted, do stupid things and feel as if it's not worth protecting, that somehow, it's an inconvenience when you get hurt from the more perilous parts of nature.  In the end, when humans do stupid things, they'll blame everyone but themselves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/miscellaneous/2016/09/08/nature-deserves-respect-too</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/miscellaneous/2016/09/08/nature-deserves-respect-too</guid>
        
        
        <category>miscellaneous</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NFL Preview</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; As further proof of the seasons changing, the NFL season is about to start, with a Thursday night rematch of Super Bowl 50, the Denver Broncos vs. the Carolina Panthers.  It should be an exciting year in the NFL, with a lot of notable events in the offseason and plenty of more on the way.  Which team will surprise this year?  Which team will disappoint this year?  Who wins the MVP?  Here's my thoughts on the NFL season on the horizon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/adrian-peterson.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Adrian Peterson&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Adrian Peterson is a BEAST!&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I was really looking forward to this season, the Minnesota Vikings were primed to make an explosion with their new stadium, US Bank Stadium up and running.  Teddy Bridgewater looked great and ready to take the next step.  Unfortunately, he tore his ACL and dislocated his knee in practice, ending his year before it started.  That left the Vikings in shock and disbelief, but with the perfect coach in Mike Zimmer, who should have been hired as a coach years ago but the Vikings aren't going to complain about that one, still have the talent to at least make the playoffs, led by Adrian Peterson (still as strong as ever) and an elite defense.  Clearly, the Vikings are going for a moon shot this year, which is why they acquired Sam Bradford from Philadelphia to replace Teddy Bridgewater this year.  A HUGE gamble to say the least, as Sam Bradford is talented, but has little time to learn the offense.  For his sake, he's in a better place than his previous stops, but only time will tell if the gamble pays off or not.  As for the rest of the NFC North, the Detroit Lions will be a different team with Calvin Johnson retiring, as we will once and for all see if Matthew Stafford is a capable quarterback or just the product of Calvin Johnson's freakish skills.  Chicago will remain mediocre, there's no reason to believe Jay Cutler will be any better or worse than before.  The Green Bay Packers, as long as they have Aaron Rodgers at Quarterback, will remain Super Bowl contenders.  My pick to win the NFC North: Green Bay.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;Their first opponent of the season is another team I've got my eye on, the Tennessee Titans, led by Marcus Mariota.  Mariota started his career with a perfect passer rating, but the Titans lacked the right weapons or coaching staff, as the Titans finished with a league worst 2-14 record.  Mike Mularkey is now the Head Coach, an interim for the failed Ken Whisenhunt.  Tennessee now has some better offensive weapons, with DeMarco Murray and last year's Heisman winner Derrick Henry joining the team as a dynamic Running Back duo.  There's no question Mariota has the talent and drive to succeed, but with Tennessee still young, how much will they improve?  Just remember, Peyton Manning had a 3-13 record in his rookie year.  Of course, the AFC South is up for grabs.  Indianapolis gave Andrew Luck a big extension, yet there are plenty of questions of surrounding players.  Houston still has a great defense led by J.J. Watt, a talented wide receiver in DeAndre Hopkins, but questions still remain at the Quarterback position, although Brock Osweiler appears to be an upgrade from the Brian Hoyer/Ryan Mallett combo from last year.  Jacksonville hasn't done much to improve their roster, and the jury's still out on Blake Bortles.  My pick to win the AFC South: Indianapolis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/marcus-mariota.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Marcus Mariota&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Will Marcus Mariota lead Tennessee to success this year?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;The New England Patriots are as loaded as ever, but Tom Brady finally got his suspension from Deflate-gate completed, so Brady will have to miss the first four games of this season.  Can Jimmy Garoppolo succeed while Brady's on mandatory vacation?  As long as Rob Gronkowski's around, I imagine the Patriots will be just fine.  The rest of the division is mediocre.  The New York Jets have a nice defense, but Ryan Fitzpatrick held out most of training camp and although he played well last year, I can't completely get behind him.  Buffalo has loudmouth schnook Rex Ryan as coach, which has improved their defense, but Tyrod Taylor is still an unknown as a Quarterback.  Miami is a confusing team, and Ryan Tannehill is the most unpredictable quarterback in the NFL, why Miami gave him a big contract is beyond me.  My pick to win the AFC East: New England.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;Chip Kelly, fired from the Philadelphia Eagles, takes his talents west to the San Francisco 49ers, who have been in the news a lot recently for Colin Kaepernick's refusal to stand for the National Anthem.  Though Kaepernick is now the teams backup quarterback, behind Blaine Gabbert (of all people), Chip will get another shot of perfecting his style of play in the NFL.  Kaepernick seemed like a good fit, but hasn't been playing as well (or has been all that healthy) to be the starter.  Thankfully, Chip Kelly won't be GM for the 49ers, because that's what cost him his job with the Eagles.  Too many questions about the 49ers roster and playing in a tough division won't help.  The NFL returns to Los Angeles as the Rams left St. Louis to come back to LA.  They still have questions about their Quarterback as top pick Jared Goff hasn't looked that well so far and was named third string at the moment behind Case Keenum and Sean Mannion (who would've thought that).  Same division as the 49ers, but lots of pressure on coach Jeff Fisher, who's obviously talented but hasn't gotten the Rams where they need to be.  Hopefully, they will get the continued production from running back Todd Gurley, who looks like a future star.  Seattle is still as talented as ever, with their stout defense, but they have lost key players since their Super Bowl win a few years ago, and Marshawn Lynch retired.  The Arizona Cardinals are still talented, and Bruce Arians is one of the best coaches in the NFL.  But who knows whether Carson Palmer can continue being the great quarterback he is.  My pick to win the NFC West: Seattle.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
    		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/andrew-luck.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Andrew Luck&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
    		&lt;h4&gt;Andrew Luck needs a big year...my Mom's counting on it!&lt;/h4&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;No team will be more puzzling to figure out than the Super Bowl Champions, the Denver Broncos.  On the on hand, their defense as a great as ever, led by Von Miller at Linebacker, whose suffocating play carried them to the Super Bowl victory over the high powered Carolina Panthers.  On the other hand, Peyton Manning retired and their quarterback replacement wound up in an unexpected way.  Brock Osweiler left for Houston, Mark Sanchez was acquired but didn't do much (ultimately, he was cut), Paxton Lynch was drafted as the future QB, but it was third string Quarterback Trevor Siemian who was named the starter after an impressive preseason.  Siemian played just one snap his rookie season, a kneel down at the end of a game, now in his second season, becomes the first Quarterback to start for a Super Bowl Champion without a single pass attempt in the NFL.  Should be very interesting to see how well they perform.  Kansas City has plenty of talent, and Alex Smith has slowly become one of the most reliable quarterbacks in the NFL.  The 49ers should have kept him over Kaepernick, but who could blame them at the time.  The Raiders, perhaps in their last year in Oakland, have suddenly shown some signs of respectability, with Derek Carr having great potential as a star Quarterback.  Their defense has improved, led by Khalil Mack, who's a complete stud.  The big question is whether the Raiders can play consistently in what might be their last year in Oakland.  One thing's for sure, the NFL would never be the same if they do in fact move to Las Vegas.  San Diego looks like a complete mess, totally wasting Philip Rivers potential as their Quarterback.  Never a good sign when rookie Joey Bosa just signed a deal after a long and pointless holdout.  My pick to win the AFC West: Kansas City.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;The AFC North, like always, will run through Pittsburgh, despite the suspension from running back LeVeon Bell.  Their defense is still good, and Ben Roethlisberger is still elite.  Baltimore had a down year last season, but with Joe Flacco still around, Baltimore will have a better year this season, but still looks mediocre at best.  Cincinnati looked like it was about to take the next step last year, and Andy Dalton certainly took the next step, but their defense is still completely undisciplined.  Plus with Hue Jackson now head coach of the Cleveland Browns, their offense could take a dive.  One thing remains for sure, the Cleveland Browns are still a terrible team.  Robert Griffin III, a.k.a. RGIII is desperate to revive his career, and he definitely needed to leave Washington, but Cleveland is still quarterback purgatory.  My feeling is that RGIII is damaged goods, and it's unfortunate, because I was pretty high on him entering the NFL.  My pick to win the AFC North: Pittsburgh.&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
 		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/von-miller.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Von Miller&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
 		&lt;h4&gt;No defensive player will be more crucial this year than Von Miller&lt;/h4&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;   
    &lt;p&gt;Carolina remains the best team in the NFC South, but the potential for a post-Super Bowl hangover could derail their hopes.  But with Cam Newton still extremely talented and most of their core back, they're still dangerous.  The Atlanta Falcons have Matt Ryan leading the way, and Julio Jones is still a talented Wide Receiver, but I'm not sure they'll be anything more than .500 team.  Tampa Bay has potential to improve this year, with Jameis Winston showing some potential, but they fired Lovie Smith as head coach and replaced him with Dirk Koetter, a puzzling move to say the least.  Meanwhile, the New Orleans Saints still have defensive flaws and will need to lean on Drew Brees once again to provide their offense.  My pick to win the NFC South: Carolina&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;The NFC East will still be up for grabs this year.  Washington was the best team last year, but they benefited from a weak division.  They were exposed in the playoffs.  I still have my doubts on Kirk Cousins.  Dallas will remain in limbo as long as quarterback Tony Romo remains hurt.  Who knows when he will come back.  Of course, Ezekiel Elliott and Dak Prescott could very well be the new dynamic duo.  They still need Romo's leadership.  The New York Giants have a new coach, with Tom Coughlin retiring, and as long as Eli Manning and Odell Beckham Jr. remain on the roster, the Giants can win some games, especially in a weak division.  Philadelphia looks like a complete mess, it's as if they completely wiped out the core of Chip Kelly's roster moves last year.  Now that Sam Bradford was traded, it's up to rookie Carson Wentz to lead what's left over for that offense.  My pick to win the NFC East: The New York Giants.&lt;/p&gt;
  
 &lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
 		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/us-bank-stadium.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;US Bank Stadium&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
 		&lt;h4&gt;The Vikings new stadium: US Bank Stadium.  All I can say is Wow!&lt;/h4&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;       
    &lt;p&gt;The AFC has plenty of strong teams like last year, and it will remain tough this year.  New England, Pittsburgh, Kansas City and Indianapolis will make the playoffs winning their divisions, with Denver and the New York Jets getting in as wild cards.  The NFC will also have some strong teams, but won't be as strong as the AFC.  Seattle, Green Bay, Carolina and New York Giants will make the playoffs winning their divisions, with Minnesota and Arizona making the wild cards.  My prediction for the Super Bowl is New England vs. Green Bay, with the Patriots winning it all.  As usual, they're the most complete team, even with Brady out four games, it won't affect their Super Bowl or playoff dreams.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/09/07/nfl-preview</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/09/07/nfl-preview</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Football Week One Thoughts</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Thank god football's back.  It's refreshing to take interest in something besides politics and this ridiculous election.  Week One is under wraps, and though only a handful of games carry any value, it's only the beginning.  Here's my thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/taiyon-devers.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Tai'yon Devers&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Tai'yon Devers with two sacks, both fumbles recovered by the Gophers&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Gophers played a tough game against Oregon State, managing to hold onto a 30-23 win despite some sluggishness in the passing game and three ejections from targeting.  Rodney Smith did a good job running and Mitch Leidner showcased his gutsy running on key downs.  Oregon State looked decent and are heading in the right direction, but still a young team, and it showed.  The first game of the season, obviously, but the Gophers will need to play better to take the next step.  Either way, the Gophers won the battle of the 'Rodents,' the only two Major FBS teams with rodent mascots.  Next up, FCS Indiana State.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also playing Thursday night was my pick as most overrated team in the Top 10, Tennessee, who went above and beyond to prove their overrated-ness, just barely beating Appalachian State in OT, 20-13, exactly nine years to the day that the Mountaineers of Appalachian State pulled off their historic massive upset of Michigan.  Safe to say, Tennessee is not there quite yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Saturday, my pick for most underrated team, Houston, played against Oklahoma in a battle of Top 15 teams.  The biggest game in Houston’s history, the Cougars surprised virtually everyone outside Houston by beating Oklahoma.  I'd figured Houston would play well, but exceeded expectations.  The game turned when Houston Auburned Oklahoma with a end-zone to end-zone missed field goal into a touchdown, reminiscent of Auburn’s famous play three years ago against Alabama.  Houston blew the game open after that.  Very impressive effort by Houston, whose Peach Bowl win against Florida State is a game of the past according to the team.  Great philosophy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/royce-freeman.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Royce Freeman&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Royce Freeman was his usual self.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Oregon Ducks began their season against UC Davis, and of course, Oregon won 53-28.  Nothing too spectacular to say, except it was nice to see Pharaoh Brown back after his horrific injury.  Dakota Prukop played as well as one would expect against an FCS team.  On the flip side, their jerseys weren't that great to me, not sure why their jerseys are gray for this game, but they go through so many combos we’ll probably never see it again.  And for the first time in 17 years, Autzen Stadium did not sell out their seats.  Next up, Virginia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for the rest of the games, here are my thoughts.  Once again, USC proved how consistently overrated they are, as defending champs Alabama completely rolled over them 52-6.  Never expected the lousy Trojans to win this game, but a good team would've kept it close.  USC on the other hand, just plain sucked. --- Navy had to pull a quarterback out of the stands to fill in after starter Tago Smith got injured.  Enjoy your fifteen minutes of fame, backup from the stands Malcolm Perry.  Georgia Tech barely beat Boston College in a game played in Dublin, Ireland.  If only Notre Dame had played against Georgia Tech, it would've been the perfect Irish matchup.  But please, no car bombs. --- Virginia, whom Oregon plays next week, lost to FCS power Richmond 37-20.  So much for having two legit Power 5 non-conference teams on the schedule.  At least there's Nebraska. --- Speaking of Nebraska, it was very sweet for them to bring out ten players during their first punt to honor Sam Foltz, who died in a car wreck in July.  Classy act.  Not classy was the scumbag who robbed his brother’s house while this was happening.  This scumbag, who was arrested today, but not identified as of yet, should become the most hated person in Nebraska. --- Northwestern lost to Western Michigan 22-21, which makes me wonder if the recently departed journalist John Saunders (R.I.P.), who went to Western Michigan, lifted them spiritually.  John Saunders was one of my favorites, he will be missed. --- Washington State again proved how unpredictable they are by losing to Eastern Washington 45-42.  They looked fairly good last year despite a loss to Portland State.  They follow up this year with a loss to another FCS team.  What in the hell is Mike Leach smoking?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/houston.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Houston&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Houston turned the game in their favorite with this missed field goal returned for a touchdown.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Week One doesn’t say a lot about the National Championship, but it’s safe to say that Oklahoma won’t win it like I predicted.  By no means does this mean they won’t make it to the playoffs, they can still win out the rest of their games and win the Big XII, but their defense isn’t as great as I thought.  I need to do some better research next time.  Of course, Houston, with its marquee win, has a chance to run the table and make the Playoffs itself.  They still have Louisville to play late in the regular season as a good non-conference game, but they have the talent to go undefeated in the American Athletic Conference and crash the Power 5 Playoff Party.  With that, here are my picks for Top Ten:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alabama&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clemson&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Florida State&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ohio State&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michigan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Houston&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stanford&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oklahoma&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;LSU&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michigan State&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/09/06/college-football-week-one</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/09/06/college-football-week-one</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kaepernicking 2.0 - The Protest Edition</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Last Friday, during a preseason game against the Green Bay Packers, Quarterback Colin Kaepernick refused to stand for the National Anthem, taking the opportunity to protest racial oppression in the United States, and plans to continue his protest until 'real change' progresses.  Reaction has not surprisingly been mixed, with some praising him for taking a stand while others are criticizing him for it.  Kaepernick is not the first athlete to use his status to protest civil rights, nor will he be the last, but the question remains, will his refusal to stand actually bring any change?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/kaepernick.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Colin Kaepernick&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Colin Kaepernick&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Sports, more than anything, can bring people together, something we saw after 9/11 and the Boston Marathon attacks.  So in that regard, perhaps sports can help solve our human rights issues.  But we've seen this happen before with little success.  The biggest success was having Jackie Robinson break the color barrier in baseball.  Another success was Jesse Owens winning multiple gold medals in the 1936 Olympics in Nazi Germany.  But other athlete protests have done nothing but made said athletes merely a symbol of protests.  Tommie Smith and John Carlos with the Black Power salute at the 1968 Olympics were courageous to do so, but that's what they're best known for.  Former NBA player Mahmoud Abdul-Rauf refused to stand for the National Anthem during the 1996 for similar reasons as Colin Kaepernick, but his career was never the same after that.  Same thing with Craig Hodges, whose NBA career was all but over after he handed a note to President George H.W. Bush at the White House protesting the treatment of minorities.  For many of the previous examples, these athletes were not notable enough, and thus, didn't have the ability to reach the masses like Michael Jordan, who famously never championed any political causes during his playing career.  The only notable athlete to protest and spread awareness for causes was the late Muhammad Ali, who sacrificed everything to avoid fighting in the Vietnam War.  In that regard, Colin Kaepernick has a steep hill to climb.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;But while things may not have been effective in the past, things are different in 2016.  Social media is rampant and people hear about things in an instant.  Celebrities make their thoughts more public (for better or worse) through Twitter.  We live in a society more aware of racist undertones and more willing to call others out for it.  So maybe now is the time for real progress.  But Colin Kaepernick's career has been on a downhill for the past few years since his miracle run to the Super Bowl.  The fact to the matter is is that no one noticed Kaepernick's refusal to stand for the National Anthem the first two games since he was injured.  One person alone, unfortunately, can not make a difference, whether it's myself, Colin Kaepernick or President Obama.  Kaepernick has a right to stand (or not stand for in his case) for what he believes in, but let's be honest, his actions won't change anything.  Speaking up is a step in the right direction, but collaboration goes further.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float:left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/salute.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Black Power Salute&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Tommie Smith and John Carlos (center and right) with the Black Power Salute&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;As long as the broken system pits us against one another, our society will never change.  As it is, Kaepernick still lives in a world that pits people against each other.  In his case, it's the African Americans against Law Enforcement, and whether Kaepernick is pitting people against each other is his intention, it's clear that Law Enforcement doesn't approve of his actions.  The San Francisco Police Department called his actions &quot;embarrassing&quot; and &quot;disrespectful.&quot;  Standing (or not standing) in protest does little to bridge the gap between said groups necessary to bring real change.  Real change requires everyone on the same page and protest together.  Unfortunately, there's no trust between the two, and that's the biggest challenge.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;Though some question Kaepernick's actions, no one should question his intentions or his passion for speaking up.  It may not be the best way to call for change, but perhaps making a provocative stand, in this day and age, can at least get people talking.  As it is, a lot of people have been talking about it.  Earlier in the year, NBA stars LeBron James, Carmelo Anthony, Dwyane Wade, Chris Paul spoke about racial justice at the ESPY awards, and though it was good for them to speak up, it didn't quite grab the attention that Kaepernick clearly has with his profound statement.  In that regard, going bold can be effective in getting people to talk, which sometimes is half the battle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/2016/08/30/kaepernicking</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/2016/08/30/kaepernicking</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>If It Sounds Like A Racist...</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last week, the Governor of Maine, Paul LePage, known for being an obnoxious blubber mouth, bluntly stated that 90% plus of all drug dealers arrested in Maine are &quot;Black and Hispanic,&quot; a statement which many found to be abhorrently racist.  After all, this is the same Governor who earlier in the year proclaimed that drug dealers &quot;are guys with the name D-Money, Smoothie, Shifty; these types of guys, they come from Connecticut and New York, they come up here, they sell their heroin, they go back home. Incidentally, half the time they impregnate a young, white girl before they leave, which is a real sad thing because then we have another issue we have to deal with down the road.&quot;  Clearly, these types of comments, focusing on skin color, are profoundly racist in nature, lumping blacks with drugs and street-names.  Yet Paul LePage, angry that Democratic State Rep. Drew Gattine allegedly called him racist, left him a vulgar voicemail demanding proof of his 'racism,' using multiple swear words against him, including cocksucker, and told him, &quot;I am after you,&quot; amongst other things.  It would be one thing to say something once, but people like Paul LePage have repeatedly made racist comments.  So what do incidents like this say about racism in our society?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/lobster.gif&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Maine Lobsters&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Sadly, Lobsters are more capable of running Maine than Governor Paul LePage&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Earlier in the year, rapper Macklemore released a song called &quot;White Privilege II,&quot; where he rapped &quot;It seems like we're more concerned with being called racist / Than we actually are with racism,&quot; and this definitely seems to be true here and in many cases.  Someone like Paul LePage doesn't seem to realize that this comments are racist or could be construed as racist, yet is immediately offended as being called a racist, focusing on self-image rather than society as a whole.  People like this knows what racism is and how to define it, but ultimately, they all ignore their own inherent racism.  Racism has been around forever, and in some shape or form will always exist, but for some, it's not an issue until someone calls you out for it.  Like it or not, defining someone based off their race or ethnicity is never the right thing to do.  It accomplishes nothing but put unburden some blame on people without cause.  People are complex beings and are not easy to define.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;It seems like we're more concerned with being called racist / Than we actually are with racism.&lt;footer&gt;Macklemore - White Privilege II&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By definition, the word racism is defined as &quot;the belief that all members of each race possess characteristics or abilities specific to that race, especially so as to distinguish it as inferior or superior to another race or races.&quot;  With LePage's comments about drug dealers, you would think that only blacks and Hispanics are capable of being drug dealers, but stereotyping minorities (or anyone in general based on certain characteristics) with negative connotations is racist, as any group of people are capable of being drug dealers.  For this instance, all this accomplishes is makes Blacks and Hispanics scapegoats for a problem that is more complicated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float:left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/lepage.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Paul LePage&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Governor Paul LePage has no clue of what it means to be racist&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Does making racist comments actually solve anything?  Here, it obviously ignores that fact that there are plenty of drug dealers that have not been caught.  Statistics have shown that police officers are far more likely to go after African Americans and Hispanics than they are whites, even though whites are more likely to be guilty of something.  It happens in places like Cleveland, Baltimore and Ferguson, and certainly does little fix the real issues.  Solving Maine's drug problem requires complex and intricate thinking, more than just identifying the dealers skin color or ethnicity.  It does nothing to stop the issue, and leads to more racial profiling, overlooking the biggest problem within all of this, the drug abusers themselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Racial profiling is not only wrong but completely immoral.  It basically states: &quot;If you are of a certain color, you're probably going to do something bad, but if you're not that color, you're fine.&quot;  Paul LePage thinks blacks are drug dealers, but plenty of blacks aren't dealing drugs, and yet, they are more likely to be accused of dealing drugs than a white person who actually deals drugs will.  So while plenty of Americans will focus on a person's skin color and their stereotypes to form their opinions about them, it ignores the complexity of human beings.  As a Jewish minority, there are plenty of negative stereotypes associated with my religion that aren't associated with me at all, yet Anti-Semitic people have already formed an opinion of me without actually knowing me that's not true.  It's the same with other groups of people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&quot;blockquote-reverse&quot;&gt;&quot;Mr. Gattine, this is Gov. Paul Richard LePage.  I would like to talk to you about your comments about my being a racist, you (obscene term). I want to talk to you. I want you to prove that I'm a racist. I've spent my life helping black people and you little (obscene term), socialist (obscene term). You -- I need you to -- just friggin'. I want you to record this and make it public because I am after you. Thank you.&quot; &lt;footer&gt;Paul LePage leaving a voicemail&lt;/footer&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether someone is actually racist or not is often debatable, but deep down, people can be implicitly racist and not realize or understand it.  These people often can identify someone else as being racist but can't comprehend their own racist thoughts.  Paul LePage certainly sees no wrong in his words, claiming he was just going through a binder full of drug arrests in his state.  But the sad truth is that many people focus on one small detail on human beings to identify everything there is to know about them: color.  There are numerous other qualities that human beings have, from genetics, environmental factors and socioeconomic upbringing, the latter which is often ignored by those who judge solely on skin color.  So while people like LePage focus on color, solving problems requires a more comprehensive research on human beings than just skin color.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/maine.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Maine&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Maine is far too beautiful to have a racist talking Governor in charge.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt; the flipside, we also have people who will say things like &quot;I like these people, I've done this and this for them,&quot; to make the claim that they are not racist.  Paul LePage has no problem stating &quot;he's done all these things to help the African-American community,&quot; but it's basically a cop-out to say things like this.  Once again, it focuses on a person's skin color or ethnicity, rather than their complete personality.  I am more than just Jewish, so really, is anything accomplished by focusing on my religion and not my complete self?  Of course not, but don't tell those whose main goal is to not be referred to as racist?  In the end, that's more important for some than the issue of racism itself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/08/28/if-it-sounds-like-a-racist</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/08/28/if-it-sounds-like-a-racist</guid>
        
        
        <category>politics</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Football Preview 2016</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Next week is the unofficial start of the College Football season, and after a boring summer filled with boring baseball, I'm ready for some football.  Although it officially started 'last night' when Cal played Hawaii halfway around the world in Sydney, Australia, next week is the start for the rest of us. As someone who spent three years at the University of Oregon and one and a half years at the University of Minnesota, I have two teams to follow, and as long as they don't play each other, I don't have to decide.  So here are my thoughts on the upcoming football season.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/leidner.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Mitch Leidner&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Mitch Leidner&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;As previously mentioned, I would hate for Oregon and Minnesota to play each other.  It's a good thing that Minnesota instead chose to open its season against Oregon State.  Not only that, Oregon is too fast for Minnesota.  Oregon State had a disappointing season last year (2-10), but I can't imagine the Beavers being that bad again this season.  With that said, Minnesota is playing at home and has the more steady hand offensively, with Mitch Leidner back at the helm at Quarterback.  Gophers win, 24-14.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;This season, the Big Ten has decided to hold nine conference games, rather than the eight they have previously played.  That means one more conference opponent instead of a crappy non conference opponent. The rest of the Gophers non conference games are against FCS Indiana State and Colorado State.  Colorado State gave them a close game last year, and could very well do the same this year, but I imagine Minnesota will finish 3-0 in the non-conference.  As for their conference games, Minnesota has a far more easier slate of conference games than last year, when Minnesota had one of the toughest schedules imagined.  Rather than playing Michigan and Ohio State, Minnesota instead gets crossover matchups against Penn State, Maryland and Rutgers, who were three of the four worst teams in the Big Ten's East Division.  As it is, Iowa is the only ranked team (#17) on Minnesota's schedule.  The good news for Minnesota, they get Iowa at home.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;So how do the Gophers perform this season?  Should the Gophers get some consistency from Mitch Leidner and their offense, the Big Ten West is wide open for Minnesota to have a chance to steal the Big Ten West from Iowa.  Wisconsin isn't dominate like they have been recently, and perhaps Minnesota can finally win Paul Bunyan's Axe (obviously the most important game of the season).  Nebraska, Northwestern and Penn State are talented enough to match with Minnesota, so winning two of those games (if not all three) is essential.  Shannon Brooks, their leading rusher last year is injured, but should be ready for the Big Ten schedule.  Their passing game showed some signs last year but needs to make the next step in order for Minnesota to contend.  My prediction: Minnesota finishes a respectable 8-4, good for second in the Big Ten West.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/prukop.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Dakota Prukop&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Dakota Prukop&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;    
    &lt;p&gt;As for the Oregon Ducks, who begin the season ranked #24 (AP) and #22 (Coaches Poll), the Ducks will once again have a new quarterback at the helm.  It was just announced yesterday, to little surprise, that FCS transfer, former Montana State QB Dakota Prukop will be the starter, and Justin Herbert, a true freshman from Sheldon High School, coming out of nowhere to supplant expected backup Travis Jonsen as the backup.  Prukop has the smarts and the footwork to be successful, although probably not as good as Vernon Adams was last year, Oregon still has plenty of offensive weapons starting with Heisman contender Royce Freeman, one of the best running backs in the country.  Their offense, assuming they stay healthy, will be fine.  Another thing to note is the return of Pharoah Brown, whose horrific injury two seasons ago nearly cost him his leg.  Any production from him will be welcomed as should he, as he's come a long ways, and was just named starting Tight End once again.  It's their defense that's killed them in the past.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Oregon has never been known for their defense, and it killed them last year blowing a 31-0 lead at the Alamo Bowl.  Though Oregon's usually stayed in house, no one from Oregon could handle the job, as Don Pellum was demoted to Linebackers coach.  In comes Brady Hoke, the former Michigan coach holding a coordinator job for the first time.  Will Oregon's defense improve?  Hard to say with losing their best defensive players from last year (DeForrest Buckner).  They'll need it as Oregon plays plenty of tough games.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Their non-conference schedule isn't anything special, with UC-Davis, Virginia and Nebraska on their plate, the latter game on the road against old nemesis Mike Riley.  Oregon should win all three of those games, heading into a conference schedule with three ranked teams, Washington (inexplicably ranked #14), USC (#20, yuck!) and Stanford (#8, again the toughest game of the year).  Can Oregon win the Pac-12 this year?  Will someone besides Oregon or Stanford win the Pac-12 North?  My hunch tells me Oregon will finish second behind Stanford again.  Oregon beat Stanford last year, but too many questions defensively for them to win the North.  My prediction: Oregon finishes 9-3, good for second in the Pac-12 North&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;As for the rest of the College Football landscape, Alabama and Clemson start the season as they ended it, #1 and #2 respectively.  Oklahoma, making the Playoffs last year as well, is still loaded and ranked #3, while Florida State is ranked #4.  The Big Ten is led by Ohio State and Michigan, and could come down to the two long time rivals.  Stanford is the highest ranked team in the Pac-12, ranked #8 (AP) and #7 (Coaches Poll), with the electrifying Christian McCaffrey at running back.  One team that's ranked too high to start is Tennessee, in the Top Ten in both polls despite their past years of mediocrity.  One team ranked too low (not surprisingly as the best non-major conference team, Notre Dame not included) is Houston (#15, AP and #13, Coaches Poll), who surprised many last year by beating Florida State in the Peach Bowl convincingly, and returning many of their best players.  They begin their season at home against Oklahoma, and though Oklahoma is probably going to win, Houston has plenty of weapons to at least contend with the Sooners (especially at home) and make another BCS Bowl.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/mccaffrey.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Christian McCaffrey&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Christian McCaffrey&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;       
    &lt;p&gt;Some other things that will intrigue me includes all of these things:  How will Baylor perform this year after their controversial summer with the firing of Art Briles for his lack of conduct over their numerous players arrested for various violent crimes?  Two teams I really hate play each other in the first game of the year: Alabama and USC.  Which team is more dispicable right now, the Crimson Tide and their big time success and complaining against Oregon-styled offenses, or the always dislikable USC that always gets ranked no matter how mediocre they really are.  LSU has had a crazy ride with floods affecting the state, particularly Baton Rouge, and the near firing of Les Miles.  How will they perform with all of this going on?  The Pac-12 has lots of talented teams, but since they joined the conference, Colorado has always been at the bottom, slowly creeping their way to respectability.  Is this the year Colorado finally makes the jump from bottom-feeder to respectable?  Lovie Smith, former Super Bowl coach for the Chicago Bears, finds himself as coach of Illinois.  That will be interesting to say the least.  &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Heisman race has two top contenders right now, the aformentioned Christian McCaffrey and Clemson Quarterback DeShaun Watson.  Either one of these two players are talented enough to win the Heisman, but McCaffrey is dangerous no matter where on the field he is.  He's my preseason pick to win the Heisman Trophy.  As for Conference Champions and Playoff teams, here are my picks:  The ACC will once again come down to Clemson and Florida State, the clear two best teams in the conference.  Clemson is obviously talented but my gut tells me Florida State will beat them and win the ACC.  The Big XII has Oklahoma clearly as the best team in the conference, and it's unlikely that will change, as Oklahoma wins the Big XII.  The Big Ten has Ohio State, Michigan and Michigan State as the three best teams in the conference, but with Michigan State losing their leader Connor Cook at Quarterback and Ohio State losing a lot of studs, I pick Michigan to win the Big Ten behind the coaching of the obnoxiously lovable Jim Harbaugh.  The Pac-12 is wide open this year, with Oregon, Stanford, UCLA, Washington and USC all capable of winning the championship, but when it's all said and done, Stanford will repeat.  The SEC is once again ridiculously loaded at the top with Alabama the defending Champion, and they will repeat as SEC Champs again.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Third College Football Playoffs, as I see it, will feature Alabama, Oklahoma, Florida State and Michigan in that order, and when it's all said and done, I pick Oklahoma to win it all, being the most complete team in the nation, a stout defense and an electrifying offense led by Quarterback Baker Mayfield.  This season will be another doozy, that's for sure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/08/27/college-football-preview-2016</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/08/27/college-football-preview-2016</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
