<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adam&#39;s Blog</title>
    <description>A blog about whatever is on Adam&#39;s mind.</description>
    <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 19:41:18 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 19:41:18 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Steven Adams - A Debate on Whether Exoticness equals Attractiveness</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/steven-adams.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Steven Adams&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;The man with the hair: Steven Adams&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;After watching seven games of the Golden State-Oklahoma City series, I have come to the conclusion that no matter how talented you are, you need a signature look to gain attention from the common-man.  Sure, Kevin Durant is quite talented, he shoots well and is one of the most feared offensive players in the league, but while I was watching this series, it was Steven Adams and his long hair, long mustache and tattoos that got all my attention, as well as an interesting back-and-forth between my Mom, her boyfriend, my sister and I on whether Adams is good-looking or not.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/steven-adams-3.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Steven Adams&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;As a youngster, he looked handsome&lt;/h4&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Naturally, people are drawn to those that look unlike anyone else.  I was always like that growing up; playing one of my favorite games as a youth in Street Fighter, I always choose Blanka and his green-skinned / orange-hair savage-like looks over the conventional karate master Ryu, who seemed bland and boring to me.  I was always drawn to the different looking characters because they were exotic, unique, out of the blue.  And with Steven Adams, there&#39;s definitely something about him that stands out, which otherwise wouldn&#39;t happen if he kept his youthful look when he was first drafted.  But is Steven Adams really attractive, or just exotic?&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/adam-morrison.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Adam Morrison&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Before Steven Adams, there was Adam Morrison.&lt;/h4&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;		
	&lt;p&gt;To some, Steven Adams looks hideous, and though there are some men who look good with long hair, Steven Adams looks unkempt with the beard and mustache When he plays.  I first thought of him looking like (former NBAer) Adam Morrison on crack.  He had the long hair and mustache, but Morrison wasn&#39;t the wild-child that Steven Adams was.  Morrison&#39;s looks were more goofy, while Adam&#39;s looks come off as more fitting.  But playing basketball, it&#39;s not about looking handsome on the court.  Players play hard, they sweat and will do anything to get the ball.  It&#39;s not like being a model on the catwalk.  Would Steven Adams look good on a catwalk as opposed to the hardwood floor?&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/steven-adams-2.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Steven Adams&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Steven Adams looks better in official pictures because he&#39;s supposed to.&lt;/h4&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;		
	&lt;p&gt;His looks personify his performance, so chances are, if Steven Adams wanted to pull that look off on the catwalk, he easily could.  The hair is pulled into a ponytail when he plays, making him look like a warrior of sorts.  But he tends to let his hair look when he&#39;s on the bench, so he can make the look more attractive when needed.  Not to mention he looks happier taking official pictures than when he&#39;s on the floor trying to win the game for his team.  A nice looking youngster when he first entered the NBA, the look has evolved in the past three years.  It&#39;s that kind of evolution that has some people interested in him and finding him more attractive than your typical player.  For some, who wants to be a typical Steph Curry when you can be wild and crazy looking Steven Adams.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/chris-andersen.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Chris Andersen&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Birdman: A man of a thousand looks...and they all look hideous!&lt;/h4&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;		
	&lt;p&gt;Some players in the NBA, current or former, have looked exotic and unique but aren&#39;t able to pull their look off well.  James Harden, for example, has the beard, which might look passable if not for the equally weird looking hair style.  To me, he looks like a big hairy mess with an unnatural beard, which covers everything past his nose minus the mouth.  Perhaps if he went bald and contained some of his beard near his mouth he would look better, but instead he&#39;s the man with the big bushy beard.  Then you have players who look bad on purpose for the sake of attention, like Dennis Rodman, whose hair dye, piercings and tattoos are well-documented.  Another player known for his appearance is Chris Andersen, a.k.a. Birdman, whose body is covered by tattoos and varying hair styles that make him look like a tattoo model than a basketball player.  These are examples of NBA players whose looks don&#39;t do them well.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/james-harden.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;James Harden&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;The man with the beard...James Harden.  No thanks.&lt;/h4&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;	
	&lt;p&gt;Yet for Steven Adams, his young looks make his evolution more appealing.  Unlike Chris Andersen, who looked unimpressive when he was young before the hair and tattoo explosion, Steven Adams comes off more of an evolution of his New Zealander roots than someone who merely just wants tattoos all over his body.  Dennis Rodman&#39;s looks made no sense other than being a rebel who wanted to look different, nor did Chris Andersen&#39;s, and James Harden&#39;s looks doesn&#39;t fit his style of play.  But while Steven Adams is not as handsome as Tony Parker, Adams is able to make it work through his roots and playing style.  Adams plays like his looks, and that to me is part of his mystique.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;In all, I would say that exotic looks have the ability to be considered attractive, if done correctly.  It doesn&#39;t necessarily apply to all athletes in the NBA, or in sports in general, but in the case of Steven Adams, it&#39;s no wonder why there&#39;s even a debate on whether he looks good or not.  The simplest test is whether a kid can pull it off, and as in the case of Oklahoma City&#39;s youngest viral fan, Lil&#39; Stache Bro, the answer is hell yeah.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-6&quot;&gt;
		&lt;blockquote class=&quot;instagram-media&quot; data-instgrm-captioned=&quot;&quot; data-instgrm-version=&quot;7&quot; style=&quot; background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:658px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);&quot;&gt;&lt;div style=&quot;padding:8px;&quot;&gt; &lt;div style=&quot; background:#F8F8F8; line-height:0; margin-top:40px; padding:50.0% 0; text-align:center; width:100%;&quot;&gt; &lt;div style=&quot; background:url(data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAACwAAAAsCAMAAAApWqozAAAABGdBTUEAALGPC/xhBQAAAAFzUkdCAK7OHOkAAAAMUExURczMzPf399fX1+bm5mzY9AMAAADiSURBVDjLvZXbEsMgCES5/P8/t9FuRVCRmU73JWlzosgSIIZURCjo/ad+EQJJB4Hv8BFt+IDpQoCx1wjOSBFhh2XssxEIYn3ulI/6MNReE07UIWJEv8UEOWDS88LY97kqyTliJKKtuYBbruAyVh5wOHiXmpi5we58Ek028czwyuQdLKPG1Bkb4NnM+VeAnfHqn1k4+GPT6uGQcvu2h2OVuIf/gWUFyy8OWEpdyZSa3aVCqpVoVvzZZ2VTnn2wU8qzVjDDetO90GSy9mVLqtgYSy231MxrY6I2gGqjrTY0L8fxCxfCBbhWrsYYAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC); display:block; height:44px; margin:0 auto -44px; position:relative; top:-22px; width:44px;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;p style=&quot; margin:8px 0 0 0; padding:0 4px;&quot;&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/p/BFzwDdiCqG4/&quot; style=&quot; color:#000; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none; word-wrap:break-word;&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lil Stache Bro in Thunder Alley.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p style=&quot; color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;&quot;&gt;A photo posted by Oklahoma City Thunder (@okcthunder) on &lt;time style=&quot; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px;&quot; datetime=&quot;2016-05-24T23:34:23+00:00&quot;&gt;May 24, 2016 at 4:34pm PDT&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
	&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; defer=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.instagram.com/en_US/embeds.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-6&quot;&gt;
		&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
			&lt;img src=&quot;/img/jason.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Jason&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
			&lt;h4&gt;Meet my Mom&#39;s Boyfriend&#39;s son Jason.  If a little kid can pull off the look, so can Jason.  I just wanted to show this picture off.&lt;/h4&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/steven-adams</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/steven-adams</guid>
        
        
        <category>basketball</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>When Keeping it Real Goes Wrong - The Social Media Edition</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Anyone who used to watch Chappelle&#39;s Show back in the day surely remembers the skit, &#39;When Keeping it Real Goes Wrong,&#39; as Dave Chappelle&#39;s comically showed skits of so-called thugs and gangstas in instances when it&#39;s not the best idea to &#39;keep it real.&#39;  But that was 2003, now in the days of social media, viral videos and tweets, it often shows that way too many people &#39;keep it real&#39; when they shouldn&#39;t.  A sad but unfortunate side effect of stupidity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/troy.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Troy Ave&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Troy Ave may think it&#39;s fine to keep it real&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Case in point, the recent shooting at New York&#39;s Irving Plaza before a T.I. show, where Brooklyn rapper Troy Ave, a gangsta rapper who leads the BSB crew, got into a seemingly random argument with allegedly another crew.  A street smart rapper would find a better time to take revenge, definitely not in a public place.  Instead, Troy Ave, losing his cool and keeping it real, started firing shots.  Even worse, he was caught on camera firing shots, a definite no-no for someone who, like a lot of criminals, can&#39;t legally own a gun.  Now everyone who knows what he looks like can watch the grainy video seeing Troy Ave looking for someone, firing shots and leaving the view.  And the worst of it all, Troy Ave&#39;s bodyguard, Banga, was the only fatality.  So while Troy Ave, seemingly on his way to the top, finds himself charged with Attempted Murder, Reckless Endangerment and Criminal Possession of a Weapon, and a fresh wound in the leg for shooting himself.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/troyaveshooting.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Shooting&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;But it can take just seconds to pull up this image of the shooting.&lt;/h4&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;This might have not been a big deal in 2003, but now, it can only take seconds for someone to screw up and have everyone find out.  Troy Ave, whose album Major Without A Deal sold a lousy 2,000 copies in his first week, must&#39;ve thought that street cred is the way to fame, but many rappers have been able to maintain their street cred without acting callously on camera.  So while people now know his name more than before, keeping it real likely has him locked him up behind bars for what fame he has gained.&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;p&gt;But you don&#39;t have to commit violent crimes to &#39;keep it real.&#39;  Just ask Azealia Banks, a female rapper who instead of making music (allegedly her contract won&#39;t let her), makes her rounds by constantly arguing with other rappers, celebrities and all of mankind on Twitter.  Some may think it&#39;s cool to talk trash about others, but there&#39;s a big difference between personal conversations and social media posts, which even deleted within seconds, will last a lifetime.  Azealia Banks, thinking it&#39;s cool to talk trash about others with foul language, has managed to offend almost everyone by &#39;keeping it real.&#39;  Yet strongly homophobic comments about singer Zayn Malik and twitter attacks on 14 year old actress Skai Jackson led to people standing up to her, as Azealia Banks was banned from Twitter for engaging in such foul and harsh language.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;And yet people would constantly mouth off and say the wrong thing back in the days.  But with social media out there, it&#39;s easier to know when people are saying stupid shit.  It&#39;s easier for people to show off and try to &#39;keep it real,&#39; as if they&#39;ll get more fans from it, but has Azealia Banks really accomplished anything?  I still don&#39;t know one song of hers, so whenever I hear about her, it&#39;s for the wrong reasons and not what she&#39;s supposed to be doing with her life.  So has &#39;keeping it real&#39; lead to any album sales?  Not really.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/azealia.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Azealia Banks&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Most people who know Azealia Banks associate her with bad Twitter behavior.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Plenty of people love to keep it real, even with a stunning lack of consequences for doing so.  It&#39;s as if people are totally forgetting about the consequences of their actions.  With social media a constant in our lives now, people are able to keep it real for the whole world to see, even if they don&#39;t intend everyone to see it.  Living in a world where anything that&#39;s shot on camera will make its way to the internet within hours or any tweet you make, no matter how much you regret it, will never go away.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/when-keeping-it-real-goes-wrong</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/when-keeping-it-real-goes-wrong</guid>
        
        
        <category>technology</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NBA Conference Finals Preview</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; As the Toronto Raptors defeated the Miami Heat in seven games, the Western and Eastern Conference Finals are now set.  It’s been a crazy ride so far, with surprise endings in some cases, but with four teams left to win the NBA Championship, who will win it all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/lowry.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Kyle Lowry&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;It wasn’t pretty, but Kyle Lowry led Toronto to their first Eastern Conference Finals.  Tough challenges await.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;It’s no surprise that the Golden State Warriors made it back to the Western Conference Finals, but their ride there has been nothing short of expected.  With Steph Curry a little banged up, missing four games, it seemed like Golden State would get challenged by the surprise Portland Trail Blazers.  And for the most part, they were tested, but with each test, Golden State proved to be just a little better, and with Steph Curry returning in Game 4, he saved his best in a thriller, scoring the majority of his points in the second half and overtime after a cold start.  In typical Steph Curry fashion, he put on a show, and while becoming the NBA’s first unanimous MVP ever, proved just how insane his game truly is.  Though Portland played great, the Golden State Warriors showed how elite they are, winning the series 4-1.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Most people, myself included, expected a Golden State-San Antonio matchup.  The Spurs played great during the season, and if not for the Warriors historic success, would have had the best record in the league.  But the Oklahoma City Thunder showed just how dangerous their duo of Kevin Durant and Russell Westbrook (or should it be Russell Westbrook and Kevin Durant) truly are, surprising the Spurs in a well fought series, winning 4-2.  With Russell Westbrook being perhaps the most underrated player in the NBA (someone I think compares favorably to Curry himself and arguably has a better all-around game but people considered not on that level), it’s no wonder the Spurs simply could not stop him, while Kevin Durant played his typical high scoring game.  But it was their defense, with the vastly underrated play of Steven Adams that really pushed them to the next level.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/westbrook.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Russell Westbrook&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Russell Westbrook’s style of play makes him impossible to defend...&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;The Eastern Conference, meanwhile, saw Cleveland easily sweeping the Atlanta Hawks behind some of the most insane three-point shooting outside of Golden State, where the Cavs made 25 threes in one game, a truly mind boggling performance.  Though the Eastern Conference improved from last year, it’s still not as strong as the West, as LeBron James and company are still clearly the best team in the East, sweeping both Detroit and Atlanta.  They’re playing their best ball by far right now, but whether they can beat Golden State or Oklahoma City remains to be seen.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/curry2.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Steph Curry&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;But Steph Curry’s game is even harder to stop.  An elite duel awaits!&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the flipside is the Toronto Raptors, making it to the Eastern Conference Finals for the first time.  They didn’t dominate by any means, losing both Game 1’s at home, but they fought, scratched and clawed their way past Indiana and Miami, with both series going to Game 7.  And though Kyle Lowry and DeMar DeRozan struggled at times, they came up big when their team needed it most, especially Lowry, who remains the heart and soul of the Raptors club.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Eastern Conference Finals looks lopsided to me.  I would be surprised if Toronto won more than one game, and would totally expect Cleveland to pull another sweep.  Perhaps Toronto can pull off the Game 1 upset due to Cleveland’s rust from all the time off, but Cleveland is leaps and bounds above Toronto.  Lowry will keep them close in at least one of their home games, but not enough consistency from DeRozan spells trouble for Toronto.  Miami would have had a better shot of winning against Cleveland, but injuries to Hassan Whiteside (not to mention Chris Bosh not available for the series) killed an otherwise outstanding performance from Dwyane Wade, keeping them from advancing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/lebron.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;LeBron James&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;No matter how much you may dislike LeBron James, you know you simply can’t stop him.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Western Conference Finals on paper looks like a better matchup, as a series with Curry, Westbrook, Durant, Klay Thompson and Draymond Green bring plenty of star power.  But while Westbrook and Durant will be hard to stop, the Warriors are on another level with Curry on the court.  There’s not a player like him, and though his shooting is mind-boggling and his offensive game his beyond crazy, it’s his supporting cast that makes them historically great, mainly the play of the impossible-to-defend Draymond Green, whose all-around game gives opponents headaches.  Oklahoma City will put up a good fight like Portland, but Golden State will find its way to victory.  I project Golden State to win the series in 5 games.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A potential repeat of last years Finals would be historically great, just like last year’s series was.  Cleveland played their hearts out last year without Kyrie Irving and Kevin Love.  The way they are playing right now, Cleveland shouldn’t be taken lightly, and they definitely have peaked at the right time.  But the Western Conference is a different beast, and Steph Curry and the Warriors are setting the tone for a new era in the NBA.  It won’t be easy for the Warriors, as long as LeBron is around, but in the end, the Warriors are my choice to cap off their historic season winning the NBA title again.  No one saw this coming five years ago, but Golden State has put together an impossible-to-beat roster without a dominating big man, something only Michael Jordan’s Bulls could pull off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The craziest season perhaps in NBA history is coming to an end, and with an even crazier summer coming, I expect to see some of the most exciting basketball to be played out in the coming weeks.  Still, the NBA Lottery on Tuesday will mean the most personally to me.  Can the Lakers win the lottery?  Will they even get a top pick?  Stay tuned, it’s going to be one heck of a show&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/booker.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Devin Booker&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Only my sis would think of Booger.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;NBA Lottery Notes - May 17, 2016&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a Laker fan, I can rejoice, they get to keep their pick, that is the good news.  Of course, the Lakers finish Number 2 again, except this year that was were they were supposed to be.  The winner of the lottery: the god-awful Philadelphia 76ers, the worst team in the league.  At least the Lakers didn&#39;t have to give them their pick.  The highlight of the night...my sister thought the Phoenix Suns representive at the Lottery had a last name of Booger.  Here&#39;s to you Devin Booker...or should I say, Devin Booger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/nba-conference-finals-preview</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/nba-conference-finals-preview</guid>
        
        
        <category>basketball</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Climate Change and Snow - The Real Story</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
#inhofe {
	float: right;
	padding: 20px;
}

.axis path,
.axis line {
  fill: none;
  stroke: #000;
  shape-rendering: crispEdges;
}


.pdxLine {
  fill: none;
  stroke: steelblue;
  stroke-width: 2px;
}

.pdxLine:hover {
	stroke-width: 4px;
}

.nycLine {
	fill: none;
	stroke: green;
	stroke-width: 2px;
}

.nycLine:hover {
	stroke-width: 4px;
}
svg {
	display: block;
	margin-left: auto;
	margin-right: auto;
	background-color: white;
	font: 10px sans-serif;
}

.key {
    padding: 10px;
    border-radius: 50%;
    display: inline-block;
}


&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Climate change is real.  97% of all scientists believe the Earth is getting abnormally hotter than usual because of greenhouse gases polluting the Earth.  But there are some people who believe it&#39;s a hoax.  Most likely it&#39;s to protect their greenhouse gas producing fuels and chemicals.  Others are religious nuts who hate science as it counters religion.  They&#39;ll find any excuse to discredit global warming and climate change as to protect their profit, and gain the support of those who disapprove man-made climate change, mostly members of the Republican Party.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;img/inhofe.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Jim Inhofe&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; id=&quot;inhofe&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;In Washington D.C., it snows virtually every winter.  Doesn&#39;t prove a thing.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;Enter Jim Inhofe, the senior Republican Senator of Oklahoma and for some reason, the chair of the Senate Committee on Environment and Public Works.  Senator Inhofe has long been a denier of climate change, and a cold winter day on February 26, 2015, Senator Inhofe blasted global warming as a hoax.  His reasoning: It was snowing outside.  He even brought in a snowball to a Congressional Hearing to back up his claim, because according to him, how can we have global warming when it&#39;s so cold outside.  So despite average temperatures trending upward since the 1970s, does Inhofe&#39;s snow theory hold up?&lt;/p&gt;
		
		&lt;p&gt;Anyone with half a brain knows it doesn&#39;t get hot in our Winter. Since the Earth&#39;s rotated at 24.5 degrees, we have different seasons and when our axis is away from the sun, it gets colder as opposed to the axis being towards the sun, when it gets hotter.  Yet Senator Inhofe thinks Global Warming only makes things hotter.  A native Portlander, I have seen many winters come and go in Portland with little to no snow, despite a decently cold temperature.  When I was younger, I saw a lot more snowy days in Portland.  Now, we&#39;ve had just a few years with any major snowstorms.  As you can see from the graph below, I&#39;ve compared snowfall levels of both Portland and New York City (where it is more likely to snow), and looking at the data, doesn&#39;t prove that Global Warming doesn&#39;t exist.&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;p&gt;As the data below shows, there is no reason to believe that snow has anything to do with global warming.  In fact, Portland shows a drop in snowfall over the years.  The snowstorm of 2008-2009 was a freak snowstorm for us here in Portland; we had not seen that much snow in that year.  But as the data shows, we in Portland saw little to no snow during the rest of that decade.  It&#39;s true that Portland doesn&#39;t represent the United States as a whole, but by Inhofe&#39;s thinking, there would be little to no variation in the yearly data.  Looking at the data for New York City, there&#39;s no variation in snow levels, varying year to year.  But this has nothing to do with temperature.  On the flipside is Phoenix, where it rarely, if ever, snows.  Senator Inhofe&#39;s snow argument wouldn&#39;t get much muster in Phoenix.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;I can&#39;t tell you where Senator Inhofe gets his ideas from.  But as someone who gets plenty of campaign money from the oil and gas industries, it would come as no shock if his opinions are being paid for.  After all, these companies are polluting the air with little regard to the environment.  But while that factor will always be there, it&#39;s Inhofe&#39;s religious stance that may be a greater cause of concern.  In 2012, Inhofe cited the Bible as irrefutable proof that climate change isn&#39;t man-made.  His quote: &lt;em&gt;&quot;[T]he Genesis 8:22 that I use in there is that &#39;as long as the earth remains there will be seed time and harvest, cold and heat, winter and summer, day and night.&#39; My point is, God&#39;s still up there. The arrogance of people to think that we, human beings, would be able to change what He is doing in the climate is to me outrageous.&quot;&lt;/em&gt; But really, why would God choose 2014 to become the hottest average temperature on the existence of Earth since they started measuring, and then break that record the following year.  Some things are easier to identify and prove than with God&#39;s will.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;h3 id=&quot;title&quot;&gt;Snowfall from 1871-2009 in New York City and Portland&lt;/h3&gt;
	&lt;div id=&quot;info&quot; style=&quot;width: 1100px;&quot;&gt;
   	&lt;div id=&quot;keys&quot;&gt;
      	&lt;p&gt;
            &lt;span class=&quot;key&quot; style=&quot;background: steelblue;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
            &lt;span class=&quot;key-text&quot;&gt;Portland&lt;/span&gt;
         &lt;/p&gt;
         &lt;p&gt;
         	&lt;span class=&quot;key&quot; style=&quot;background: green;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
         	&lt;span class=&quot;key-text&quot;&gt;New York&lt;/span&gt;
         &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;	
	&lt;script src=&quot;//d3js.org/d3.v3.min.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
	&lt;script&gt;

var margin = {top: 20, right: 20, bottom: 30, left: 50},
    width = 960 - margin.left - margin.right,
    height = 500 - margin.top - margin.bottom;

var formatDate = d3.time.format(&quot;%Y&quot;);

var x = d3.time.scale()
    .range([0, width]);

var y = d3.scale.linear()
    .range([height, 0]);

var xAxis = d3.svg.axis()
    .scale(x)
    .orient(&quot;bottom&quot;);

var yAxis = d3.svg.axis()
    .scale(y)
    .orient(&quot;left&quot;);

var pdxLine = d3.svg.line()
    .x(function(d) { return x(d.date); })
    .y(function(d) { return y(d.pdx); });
    
var nycLine = d3.svg.line()
    .x(function(d) { return x(d.date); })
    .y(function(d) { return y(d.nyc); });    
				
var svg = d3.select(&quot;body&quot;)
	 .append(&quot;svg&quot;)
    .attr(&quot;width&quot;, width + margin.left + margin.right)
    .attr(&quot;height&quot;, height + margin.top + margin.bottom)
  	 .append(&quot;g&quot;)
    .attr(&quot;transform&quot;, &quot;translate(&quot; + margin.left + &quot;,&quot; + margin.top + &quot;)&quot;);


d3.tsv(&quot;data/data.tsv&quot;, type, function(error, data) {
  if (error) throw error;
  
  x.domain(d3.extent(data, function(d) { return d.date; }));
  y.domain(d3.extent(data, function(d) { return d.nyc; }));

  svg.append(&quot;g&quot;)
      .attr(&quot;class&quot;, &quot;x axis&quot;)
      .attr(&quot;transform&quot;, &quot;translate(0,&quot; + height + &quot;)&quot;)
      .call(xAxis);

  svg.append(&quot;g&quot;)
      .attr(&quot;class&quot;, &quot;y axis&quot;)
      .call(yAxis)
    .append(&quot;text&quot;)
      .attr(&quot;transform&quot;, &quot;rotate(-90)&quot;)
      .attr(&quot;y&quot;, 10)
      .attr(&quot;dy&quot;, &quot;.71em&quot;)
      .style(&quot;text-anchor&quot;, &quot;end&quot;)
      .text(&quot;Snowfall (inches)&quot;);
  		
  svg.append(&quot;path&quot;)
      .datum(data)
      .attr(&quot;class&quot;, &quot;pdxLine&quot;)
      .attr(&quot;d&quot;, pdxLine);
 
 	svg.append(&quot;path&quot;)
 		.datum(data)
 		.attr(&quot;class&quot;, &quot;nycLine&quot;)
 		.attr(&quot;d&quot;, nycLine);
 
});

function type(d) {
  d.date = formatDate.parse(d.date);
  d.pdx = +d.pdx;
  d.nyc = +d.nyc;
  return d;
}

&lt;/script&gt;
	
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/climate-change-and-snow</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/climate-change-and-snow</guid>
        
        
        <category>politics,</category>
        
        <category>environmnent</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why I Voted for Hillary Clinton</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
	&lt;p&gt; At the end of this year, the United States is going to elect a new President, as Obama’s two terms reaches its end.  With that said, it’s important to me that we continue to make progress in building our country&#39;s economy, security and social progression.  The Republican’s presumptive candidate is Donald Trump, billionaire entrepreneur and reality TV star.  I will never vote for Donald Trump; he attracts the worst kind of attention and has led the most hateful campaign ever.  But it was much more difficult to choose between Hillary Clinton and Bernie Sanders, her Democrat competition for the Democratic nominee.  Though both candidates have their strengths and weaknesses, in the end I am throwing my support behind Mrs. Hillary Clinton.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Neither Hillary nor Bernie excite me as a candidate in the same way Barack Obama did back in 2008.  When Hillary Clinton announced her candidacy, most people assumed she was easily win, but Bernie surprised many by mounting an amazing grassroots style campaign that would make Obama envious.  I salute Bernie Sanders for bringing up many of the issues I consider the biggest detriments to a successful country; corruption of the Elite class, Citizens United allowing unlimited cash flow to candidates, and a power structure that favors money over the people.  Our problems are bigger than the issues themselves, with the structure of Congress and its ridiculous rules preventing any progress from happening.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float:left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/hillary.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Hillary Clinton&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Hillary Clinton isn’t perfect, but no candidate is&lt;/h4&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;But when it comes to ideas, Bernie Sanders’ ideas sound too good to be true and unrealistic, and to me, ideas are important.  As Comedian Dave Chappelle once said on his hit sketch show Chappelle’s Show, “Complex problems require complex solutions.”  And it’s true, it’s not as simple as ‘Free education for all’ or ‘Medicare for all’ as Bernie Sanders has suggested as solutions to raising the middle class.  While these things sound nice, they’re unattainable and unrealistic.  It’s for this reason that I didn’t vote for Bernie Sanders in the Democratic Primary.&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;blockquote class=&quot;blockquote-reverse&quot; style=&quot;font-size: 24px; border:none&quot;&gt;
Complex problems require complex solutions
		&lt;footer&gt;Dave Chappelle&lt;/footer&gt;
	&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the flip side, Hillary Clinton isn’t perfect as a candidate, and there are characteristics I certainly don’t like about her, but yet many of the issues the Republicans keep talking about are mere distractions and unimportant to the Presidential race.  The obvious issue the Republicans keep trying to convince us is the worst attack in our lifetime (nevermind 9/11) is the Benghazi attack.  Though it was tragic to see four men die in the attack, including our Ambassador to Libya, Chris Stevens, to hear Republicans say it, Hillary all but invited the terrorists involved to make the attack, and even though they have held numerous wasteful hearings trying to find out ‘the truth’, they’ve accomplished nothing but proven what a political witch-hunt this has become.  As House Majority leader Kevin McCarthy infamous stated, “Everybody thought Hillary Clinton was unbeatable, right? But we put together a Benghazi special committee, a select committee. What are her numbers today? Her numbers are dropping. Why? Because she’s untrustable. But no one would have known any of that had happened, had we not fought.”  Clearly, the issue is political partisanship at its worst, and yet, Hillary Clinton has held her own against United States House Select Committee on Benghazi chairman Trey Gowdy, never buckling down from hours of pointless and repetitive questions.  Republicans know she’s strong and know she’s a threat to taking over the Presidency chair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote style=&quot;font-size: 24px; border:none&quot;&gt;
Everybody thought Hillary Clinton was unbeatable, right? But we put together a Benghazi special committee, a select committee. What are her numbers today? Her numbers are dropping. Why? Because she’s untrustable. But no one would have known any of that had happened, had we not fought.
&lt;footer&gt;Kevin McCarthy, House Majority leader&lt;/footer&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second issue which Republicans keep talking about is the e-mail issue.  Hillary Clinton may have used a private server for using her personal e-mail address for official government uses, which sounds naive and irresponsible at best, but with laws on e-mails and record keeping were evolving at the time, it’s unclear whether Hillary broke any actual laws.  That’s not to say other politicians have done similar, whether it’s Condoleeza Rice, Colin Powell or Jeb Bush.  Yet no one cares ever bothered to investigate them like Hillary has been by the Republicans.  Same with Benghazi.  Thousands of people died on 9/11; if Al Gore were president, the Republicans would have spent eight years investigating him.  It’s their only recourse against a woman who’s not only strong but has the balls to take them on head-on.  Republicans claim this is a major trust issue, as many who don’t like Hillary don’t trust her, but Politicians on the whole are untrustworthy.  Every politician lies, and Hillary Clinton is no less untrustworthy than her opponents or friends, so as Bernie Sanders said during the first Democrat debate, “The american people are sick and tired of hearing about her [Hillary&#39;s] damn emails.”  Please, give me a break.&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;blockquote class=&quot;blockquote-reverse&quot; style=&quot;font-size: 24px; border:none&quot;&gt;
The american people are sick and tired of hearing about her damn emails!
		&lt;footer&gt;Bernie Sanders, regarding Hillary Clinton&#39;s email use&lt;/footer&gt;
	&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bill Clinton was the best president of my lifetime.  He did great wonders for the United States, and his centrist Liberal views were a plus for me.  Being married to Bill Clinton for many years, I would hope that Hillary has learned a thing or two from Bill on how to get things done.  To me, that is one of her biggest strengths; her unrelentless approach.  But unlike Bill, Hillary seems more willing to shift her views to make herself appeal to the Progressive left.  This would be fine for a Progressive, but I don’t consider myself that Liberal.  Bernie Sanders has pushed her towards his direction for better or worse.  And yes, Hillary has a goofy personality, kind of like Joe Biden but with a stronger aggressive side, which kind of turns me off.  However, with that aggressive personality is the ability to get things done, which she has accomplished throughout the years as Senator and Secretary of State.  Her experience with National Security issues is a plus, which is something the Republican candidate can’t say.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/trump3.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Donald Trump&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Infinite Thumbs Down - Anyone But Trump&lt;/h4&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best reason to vote for Hillary Clinton, is that despite all her faults with her personality and trustworthiness, she’s not Donald Trump.  Donald Trump would be a complete disaster as President of the United States.  Virtually everyone around the world can’t stand the guy; the only person who seems to like him is our supposed #1 geopolitical foe, Vladimir Putin of Russia, who like Trump is a bully incapable of listening to anybody.  Trump would make our country a joke, with other countries unwilling to work with a chauvinistic greedy xenophobic divisive putz.  We need someone who is serious about fixing our problems, rather than someone who thinks this is all a joke, like Trump has proven over and over again.  Having an unpredictable loose cannon that acts like a five year old when being criticized is a poor quality and completely unpresidential.  It’s not as easy as making mindless chants and gimmicks; being President requires intelligence and great decision making, something Donald Trump does not have.  Although Hillary Clinton is not the most mature person out there, anyone is better than a spoiled child who expects everyone to say ‘Yes’ to him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump is a poor businessman at best, lame reality TV star at best, and a horrible Presidential candidate who has completely destroyed the Republican party’s credibility.  America deserves better than this.  Truth be told, we’re screwed no matter who’s President; we still have incompetent Senators, Congressmen and Congresswomen who bicker like babies and refuse to work with each other in an attempt to win the game.  But we’ve made progress with Obama despite the Republicans obstructionist ways, despite the Recession left over from George W Bush’s Presidency.  We can’t replace Obama with an idiot who doesn’t know where Obama was born, thinks the Chinese invented global warming to improve their economy, acts like non-white foreigners are the root of all our nations problems, and most important, an idiot who has never given a damn about anyone else in his life other than himself.  Vote Hillary Clinton for President.  Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/why-i-voted-for-hillary-clinton</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/why-i-voted-for-hillary-clinton</guid>
        
        
        <category>politics</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to Adam&#39;s Blog 2.0 - The Rise of Jekyll</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;img/mthood.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Mt. Hood&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Mt. Hood&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learning new ways to make blog posts or any developing tools in general is something I have always enjoyed.  It&#39;s something encouraged by IBM, the parent company I work for.  With that said, I am revamping my blog post as its own entity, rather than part of the Express framework I&#39;m using for Bodie Web Design.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are the advantages of doing this, you ask?  Let me explain the ways to you in the most simplistic ways.  This new blog engine is powered by Jekyll, a static website generator powered by Ruby.  With it, I have more flexibility as to how I can layout my blog.  Gone are the days of sticking to one layout as I have been doing with my Jade-JSON backed blog posts.  Now I can use markdown files, which translates raw text to HTML.  For example, I would have to make parse my blogs with JSON, like in the first example below, then would retrieve those values with the Jade templating language, as seen in the second example below to convert them into html.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-javascript&quot; data-lang=&quot;javascript&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Example&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;err&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;title&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;err&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Example&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;date&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;err&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;May 4, 2016&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;description&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;err&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[{&lt;/span&gt;
                &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;paragraph&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hello World, I&#39;m a paragraph in JSON!&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
            &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;},&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
                &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;paragraph&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi Foobar, I&#39;m another paragraph in JSON!&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
            &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;],&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;image&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;err&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[{&lt;/span&gt;
                &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;name&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;img/image.jpg&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
                &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;caption&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;I&#39;m a caption!&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
            &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;}]&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-jade&quot; data-lang=&quot;jade&quot;&gt;.article
	- for (var x = 0; x &amp;lt; post.description.length; x++)
   - var y = x / 3       
   	if post.description[x].paragraph !== undefined
      	p #{post.description[x].paragraph}
      	p I&#39;m Jade!
         &lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Though this got me thinking code and algorithms, it also limited my flexibility, having to follow a set pattern for each post I made.  Not to mention the quotation marks for each piece of JSON code.  Enough to drive you mad.  JSON is easier to read than XML, but the quotation marks are maddening.  But with Jekyll, I can make my posts with pure raw text in markdown files, which are converted to HTML.  Now I can have the freedom to add additional content in my posts without having to write code in the html files being outputed from the markdown files.  Want to add a random h4 header?  All I got to do is this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt; I&#39;m an H4 header &lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Want to make an H4 header green, I can do this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 style=&quot;color: green&quot;&gt; Now I&#39;m a green H4 header&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt; And all I did was add html to my markdown file, rather than make some funky rule in my Jade Template to apply for one instance, check this out:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-html&quot; data-lang=&quot;html&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;h4&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;style=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;color: green&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; Now I&#39;m a green H4 header&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;/h4&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;   &lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another big change you&#39;ll see right off the bat is that my blog is now paginated.  Instead of everything on one page, it is now broken off to 10 posts per page.  At the time of this post, that&#39;s 4 pages of blog posts.  Much easier to navigate, less code to load, and a better, faster experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The possibilites are endless with Jekyll, and expect to see more power with my blogs and posts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/welcome-to-adams-blog-2</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/welcome-to-adams-blog-2</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ted Cruz - The Definition of Pathetic</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; I&#39;ve seen and read about many bad politicians in my lifetime.  Former Senator Trent Lott, who in 2002 claimed we’d be better off had we voted for racist Senator Strom Thurmond is one.  Former Illinois Governor Rod Blagojevich attempts to sell Obama’s Senate seat and other criminal activities is another.  Former Florida Congressman Mark Foley and his sexually explicit texts to teenage boys was also disturbing, along with the many congressmen and politicians who’ve cheated on their spouses, i.e. Newt Gingrich, Eliot Spitzer and Anthony Weiner.  But despite all those with questionable ethics, criminal policies and downright slanderous misgivings, no politician has or ever will be more pathetic, manipulative, uncooperative or untrustworthy than Senator Ted Cruz.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;img/booger.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Ted Cruz ate a booger.  Thanks sis for the reminder.&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Ted Cruz ate a booger.  Thanks sis for the reminder.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ted Cruz was elected as Senator for the ‘great’ state of Texas in 2012, part of the Tea Party’s wave of extremist anti-Obama candidates who think working for him and the Democrats is ‘part of the problem’.  Yet in short time, Ted Cruz has proven that he is self-centered, uncaring for anyone except his followers (though in reality he only cares about himself) and willing to destroy anything in his path just to get his way, alienating virtually all of his fellow Senators and Congressmen and Congresswomen in the process.  His extreme hatred for Obamacare was the main culprit, as Ted Cruz became popular amongst extremists and despised by everyone with a brain by partially shutting down the Government in a pathetic attempt to get rid of Obamacare.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Democrats controlling the Senate and Obama the President, there was no way they would agree to Ted Cruz’s demands to fund the Government without Obamacare.  Ted Cruz surely knew this, as a graduate cum laude at Princeton.  Yet to hear him say it, it was all the Democrats fault for shutting down the Government for two plus weeks, and would have done it again if he could.  Why?  Because they wouldn’t go along with his demands.  As if the Democrats would blindly do something he likes and get nothing in return.  But that is the Republican’s mantra these days, and Ted Cruz is the King of the Obstructionists in congress, the public face of the Tea Party extremists who think all Liberals have to do as they say or else, and should do everything according to the Bible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like any politician willing to do whatever to get people on his/her side, Ted Cruz frequently lies about just about everything.  He repeats the same lie over and over again and his fellow supporters will assume it&#39;s true, even though anyone who actually researches the topic at hand knows it&#39;s completely bogus.  The supporters WANT these things to be true, even when it&#39;s clearly the opposite that is true, so they’ll just assume it’s true.  Cruz plays into their fears and into their hands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;img/trust.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Trust: the last word anyone should associate with Ted Cruz.&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive pull-right&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Trust: the last word anyone should associate with Ted Cruz&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;p&gt;One of Cruz’s favorite lies is about Obamacare, which he believes is a catastrophic bill that has done nothing but kill jobs. Problem is, we’ve seen more jobs created since the inception of Obamacare than we’ve lost jobs.  Though the economy was quite bad when Obamacare first passed due to the Recession, it&#39;s ridiculous to claim it&#39;s killing jobs when the economy has grown since then. Yet Ted Cruz, on a personal mission to do anything to get rid of Obamacare, makes up reasons it&#39;s bad, repeating false claims and furthering using his manipulative ways to misinform his followers on what Obamacare actually is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ted Cruz can easily criticize just about every other politician or wannabe politician, saying ridiculous and often bogus claims, pointing out others flaws, whether true or not and shows little remorse for his words.  But when someone attacks him, my god, someone call the police! Cruz attacks Obama almost daily yet when Obama disagrees with something he suggests, such as the US-Iran deal, Ted Cruz suggests it’s outrageous for Obama to criticize him behind his back, and quote-unquote, should say it to his face, threatening to fight him in the process.  And being locked into a battle with Donald Trump, has managed to take mudslinging to a whole new level.  We need mature candidates, not those who act like fifth graders.  It&#39;s unfortunate that we live in the age of trash-talk TV and controversy sells, as Cruz takes advantage of the times by acting childish and idiotic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But despite all of these characteristics, the thing that is most irritating about Ted Cruz is his narcissistic intolerant attitudes towards others, waging war on those who stand in his way, making false claims about those he doesn&#39;t like, and his sincere belief that everything must be done according to the Bible.  These characteristics are more fitting for a terrorist than a politician, yet Ted Cruz continues to attack his enemies as Un-American, wrong on everything and somehow not deserving the same rights as Christians.  Cruz bashes any idea that’s Liberal, claiming most criminals are registered Democrats, which isn’t remotely true.  He claims Muslims are trying to take over the country with Sharia law, and that we need constant surveillance on all Muslim neighborhoods.  Cruz’s answer for this; make everything Christian-like.  But Ted Cruz’s biggest war is against the LGBT community, whom Cruz feels shouldn&#39;t have the same rights as Christians, that it&#39;s okay for them to be denied services and marriage while claiming Christians are the ones suffering by not being able to deny services to the LGBT community.  Despite the law being against his side and same-sex marriage being legalized, Cruz will try to convince you it&#39;s a states right issue and rewrite the Constitution in the process.  Too bad the Supreme Court overruled a ban on interracial marriage back in the day.  Maybe Cruz needs to read up in history rather than try to redefine it.  And now with the battle waging against transsexual bathroom use, Cruz claims keeping them out of their preferred bathrooms will keep little girls safe from grown men.  Too bad this isn&#39;t about grown men, it&#39;s about transgendered women who will look out of place in a men’s bathroom, as if it’s okay to tell them;  ‘Hey, I’m only in here because of what’s underneath my underwear, come and get me.’ ALL people have rights to live their lives freely, not just Christians. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;img/zodiac.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Ted Cruz isn&#39;t the Zodiac Killer...he&#39;s worse than the Zodiac Killer!&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Ted Cruz isn&#39;t the Zodiac Killer...he&#39;s worse than the Zodiac Killer!&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ted Cruz has all the qualities of at worst, a terrorist and at best, a controlling husband.  Would he treat his wife the way he treats his fellow congressmen and congresswomen?  It doesn&#39;t work in a marriage, why would it work in the Senate?  He thinks he can do whatever he wants and expects everyone to follow him.  People can appreciate him for standing up to their values, but we live in a world that wants results.  Ted Cruz accomplished NOTHING.  All he did was make himself look better, and that’s the only thing Ted Cruz has ever cared about, the man in the mirror.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I am writing this blog, news broke that Ted Cruz officially dropped out of the race, having been beaten pretty badly in Indiana.  My first two words were: Good Riddance.  My next three words, pardon my language, is: Good Fuckin’ Riddance.  Ted Cruz has been nothing but a complete disaster as a Senator, Presidential candidate, and as a person.  And even though we are left with Donald Trump as the Republican candidate, whose racist comments and ridiculous lies are just as bad if not even worse than Ted Cruz’s, I can truly say that Ted Cruz is far worse than Donald Trump, mainly for being such a religious extremist.  Whether Donald Trump is genuinely pathetic or pretending is in question; it’s not a question for Ted Cruz.  I never thought Ted Cruz would even make it this far, but the result was as predicted, Americans have rejected Ted Cruz the same way his fellow Senators and Congressmen have.  So here’s to you Congressman Peter King, who can get rid of the cyanide he jokingly claimed would take if Cruz won the nomination.  Here’s to you Senator Lindsey Graham, who could very well now shoot Ted Cruz and not get convicted.  Here’s to you Satanists who roundly reject Ted Cruz as a Satanist even though John Boehner referred to him as ‘Lucifer in the Flesh,’ proving that perhaps Ted Cruz is even more evil than Satan himself.  Here’s to those who think Ted Cruz is the Zodiac Killer, you can move on and live your lives freely and in peace.  And of course, to all the American’s who are open to other people’s opinions and respect people who aren’t like them, this one’s for you.  Good bye Ted Cruz.  The fight to completely remove him from public office and out of our lives begins today!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/ted-cruz-the-definition-of-pathetic</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/ted-cruz-the-definition-of-pathetic</guid>
        
        
        <category>politics</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Don&#39;t Be Stupid on the Internet</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last night was the first round of the NFL Draft, a time for the best ranked prospects to join the NFL, a joyous time for those to hear their name called. Yet in this day and age, being stupid sells, and being stupid on the Internet never goes away no matter how hard you try. That&#39;s why all the buzz today is around Laremy Tunsil, a highly ranked offensive tackle who ended up falling to the 13th pick to the Miami Dolphins, as someone allegedly hacked into his Twitter account and posted a video of him smoking a bong through a gas mask earlier in the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;img/tunsil.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;This should have been the highlight of Laremy Tunsil&#39;s night, but everyone&#39;s talking about the bong.&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;h4&gt;This should have been the highlight of Laremy Tunsil&#39;s night, but everyone&#39;s talking about the bong.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;p&gt;People are going to be stupid, you can&#39;t stop that.  But being stupid on the Internet is a big mistake.  Once something gets posted online, it never goes away, it exists in some form of data and will follow you for the rest of your life, like a bad tattoo.  For Laremy Tunsil’s case, his Twitter account was closed just minutes after the video hit the web, yet anyone reading about the NFL Draft or the news in general has already seen an image of said video, knowing it exists.  That never goes away no matter how hard you try.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s true that people have the right to post things they think are cool, like smoking pot through a bong.  That doesn&#39;t mean people should post things like that, especially if it&#39;s illegal.  Unfortunately for Tunsil, his Instagram was hacked later that night, posting a cell conversation with an Ole Miss staff member about payments, which as anyone knows, is a major violation in college football.  Tunsil manned up and admitted what he did, but the fallout will be far worse than that, with investigations at Ole Miss likely to start because of this.  Why anyone would ever save a text message talking about rule-breaking is also stupid, as any smart person knows not to leave a trail of any kind.  Digital trails are especially easy to track in this day and age.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This doesn&#39;t just apply to athletes and celebrities, who are more likely to be targeted for their fame, but anyone can say something stupid online, often controversial, sometimes illegal suggestions.  Miles away from the NFL Draft, John Martin Ross, a 61 year old man from Medford, Oregon was arrested for threatening President Obama.  Among the evidence found, online rants complaining about Obama and suggesting Obama should be shot and killed.  This dumb gentleman has a right to complain about Obama, but that doesn&#39;t mean he should use such strong language.  Anyone can read it and call the cops if violence is implied.   A search warrant to his house led to the discovery of pipe bombs, setting this dumb gentleman up for even more harsh punishment, and as the owner of the words he said online, they can be used against him in the court of law.  Mr. Ross wrote on his Facebook: “I guess you can’t tell the world you hate Obama so much you will shoot him.”  And it’s true, you can’t.  Why?  Because threatening to shoot someone is not only immoral but illegal.  The First Amendment doesn’t protect you from it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Social media posts tell a lot about people, probably more info than needed.  If you&#39;re willing to share your thoughts publicly, anyone can access them, from strangers to employers, so on.  You own your thoughts, and sharing them comes with consequences if not handled properly.  Of course, it comes with great responsibility as well.  Don’t want people to see you smoking a bong but want to show your friends?  Make it private, or better yet, show them in person.  Be smart.  Thinking about harming someone? Only an idiot would share their thoughts with someone else, especially online.  The more that people know, the less successful you&#39;ll be at pulling it off.  And it&#39;s definitely not the way to get attention.  Texts come at face value, no sarcasm or emotion appears with said text.  So please, next time you want to put something stupid on the Internet, don&#39;t do it.  It could cost you dearly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, people like Laremy Tunsil and John Martin Ross are becoming more common these days than not.  These days, news spread like wildfire and anyone can say something that can become viral in seconds.  For people of a certain celebrity like Tunsil, there’s always a price to pay for being famous, and that is that people will find anything against you to humiliate you because of fame and jealousy.  It’s up to them at the end of the day to find a balance between living life freely and avoiding missteps.  As for common people like John Martin Ross, it all comes down to knowing that you’re not invincible.  People often post negative stuff online to avoid physical confrontation with other people, thinking they can’t be caught without a care in the world.  But when stupid people bring up violence, chances are the good people will do the right thing and report you.  Sadly, in these days, when children are learning to swear at younger ages and adults are voting for Presidential candidates who often say derogatory things, social media brings out the worst in people and the stupidest thoughts.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/dont-be-stupid-on-the-internet</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/dont-be-stupid-on-the-internet</guid>
        
        
        <category>technology</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Curse of Donald Sterling Lives</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Growing up, I didn&#39;t think much of the Los Angeles Clippers. Why should I have? They were a complete joke, a bumbling group of losers who couldn&#39;t win squat, couldn&#39;t put together a decent roster and worst of all had an incompetent owner who wouldn&#39;t spend any money to keep what little talent they had. It wasn&#39;t until the other owners handed them Chris Paul in an effort to keep him from being traded to the Laker did the Clippers finally start to look like a real basketball team. But as the Lakers sunk to the floor, have the Clippers overtaken them? Not even close. No matter how talented the Clippers are, they’ll always be in second place, and incapable of winning the title. Whether they like it or not, they are defined by their disgraceful former owner Donald Sterling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;img/sterling.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Everything Clippers related is tied to Donald Sterling, the joke.&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;h4&gt;Everything Clippers related is tied to Donald Sterling, the joke.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The Clippers had an obvious crisis two years ago when Donald Sterling was recorded making numerous racist remarks about his fans, bringing the Clippers to national headlines, as people were disgusted with their idiotic owner and the players angry over the comments as well.  Even after kicking Sterling to the curb and being bought by Microsoft billionaire Steven Ballmer with his own money, the Clippers are still losers compared to the Lakers, even if they’re winning more than the Lakers.  They haven&#39;t completely shaken the bad aura of Donald Sterling, affecting their attitude and play in the process, often finding themselves on the wrong end of disappointment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Clippers have never made it to the Western Conference finals, let alone the NBA finals in their history, from their foundings as the Buffalo Braves to their unnoticeable years as the San Diego Clippers and of course, as the ‘Donald Sterling joined L.A. because he couldn’t beat the Lakers, so he joined them‘ Los Angeles Clippers. They had a chance last year but blew a 3-1 lead against Houston.  Typical Clippers blunders, one joke after another, and had home court advantage to boot after 4 games.  This despite having a talented roster led by Chris Paul and Blake Griffin, who rank as two of the most talented players in the NBA.  And this year, with a possible chance to play Golden State without Steph Curry, they manage to lose both Blake Griffin and Chris Paul for the season in the same game. Beating Portland just became a lot tougher, if they can even do that at all.  But one has to wonder how the Clippers keep messing things up?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They have a great coach in Doc Rivers; the only coach with NBA title winning pedigree, maturity and understanding of the Donald Sterling mess, really the only coach capable of bringing the team together and sympathizing with their plight as well.  Chris Paul is an elite point guard, great leader and the heart and soul of the team.  You’d think those two would bring the character the Clippers need.  Instead, they have obnoxious, selfish players who gloat like Blake Griffin and DeAndre Jordan.  Blake Griffin, the guy who broke his hand punching an assistant trainer in a stupid fight, costing him a month of action. DeAndre Jordan, who waffled between leaving for Dallas and staying with the Clippers, loving every minute of the attention he got via the so-called Emoji Wars.  Unfortunately, it&#39;s these two who carry the team&#39;s me-first Lob City gloating attitude that makes the Clippers the underachieving team they are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Lakers never acted like that during any of their prime years.  Yet the Clippers seem to casually stroll into games like it doesn&#39;t care, lacking the instinct to perform to its potential.  They wouldn&#39;t even be a playoff team without Chris Paul; he’s the only player with heart, which goes without saying.  Is it because of Donald Sterling’s past influence? The feeling they’ll never pass the Lakers in prestige?  Maybe their key players are immature cry baby&#39;s with questionable character flaws.  Whatever the case, it&#39;s apparent that while Steve Ballmer can throw a whole bunch of money to try to make the Clippers a serious team, they&#39;ll never get rid of the curse that is Donald Sterling. So while Laker fans are saddened by their team&#39;s recent struggles, it compares nothing to being the sad joke that is the Los Angeles Clippers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/the-curse-of-donald-sterling-lives</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/the-curse-of-donald-sterling-lives</guid>
        
        
        <category>basketball</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Oregon Primaries - Ted Cruz need not apply</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As we&#39;re weeks away from Oregon’s Primary election, May 17th, it has become clear that for the first time in ages, Oregonians everywhere will actually have a say for the primaries. As one of the last states, the candidate has typically been decided before April, but this year we’re in a dead heat on both sides of the puzzle. With Kentucky the only other state with their primary the same day, Oregon at last will get the attention it needs for determining each party&#39;s nominee for President.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;img/donkey.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Don&#39;t we all wish we could do that to Ted Cruz.&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;h4&gt;Don&#39;t we all wish we could do that to Ted Cruz.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Obviously, Oregon is a Liberal state; it&#39;s going to vote Democrat for the Presidential election no matter who wins the race.  Hillary Clinton and Bernie Sanders are the two choices to pick from.  Hillary Clinton stands out as a former Senator, First Lady and Secretary of State, yet her campaign isn&#39;t as strong as it should be, with issues of trustworthiness being a big concern.  Bernie Sanders, an Independent Senator from Vermont and admitted Socialist, has come seemingly out of nowhere to pick up support from the Progressives who hate the fact that the system is rigged to favor the millionaires and billionaires.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet there are conservatives in Oregon as well, and they have their candidates.  Donald Trump leads the way with his big mouth and frequent racist divisive comments, yet Republicans are trying anything they can to keep him out of office. Ted Cruz, the religious nutcase Senator from Texas who hates to compromise, shows no appreciation for non-conservative thoughts and seems to hate everyone that&#39;s not Christian is also in the running. John Kasich, the Governor of Ohio, hangs on by a thread, hoping for a contested convention as he’s only won his home state, despite being the most traditional candidate left and the most reasonable of the bunch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can&#39;t say I&#39;m excited about any of the candidates, but I know one thing I am determined to see: that neither Donald Trump nor Ted Cruz get elected as President.  Both of these men (if we can even call them men, they act like a bunch of babies) are ridiculously unqualified and share absolutely pathetic views on the world, not to mention their hate filled speech.  I&#39;m not crazy about either Hillary or Bernie but either one would be an easy choice over those two dweebs. John Kasich is a decent man but is lucky to be where he is and lacks charisma to get people to vote for him.  With the Republicans being so angry, I would be shocked if they settled on Kasich since he’s actually willing to compromise to get things done, an apparent no-no with Republicans these days.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;img/bernie.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Millionaires and Billionaires hate Bernie Sanders.&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;h4&gt;Millionaires and Billionaires hate Bernie Sanders.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;As a native Oregonian, I can tell you proudly that Ted Cruz would not like our state at all, at least the Portland area.  So as news rolled last night that the Kasich and Cruz campaigns have apparently agreed to coordinate primaries to best keep Trump from gaining the magic number of delegates, it was no surprise that Cruz agreed to let Kasich have Oregon and New Mexico in exchange for Indiana.  Whether Cruz actually follows through or stabs Kasich in the back as he does with everyone else remains to be seen, but Cruz has no chance to win Oregon’s Republican primary.  With the largest percentage on non-religious people per capita in the state and a largely Progressive population, Ted Cruz would have a better chance convincing Oregonians he’s actually a woman than he does of convincing them to vote for him.  For once, I’ll thank Ted Cruz for not even bothering showing up to my home state.  It’s embarrassing enough to have him living in the same country as I do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our system for electing politicians, creating rules and regulations and basically everything tied to the government is broken, corrupt and filled with greed.  Bernie Sanders has emphatically made that the centerpiece of his campaign, and I have much respect for Bernie for mentioning this as the big problem.  With the passing of Citizens United in 2010 allowing unlimited cash flow to campaigns, it’s easy for those without money to get any say at all, having their voices drowned out by money and big corporations.  Gerrymandering congressional districts designed to drown out minority voters, prejudice tactics to keep people from voting and congressional rules that prevent bills from even reaching the floor have turned our system into a cesspool for corruption.  Bernie Sanders inspires people to understand the voice for the common man, which is why people are enthusiastic for him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the downside to Bernie Sanders is his ideas of fixing the broken system.  I wish we could live in a Utopia like he offers, with free healthcare, free college tuition, $15.00 plus minimum wage, and a total dismantling of the millionaires and billionaires of Wall Street.  But it’s never going to happen.  We’re always going to have Republicans on the other side who find these ideas too expensive and burdensome for the wealthy.  Like it or not, some Republicans have decent ideas and fiscally speaking, they’re worth at least exploring as a compromise; unfortunately, their voices are drowned out by the extremists unwilling to negotiate and expecting their way.  This is where Bernie Sanders ultimately fails to me.  I don’t see him having the balls to be aggressive and standing up to these Republicans if leading the way.  Another issue I have with Bernie is my appreciation for moderation.  Nothing about Bernie economically says moderation.  It’s all about attacking Wall Street and their rich snobs.  While it’s true they are driven by greed and power, I also find it necessary for us to work together, not pit sides against another.  We need to find ways to work with them for more business friendly ideas to improve the economy.  Like anything, being in the middle represents the best of both worlds, and the only realistic way to get anything done.  To me, Hillary Clinton would be an easy choice for this except for her sometimes brash personality and somewhat goofy immature attitude she displays.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;img/hillary.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Republicans REALLY hate Hillary Clinton.&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;h4&gt;Republicans REALLY hate Hillary Clinton.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Hillary Clinton, unlike Bernie Sanders, is more well-rounded with experience on all sides of the issues, from economic to foreign policy issues, and clearly has the personality to get things done, never afraid to fight.  But yet her ideas are average at best, as she’s being drawn further to the left to fend off Bernie Sanders’ obvious charismatic ways.  I know Hillary Clinton would be better handled to tackle on foreign policy issues, a big concern of mine with her experience as Secretary of State, and she has more balls to tackle on the Republicans across the aisle, but Republicans have an extreme hatred for Hillary Clinton and would treat her as they have Obama for the past seven years.  Unfortunately, I’m not convinced Hillary would be any more willing to reason with them than they would with her.  During the first Democratic debate, Hillary declared Republicans as her favorite enemy, kind of an immature thing to say to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But in terms of ideas, her beliefs are more reasonable, such as improving Obamacare to be more cost friendly rather than completely revamp it as a single-payer system with Medicare for all, which again, sounds nice, but isn’t realistic.  They aren’t nearly as far-fetched as Bernie Sanders extreme ideas.  But yet, Hillary doesn’t excite me at all.  Her personality is a turnoff for me, and I do consider her somewhat of an opportunist, changing beliefs to better fit her electorate rather than being the more centrist Democrat her husband Bill was, which made him the best President of my lifetime, in my opinion (keep in mind I was born in the Reagan days).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m confident both races in Oregon will be one-sided.  Oregon is ripe with Progressives who love Bernie.  Most bumper stickers I see are for Bernie Sanders, and it’s no surprise for me.  Bernie will beat Hillary easily, with the young white electorate far outweighing the minority support which Oregon doesn&#39;t have much of.  The Republicans are less clear but Donald Trump fits the angry Republicans better than Ted Cruz the religious nutcase.  The fact he would let John Kasich have a better opportunity says that Ted Cruz could never win our state, he could only win the state if he was the only candidate, and even then he would barely beat ‘Other’. So Donald Trump is the likely winner on the Republican side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the end, while my heart says Bernie Sanders is the best choice, for understanding people’s frustrations with the system the best, my brain says Hillary Clinton for providing the most realistic approach to solving problems and being the most experienced person to handle our problems.  Whether I should follow my heart or my brain is the big issue I haven&#39;t settled completely on yet.  The rest of me says anyone but Donald Trump or Ted Cruz, as those two imbeciles would turn our country into a joke.  In the end, that&#39;s the most important thing to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/the-oregon-primaries-ted-cruz-need-not-apply</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/the-oregon-primaries-ted-cruz-need-not-apply</guid>
        
        
        <category>politics</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
