<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adam's Blog</title>
    <description>A blog about whatever is on Adam's mind.</description>
    <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2016 19:28:47 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2016 19:28:47 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Making A Murderer - Brendan Dassey's Redemption</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; When I watched Netflix's &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/entertainment/2016/01/19/making-a-murderer-my-thoughts-on-the-steven-avery-case&quot;&gt;Making a Murderer&lt;/a&gt; early in January, the biggest puzzling thing about that case was that Steven Avery's nephew Brendan Dassey was convicted of anything at all, much less for the murder of Teresa Halbach based on a clearly coerced confession.  As news hit yesterday that a Federal judge in Milwaukee agreed, overturning the conviction, I can't help but feel relieved that Dassey got some redemption.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/dassey.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Brendan Dassey.&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Light at the end of the tunnel for Brendan Dassey&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Clearly, Brendan Dassey had nothing to do with the murder.  Watching the confession tape, it's clear that Dassey was manipulated by the cops.  Thankfully, the Federal judge in Milwaukee rightfully pointed out that the police who interviewed him made up false promises and Dassey, with a low IQ, seemed eager to tell the cops what they wanted so he could go back home, as the police promised him.  Of course, they lied their asses off, and Dassey was arrested after the false confession.  With all the talk about police corruption around the country, it's not a surprise they would do this.  Even worse, Dassey, just 16 at the time, did not have his mother as was required, as he needed her help with his low IQ.  And of course, his initial defense attorney was not present and seemed too eager to make a deal with the prosecutors in exchange for grilling Steven Avery.  The Federal judge deemed he was excited by the media coverage and did nothing to help his client.  Had police followed protocol, Dassey's mother would have set them straight, but instead, they bullied him and arrested him while he was too mentally disabled to understand what was going on.  The prosecution has 90 days to bring him back to trial, but since his false confession was the only thing that got him convicted, it's unlikely they would do so.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The bigger question remains, how does affect Steven Avery?  It was my opinion that there wasn't enough evidence to convict him.  Most of the evidence was coincidential at best; the blood in the RAV4, the key found at the dresser, and so on.  Not to mention a lack of motive.  His lawyers fought hard and presented an arguable case in my opinion.  But while some have argued that the Manitowoc County police framed him and planted evidence, I still find this kind of ridiculous.  I do believe they were too eager to investigate Steven Avery since he was the last person to be seen with Teresa Halbach.  Just like the initial rape case he wrongfully spent in prison.  They clearly had a bone to pick with Avery and were so focused on him, they ignored the evidence that pointed to the real rapist.  It's possible they planted evidence, but I don't think they killed her.  Someone with a grudge against Avery could've very well killed Halbach.  After all, they never found the body.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;As for Brendan Dassey, the system was rigged against him, as it is for many people falsely accussed and convicted of crimes.  The police were so eager to place him at the scene of the crime that they bullied him into telling them what they wanted to hear to fit their story.  It happens to too many people, targeting those who are vulnerable, mental disabilties amongst them.  How the jury convicted him of all charges; murder, rape and mutilation of a corpse, which Steven Avery wasn't even convicted of all those charges, is quite puzzling.  Different jury aside and different lawyers (not as good as Avery's), the jurors took his false words at face value and didn't consider anything else.  That the was only evidence they had against him, basically.  Now that the conviction has been overthrown, they have nothing against him.  It goes to show how corrupt our legal system and police officers can get.  I've read plenty of stories, more so recently, about mass police corruption in Baltimore, Cleveland and Ferguson, painting a grim picture of officers taking advantage of minorities, and it can certainly happen to anyone the police wants to target.  While it's easy for some to claim &quot;The police is always right,&quot; while claiming &quot;It's wrong to accuse police of acting stupidly,&quot; clearly anyone can be corrupt, including those who serve.  At the end of the day, Brendan Dassey got his redemption and hopefully those police officers would get punished for not following protocol.  There are too many good police officers getting lumped with the bad ones.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;It's good to know that Brendan Dassey got his conviction overturned.  If I were him, I would file a lawsuit against the Manitowoc County police, like Steven Avery did years earlier.  It would also be good for Dassey to move as far away from the county as he reasonably could.  Probably not realistic, but he deserves better, just like Steven Avery.  Now we'll wait to see what happens to him.  Can they prove his innocence?  Will they get better results on the blood in the RAV4?  What about the biased juror?  There are way too many questions left unanswered about Steven Avery's case.  In the meantime, we can rejoice that Brendan Dassey got his redemption for something he clearly had no involvement in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/entertainment/2016/08/13/making-a-murderer-brendan-dasseys-redemption</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/entertainment/2016/08/13/making-a-murderer-brendan-dasseys-redemption</guid>
        
        
        <category>entertainment</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Pledge</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.article span {
	font-size: 1.1em;
	font-weight: bold;
}
@media (max-width: 512px) {
	h3, p, img {
		clear: both;
	}
	.blog-pic {
		max-width: 100%;
	}
	.blog-pic h4 {
		max-width: 100%;	
	}
}
&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Three months from today, on November 8th, the country I call home, the United States of America, will elect a new President. Our country's future is at stake.  On one hand is Hillary Clinton, Former First Lady, Senator of New York and Secretary of State.  On the other hand is Donald Trump, who can simply be described as a Tyrannical Racist Ugly Misogynistic Pig.  I am sick and tired of hearing about this fool.  Everything he says is stupid, childish and filled with hate.  There are a plethora of reasons not to vote for this degenerate, I've managed to find one-hundred reasons, but the reasons don't stop there.  He has zero qualities of a worthy President and even less qualities of a proud American. This is why I am taking a pledge to no longer refer to him by his name and pledge to start calling him simply as The Idiot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Happy &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/CincoDeMayo?src=hash&quot;&gt;#CincoDeMayo&lt;/a&gt;! The best taco bowls are made in Trump Tower Grill. I love Hispanics! &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/ufoTeQd8yA&quot;&gt;https://t.co/ufoTeQd8yA&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/k01Mc6CuDI&quot;&gt;pic.twitter.com/k01Mc6CuDI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Donald J. Trump (@realDonaldTrump) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/728297587418247168&quot;&gt;May 5, 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Claiming to like Hispanics by eating 'their' food is a stupid attempt at getting their support.&lt;/h4&gt;	
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;On Immigration&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Idiot is flat out wrong on immigration.  When the Idiot first entered the race, he managed to set the tone for his whole campaign by saying &lt;span&gt;&quot;When Mexico sends its people, they're not sending their best... They're bringing drugs. They're bringing crime. They're rapists. And some, I assume, are good people.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  This obviously appeals to racist bigots who hate all things Hispanic, but most immigrants are good people and only leads to discrimination against Hispanics in general, no matter their legal status.  He even had the nerve to ask &lt;span&gt;&quot;Well, somebody's doing the raping, Don (Lemon)! I mean somebody's doing it! Who's doing the raping? Who's doing the raping?&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  As if every rapist in the United States is somehow undocumented and from Mexico?  Not true!  The Idiot doesn't have any ideas to fix our broken immigration system other than to say &lt;span&gt;&quot;Mexico's going to pay for the wall.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  Historically speaking, walls have never been effective and anyone wanting to cross the border will find ways to get over the stupid wall.  It's especially stupid to think that Mexico will pay for something they don't want.  Stronger border security is the best way to go.  Not bashing all undocumented immigrants, singling them out for committing crimes when crimes are committed by all races, genders and religions, or building a stupid wall.  The immigration system isn't perfect, but with over 11 million undocumented immigrants, the solution isn't as easy as treating all of them as criminals and deporting them.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;On Terrorism&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Idiot is flat out wrong on terrorism.  Keeping us safe is not as easy as saying &lt;span&gt;&quot;Donald J. Trump is calling for a total and complete shutdown of Muslims entering the United States.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  This does nothing to stop attacks like the ones in Boston, Orlando, Fort Hood and San Bernardino, all committed by Muslim-Americans, many of whom were born in America, and like his attacks on immigrants, unfairly places the blame on foreigners, treating them all as potential criminals rather than people.  An actual strategy to stop Terrorism requires working with our allies to attack Terrorists, rather than declaring war on all of Islam, as the Idiot has clearly done multiple times &lt;span&gt;&quot;I think Islam hates us.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  That only encourages Terrorists like ISIS to continue their fight and justify their message that somehow &quot;The West hates them,&quot; even though that's not true.  They're already using the Idiot's words for propaganda.  This is from someone who didn't think ISIS was even our fight to begin with, &lt;span&gt;&quot;Let Syria and ISIS fight. Why do we care? Let ISIS and Syria fight. And let Russia, they're in Syria already, let them fight ISIS.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  The Idiot's methods for defeating Terrorism include committing war crimes, &lt;span&gt;&quot;The other thing with the terrorists is you have to take out their families, when you get these terrorists, you have to take out their families,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; creating a national registry for Muslims &lt;span&gt;&quot;I would certainly implement that, absolutely,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; singling out refugees as the only ones capable of committing attacks at home with the false idea that &lt;span&gt;&quot;There is 'no system to vet' refugees from the Middle East,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; and using three little words, &lt;span&gt;&quot;In his remarks today, President Obama disgracefully refused to even say the words 'Radical Islam.' For that reason alone, he should step down. If Hillary Clinton, after this attack, still cannot say the two words 'Radical Islam' she should get out of this race for the Presidency.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  Coming from a man who claims &lt;span&gt;&quot;I know more about ISIS than the generals do,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; it's not surprising with his idiotic ideas that he knows nothing about fighting terrorists or the Middle East in general.  Of course, when 49 innocent people were killed by an ISIS supporter in Orlando, all this Idiot could do was take credit for being 'right' about terrorism, even though he was dead wrong &lt;span&gt;&quot;Appreciate the congrats for being right on radical Islamic terrorism, I don't want congrats, I want toughness and vigilance. We must be smart!&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/fake-tweet.png&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Idiot&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;This Idiot thought this was true.  It's not even remotely true.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;On Race Relations&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Idiot is flat out wrong on race relations.  Obama is not responsible for making race relations worse, as the Idiot claims &lt;span&gt;&quot;I'm a unifier, unlike our president now, I'm a unifier&quot;&lt;/span&gt;.  It's people like The Idiot who refuse to accept the fact that we elected an African American President (twice).  It's ridiculous for the Idiot to claim that blacks are responsible for most gun crimes in the country, all while siding with White Supremacists and not being outraged by their support &lt;span&gt;&quot;I don't know anything about David Duke.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;   The Idiot targets blacks, Hispanics, and Muslims, yet with White Supremacists, he retweets their racist, anti-Semitic imagery while running a campaign tailored for their policies, no matter what the Idiot says otherwise.  That's why David Duke is so enthusiastic about The Idiot's campaign.  The Idiot frequently injects racist names when discussing African Americans &lt;span&gt;&quot;Our great African American President hasn't exactly had a positive impact on the thugs who are so happily and openly destroying Baltimore!&quot;&lt;/span&gt; or with Hispanics &lt;span&gt;&quot;The protesters in New Mexico were thugs who were flying the Mexican flag. The rally inside was big and beautiful, but outside, criminals!&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  This divisive attitude has fueled the anger that had led to more shootings and violence throughout the nation.  For someone who claims &lt;span&gt;&quot;I am least racist person there is,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; he has done nothing but attacked African Americans, Hispanics, Muslims, Asians and just about every other minority with bigoted hate-filled spew.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/donald-trump-star.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Idiot&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;The Idiot's campaign is catered for White Supremacists: That's why he always retweets their ideas rather than dismiss them as hate-speech.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;On Guns&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Idiot is flat out wrong on guns.  No one is trying to get rid of the 2nd Amendment, despite the Idiot claims that &lt;span&gt;&quot;Hillary Clinton wants to abolish the Second Amendment.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  Increasing background checks a little is not the mass destruction of gun rights.  It's protected to keep the guns out of the hands from those who don't need them; criminals and terrorists.  These opinions are bought by the NRA, and their corruption and lack of empathy on gun shootings must stop. Having a gun on you doesn't guarantee your survival from an attack, &lt;span&gt;&quot;The bullets were going one way, not the other way. And if they were, if somebody had protection, a few people, not all, a few people had protection we would not have had 130 people dead.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  Too bad those who commit these acts are more prepared and have stronger weapons than a simple handgun for protecting.  Handguns won't stop suicide bombers who want to die, powerful assault weapons designed to kill or trucks driven by maniacs.  Requiring teachers to have guns will make those wanting to shoot up a school go after the teacher first, &lt;span&gt;&quot;Let me tell you, if you had a couple teachers with guns in that room, you would have been a hell of a lot better off.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  We can't live our lives waiting for someone to shoot us, and we shouldn't have to.  It's way too easy for criminals to get a hold of guns, with all the loopholes the NRA wants to leave open.  This Idiot even claims that Hillary Clinton wants to release violent criminals from jail, claiming &lt;span&gt;&quot;This is Hillary Clinton's agenda, too, to release the violent criminals from jail. She wants them all released.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  Too many people have died and nothing is being done about it, yet The Idiot only shows compassion for the victims and their loved ones if the perpetrator is undocumented, Muslim or Black.  All victims of gun violence deserve the same love and attention, regardless of who killed them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;These crimes won&amp;#39;t be happening if I&amp;#39;m elected POTUS. Killer should have never been here. &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/AmericaFirst?src=hash&quot;&gt;#AmericaFirst&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/XDGKaj0ico&quot;&gt;https://t.co/XDGKaj0ico&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Donald J. Trump (@realDonaldTrump) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/748920081942327296&quot;&gt;July 1, 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/donald-trump4.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Idiot&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;This Idiot thinks foreign policy is like running a Miss Universe pageant.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;On The Economy&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Idiot is wrong on the Economy.  How can someone filthy rich &lt;span&gt;&quot;I'm Really Rich!&quot;&lt;/span&gt; understand the plight of the common man?  Giving the rich huge tax breaks won't trickle down the economy.  This Idiot has taken advantage of every rule and loophole to maximize his profit without any regard for anyone but himself, &lt;span&gt;&quot;It's none of your business, you'll see it when I release. But I fight very hard to pay as little tax as possible.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  It's no wonder he refuses to release his taxes.  Take it from someone who's filed Bankruptcy four times &lt;span&gt;&quot;I have never gone bankrupt, by the way&quot;&lt;/span&gt;, all while stifling contractors and taking the money for himself.  This is from someone who hires foreign workers almost exclusively, the same ones he bashes on a regular basis, while thinking it's easy to get jobs back here &lt;span&gt;&quot;We're going to bring businesses back. We're going to have businesses that are now in Mexico come back to New Hampshire and you can tell them to go f*** themselves.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  That's not the economy working for all, that's the economy working for him.  We need someone who understands how to get money for the middle class, not someone who thinks wages are too high &lt;span&gt;&quot;But, taxes too high, wages too high, we're not going to be able to compete against the world. I hate to say it, but we have to leave it the way it is. People have to go out, they have to work really hard and have to get into that upper stratosphere.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  They're not!  And we certainly need someone who will get us out of debt, not someone who loves debt &lt;span&gt;&quot;I'm the king of debt. I love debt,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; or thinks printing more money is a good idea &lt;span&gt;&quot;You never have to default because you print the money.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/Don_Vito_08&quot;&gt;@Don_Vito_08&lt;/a&gt;: &amp;quot;A picture is worth a thousand words&amp;quot; &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump&quot;&gt;@realDonaldTrump&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/LyingTed?src=hash&quot;&gt;#LyingTed&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/NeverCruz?src=hash&quot;&gt;#NeverCruz&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/MELANIATRUMP&quot;&gt;@MELANIATRUMP&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/5bvVEwMVF8&quot;&gt;pic.twitter.com/5bvVEwMVF8&lt;/a&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Donald J. Trump (@realDonaldTrump) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/712850174838771712&quot;&gt;March 24, 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;On Women&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Idiot is flat out wrong on Women.  He calls them names, objectifies them solely on their looks &lt;span&gt;&quot;Look at that face! Would anyone vote for that? Can you imagine that, the face of our next president?,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; proclaims they're playing the 'woman card' to win &lt;span&gt;&quot;The only card she (Hillary Clinton) has to play is the woman's card,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; and makes vulgar jokes about menstruation &lt;span&gt;&quot;You could see there was blood coming out of her eyes. Blood coming out of her wherever,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; and rape &lt;span&gt;&quot;...she got schlonged, she lost, I mean she lost.&quot;&lt;/span&gt; The Idiot thinks women should be punished for abortions, &lt;span&gt;&quot;There has to be some form of punishment.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  When it comes to equal pay, the Idiot claims woman need to work harder to get the same salary as a man when they already do, &lt;span&gt;&quot;You're gonna make the same if you do as good a job.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  The Idiot even selected extreme Anti-Abortionist Mike Pence as his running mate.  Shouldn't expect anything less from a womanizing unfaithful husband who would date his own daughter if he could, &lt;span&gt;&quot;If Ivanka weren't my daughter, perhaps I'd be dating her&quot;&lt;/span&gt; and raped his first wife.  Women are people too, not objects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/donald-trump7.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Idiot&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;This Idiot hates Women.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;On Healthcare&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Idiot is flat out wrong on healthcare.  He has no actual ideas to fix Obamacare, other than to claim that he will &lt;span&gt;&quot;Replace with something terrific.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  That's code for nothing.  Republican's have had years to try to improve Obamacare but have done nothing but want to get rid of it and go back to the way things were.  Get some ideas or don't say anything at all. By the way, the website works, &lt;span&gt;&quot;The $5 billion website for Obamacare - never worked. Still doesn't work.&quot;&lt;/span&gt; It really works.  And vaccines don't cause Autism &lt;span&gt;&quot;We had so many instances [in which] a child had a vaccine, and came back and a week back had a tremendous fever, got very very sick, and now is autistic.&quot;&lt;/span&gt; Anyone who believes that is an idiot, as this has been disproven for years now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;An: Media fell all over themselves criticizing what DonaldTrump &amp;quot;may have insinuated about &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/POTUS&quot;&gt;@POTUS&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;quot; But he&amp;#39;s right: &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/bIIdYtvZYw&quot;&gt;https://t.co/bIIdYtvZYw&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Donald J. Trump (@realDonaldTrump) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/743075154507489280&quot;&gt;June 15, 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;The Idiot claims proof Obama supports ISIS, but this is obviously not true.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;On President Obama&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Idiot is flat out wrong on Obama.  President Obama was born in Hawaii, not Kenya &lt;span&gt;&quot;His grandmother in Kenya said he was born in Kenya and she was there and witnessed the birth, okay?&quot;&lt;/span&gt; and he's a Christian, not Muslim &lt;span&gt;&quot;I wonder if President Obama would have attended the funeral of Justice Scalia if it were held in a Mosque? Very sad that he did not go!&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  This was proven years ago, yet the Idiot still thinks he's a Kenyan-born Muslim and refuses to correct anyone with the truth, even blaming Hillary for the the Birther movement which he is the king of &lt;span&gt;&quot;Just remember, the birther movement was started by Hillary Clinton in 2008. She was all in!&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  The Idiot claims Obama supports terrorism &lt;span&gt;&quot;President Obama claims to know our enemy, and yet he continues to prioritize our enemy over our allies, and for that matter, the American people,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; and has divided America based on color &lt;span&gt;&quot;The irresponsible rhetoric of our President, who has used the pulpit of the presidency to divide us by race and color, has made America a more dangerous environment for everyone.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;   The Idiot claims Obama is the worst President ever &lt;span&gt;&quot;'In politics, and in life, ignorance is not a virtue.' This is a primary reason that President Obama is the worst president in U.S. history!&quot;&lt;/span&gt; None of this is true.  Obama gave the order to kill Osama bin Laden, speaks greatly about people of all races and color and got us out of the Recession.  The Idiot, like every extreme Republican, refuses to believe One Word the President has ever said and will say anything against him (Not one Republican criticized George W. Bush for not stating those three little words but yet it's only an issue with Obama as President).  End of Story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/trump2.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Idiot&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;This Idiot sounds like a spokesperson for Greenhouse-Gas emitting companies&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;On Climate Change&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Idiot is flat out wrong on Climate Change.  No, Global Warming is not a hoax invented by the Chinese &lt;span&gt;&quot;The concept of global warming was created by and for the Chinese in order to make U.S. manufacturing non-competitive.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  97% of all Scientists agree it's real.  And just because it's snowing one place &lt;span&gt;&quot;Snowing in Texas and Louisiana, record setting freezing temperatures throughout the country and beyond. Global warming is an expensive hoax!&quot;&lt;/span&gt; doesn't mean it's snowing on the opposite side of the world.  That's why we have four seasons.  By the way, we haven't heard anything from the Idiot regarding Flint's water problems.  Who really cares about the environment? Not the Idiot wanting support from the very organizations polluting the Earth for profit.  It is a bigger potential concern than Terrorism, it affect everybody, including Terrorists.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/donald-trump6.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Idiot&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;This Idiot expects us to &quot;Believe Me&quot; with numbers.  Ridiculous!&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;On Numbers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Idiot is flat out wrong on Numbers. Pick a number, any number.  If used by Donald Trump, there's a 1000% chance it's not the right number and a complete over exaggeration of the truth.  &lt;span&gt;&quot;Don't believe those phony numbers when you hear 4.9 and 5 percent unemployment. The number's probably 28, 29, as high as 35. In fact, I even heard recently 42 percent.&quot;&lt;/span&gt; The unemployment rate may not show a complete picture, but it's far closer to 5% than 42%.  &lt;span&gt;&quot;I am now hearing it's 30 million, it could be 34 million, which is a much bigger problem.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  Try 11 million undocumented immigrants. &lt;span&gt;&quot;We're the highest taxed nation in the world.&quot;&lt;/span&gt; Not even close. &lt;span&gt;&quot;If you look at what's going on in this country, African-American youth is an example: 59 percent unemployment rate; 59 percent.&quot;&lt;/span&gt; Try 19 percent. &lt;span&gt;&quot;We have 93 million people out of work. They look for jobs, they give up, and all of a sudden, statistically, they're considered employed.&quot;&lt;/span&gt; Closer to 21 million, and no, they're not considered employed. Not even close. &lt;span&gt;&quot;He's gonna tax you people at 90 percent.&quot;&lt;/span&gt; Bernie Sanders wouldn't do that.  When the Idiot mentions a number, do yourself a favor, don't believe it, you can't believe a word he says.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/donald-trump2.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Idiot&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;This Idiot thinks Russia is a better country than the United States.  WRONG!&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;On Leadership Qualties&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Idiot is flat out wrong on Leadership qualities.  Being a great leader is willing to work others.  The Idiot on the other hand thinks dictators like Vladimir Putin &lt;span&gt;&quot;I will tell you in terms of leadership he is getting an 'A,' and our president is not doing so well,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; and Kim Jong Un &lt;span&gt;&quot;It's incredible. He wiped out the uncle, he wiped out this one, that one. I mean this guy doesn't play games. And we can't play games with him,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; are great leaders.  He calls Obama weak and criticizes his allies &lt;span&gt;&quot;He's (Vladimir Putin) making mincemeat out of our president,&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  while praising Saddam Hussein for killing terrorists &lt;span&gt;&quot;He was a bad guy -- really bad guy. But you know what? He did well? He killed terrorists. He did that so good. They didn't read them the rights. They didn't talk. They were terrorists. Over.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;.  Too bad Saddam Hussein was a well-known sponsor of terrorism and protected groups that aligned with him.  These are not great leadership qualities.  Leaders have empathy for others, while the Idiot hasn't shown empathy for anyone but himself.  That type of leadership is more for dictators.  A foreshadowing of what life would be if this Idiot was elected President.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/donald-trump-mocks-disabled-reporter.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Idiot&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;This is what The Idiot looks like when he makes fun of someone's disability&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;On Character&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Idiot is flat out wrong on Character.  This Idiot has no redeeming characteristics.  Instead, this Idiot acts like a five year old when arguing with others &lt;span&gt;&quot;He started it. I didn't start it.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;, makes up stupid childish nicknames &lt;span&gt;&quot;Lyin' Ted Cruz denied that he had anything to do with the G.Q. model photo post of Melania. That's why we call him Lyin' Ted!&quot;&lt;/span&gt; makes childish threats out of spite &lt;span&gt;&quot;The wall just got 10 feet taller, believe me,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; makes jokes about his genitalia &lt;span&gt;&quot;And, he (Marco Rubio) referred to my hands if they're small, something else is small,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; claims to have seen videos that don't exist &lt;span&gt;&quot;And I watched in Jersey City, N.J., where thousands and thousands of people were cheering as that building was coming down. Thousands of people were cheering,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; repeats ridiculously false conspiracy theories &lt;span&gt;&quot;His (Ted Cruz's) father was with Lee Harvey Oswald prior to Oswald being, you know, shot. I mean the whole thing is ridiculous. What is this, right, prior to his being shot? And nobody even brings it up,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; mocks POW's &lt;span&gt;&quot;He's (John McCain) not a war hero -- he's a war hero because he was captured. I like people that weren't captured.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;, stereotypes people based solely on their name &lt;span&gt;&quot;Take a look. I mean, you look at the names, you look at what's happened. You tell me,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; makes fun of someone's disability &lt;span&gt;&quot;Now, the poor guy, you've got to see this guy: 'Uhh, I don't know what I said. Uhh, I don't remember,' he's going like 'I don't remember. Maybe that's what I said'&quot;&lt;/span&gt; promotes violence at his rallies &lt;span&gt;&quot;Knock the crap out of them, would you? Seriously. OK? Just knock the hell -- I promise you, I will pay for the legal fees. I promise, I promise,&quot;&lt;/span&gt;, threatens violence at other people's rallies &lt;span&gt;&quot;Bernie Sanders is lying when he says his disruptors aren't told to go to my events. Be careful Bernie, or my supporters will go to yours!&quot;&lt;/span&gt;, claims he wouldn't lose supporters if he shot someone &lt;span&gt;&quot;I could stand in the middle of 5th Avenue and shoot somebody, and I wouldn't lose voters,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; claims an American born judge is out to get him solely on his ethnicity &lt;span&gt;&quot;I have a judge who is a hater of Donald Trump, a hater. He's a hater, we believe, Mexican, which is great.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;, verbally attacks a Muslim woman in grief of losing her son in the Iraq War for not speaking &lt;span&gt;&quot;If you look at his wife, she was standing there. She had nothing to say. She probably, maybe she wasn't allowed to have anything to say. You tell me,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; diminishes the value of a life lost in war &lt;span&gt;&quot;I've made a lot of sacrifices. I work very, very hard. I've created thousands and thousands of jobs, tens of thousands of jobs, built great structures,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; all while claiming to be the victim every time someone says something negative about him &lt;span&gt;&quot;I was viciously attacked by Mr. Khan at the Democratic Convention. Am I not allowed to respond? Hillary voted for the Iraq war, not me!&quot;&lt;/span&gt; This Idiot has no redeeming qualities on character and can't take the slightest criticism without scorching the Earth every time someone goes after him.  The First Amendment is for all Americans, not just for The Idiot and his followers.  No person would ever act this way to others, let alone a President to his country.  This Idiot will believe anything that's on the Internet &lt;span&gt;&quot;I don't know, all I know is what's on the internet,&quot;&lt;/span&gt;, even if it's clearly not true...&lt;span&gt;&quot;USSS did an excellent job stopping the maniac running to the stage. He has ties to ISIS. Should be in jail!  &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/tkzbHg7wyD&quot;&gt;https://t.co/tkzbHg7wyD&lt;/a&gt;?ssr=true&quot;&lt;/span&gt; unless it's about him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/donald-trump3.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Idiot&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;This Idiot hates America, he'd be glad to take everything from us just to enrich himself.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;On America&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Idiot is flat out wrong on America.  We're not on fire, crime isn't rising, refugees aren't coming in to attack us, immigrants aren't taking all of our jobs, and not everything is Obama and Hillary Clinton's fault, despite the Idiot's claim that &lt;span&gt;&quot;It's(The Obama Administration) failed them at every level.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  This Idiot made a rambling speech at the RNC about how bad things are, how he alone can fix everything as fast as snapping your fingers, &lt;span&gt;&quot;Nobody knows the system better than me, which is why I alone can fix it,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; all while accusing Democrats of destroying the very fabric of this nation.  Last time I checked, the Economy is better than it was in 2008, people have more rights, more access to healthcare and believe it or not, more safe than in 2008.  America is not perfect, but it's not a war zone &lt;span&gt;&quot;There are places in America that are among the most dangerous in the world. You go to places like Oakland. Or Ferguson. The crime numbers are worse. Seriously.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;, and insulting our Armed forces &lt;span&gt;&quot;Our military is a disaster,&quot;&lt;/span&gt;, our Generals &lt;span&gt;He's (General John Allen) a failed general,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; and American citizens &lt;span&gt;&quot;I Love the Poorly Educated,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; is as un-American as you can get.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/donald-trump1.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Idiot&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;This Idiot is UGLY&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;On Honesty&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Idiot is flat out wrong on honesty.  He's a con-artist and a fraud, plain and simple.  He stole millions of dollars from people through his sham of a University while pretending it wasn't true &lt;span&gt;&quot;We (Trump University) have an 'A' from the Better Business Bureau,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; told people he'd love for a housing bubble to occur to reap the benefits, &lt;span&gt;&quot;I sort of hope that happens because then people like me would go in and buy,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; and refused to pay contractors for work they did on his crappy Bankrupted buildings.  The Idiot pretends to be an outsider &lt;span&gt;&quot;I'm self-funding my own campaign,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; but his opinions can be bought, &lt;span&gt;&quot;I, on the other hand, received the early and strong endorsement of the National Rifle Association.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  The Idiot even thinks he's attractive despite his ridiculous hair and ugly looking chin, &lt;span&gt;&quot;It is very hard for them to attack me on looks, because I am so good looking.&quot;&lt;/span&gt; He helped the USFL win a landmark $1 from a lawsuit against the NFL, terrorized renters on his properties in the 80s to force them out, and continues to hire employees as cheap as he can to pocket the extra dough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;In Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When it's all said and done, this Idiot is the worst Presidential nominee in the history of the United States.  He is a historically awful, pathetic, stupid, bigoted, racist, tyrannical, misogynist, narcissistic, greedy, selfish, untrustworthy piece of shit.  I'm tired of hearing about him.  I'm tired of his stupid games.  I'm tired of everything about him.  He has completely destroyed the Republican Party as we know it, for better or for worse.  Electing him President will start a World War, crash our Economy into a complete Depression, make all of us extremely unsafe, and worst of all, make America look like a complete f**in' joke.  America is better than this.  I hope you all join me and boycott his name and start calling him The Idiot.  We must do everything we can to make sure he doesn't take over the United States.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/08/08/my-pledge</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/08/08/my-pledge</guid>
        
        
        <category>politics</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>RNC vs. DNC - Two Different Worlds</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; The Republican and Democrat National Conventions have come and gone, officially ending the Primaries.  Seeing bits of each, I can safely say one thing: the two Parties are from two different worlds. One filled with anger and hate, the other filled with love and passion.  So which one better reflects us as a nation?  Here are my thoughts on each convention and my allegiance going forward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/obama-clinton.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Obama and Clinton&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Barack Obama and Hillary Clinton&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The RNC, not surprisingly, was a complete mess, full of hatred and spew.  There were no legitimate complaints about Hillary Clinton and Barack Obama, just lies, lies and more lies.  Clearly, the Republicans are full of anger.  For example, Hillary Clinton does not want to get rid of the Second Amendment, yet this was repeated multiple times.  Many of the speakers criticisms were emotionally charged falsehoods that attack their opponents personally without any evidence to back up their claims.  It's been proven for years that Obama has never been a Muslim yet the Right refuses to accept that he is a Christian, claiming he must be a Muslim because of his worldview being so different from theirs.  No matter how hard they try, it will never be true.  That is called RACISM. And Hillary’s emails? Just another distraction from the real issues facing our country and the Republicans lack of substantial ideas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The main speakers tried to paint Donald Trump in a positive viewpoint; mainly his family, but this is a very limited piece of Donald Trump.  He wants to run this country like his business, not like he treats his family.  His business record speaks for itself.  Bankruptcies, lawsuits, not paying workers and fraud.  And not surprisingly, his family doesn't see this or chooses not to accept this. Melania Trump’s speech was a ripoff of Michelle Obama’s speech at the 2008 DNC; clearly not that smart.  Republicans like Newt Gingrich claim it's not a big deal she plagiarized someone else's speech, but surely he'd cry foul if Hillary Clinton did the same thing. Duh!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/christie.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Chris Christie&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Chris Christie: Guilty or not guilty of hugging Hillary Clinton?  GUILTY!&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some low points include Chris Christie's mock trial for Hillary Clinton.  Chances are, they wouldn't complain about Colin Powell and Condoleezza Rice doing the exact same thing as Hillary Clinton did with her stupid emails.  It was stupid, not criminal, but Republican's merely WANTED her to be indicted.  They don't care about the truth.  Coming from an opportunistic ass wipe who rightfully complained about Donald Trump, then starting kissing his feet the moment he dropped out of the Presidential race.  Another low point was Ted Cruz refusing to endorse Donald Trump, leading to boos and anger from a divided crowd.  I don't blame Cruz (for once), after all, Trump made trash TV comments about his family.  It says a lot about the Republicans in general.  With that said, I passionately hate Ted Cruz and will love to see the end of his Political career, hopefully sooner than later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Which leads us to Donald Trump himself.  After his speech, it's hard to believe he even likes America.  I certainly felt like I wasted my time listening to his ridiculous angry dribble.  He spent his time criticizing everything about us, believing the world is on fire, life is in shambles, and everything is on the verge of collapse.  Not surprisingly, the only thing Donald Trump talked good about was wait for it...HIMSELF.  He believes he's the only one who can fix things, pumps himself up as a Messiah, all while blaming everything on the Democrats.  But Trump has no ideas on how to fix anything.  No plan to defeat ISIS, no plan to help the Economy, Nothing.  His campaign is a joke full of catchphrases, extreme hyperboles, empty promises worth less than a degree from Trump University, hateful rhetoric towards everyone not like him, and all for personal gain. Trump’s vision of this country is blatantly false, dreary and downright scary, and he can't be trusted to fix anything, let alone fix things ‘quickly’.  I certainly don't leave my house everyday wondering if a Terrorist is going to attack me.  I don't have any reason to believe everything wrong with my life is due to Foreigners.  I certainly don't believe a man so secretive can be trusted with doing the dishes, let alone lead our country.  All the nice things said about him really can't be proven, because his public persona is that of an egotistical misogynistic asshole.  I didn't watch the RNC live, I was up thankfully out of town.  I did not miss a thing.  A few stupid clips I saw were downright pathetic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/clinton-kaine.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Hillary Clinton and Tim Kaine&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Hillary Clinton and Tim Kaine: Real Leaders&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The DNC was not surprisingly, more kind and accepting towards all people.  They showed appreciation for both the Police and African Americans.  The RNC only likes the Police, vilifying African Americans, particularly Black Lives Matter, as the problem; mere Police Killers. NOT TRUE! Their complaints about Donald Trump were based primarily on his own words, not made up rhetoric based on fiction and selfish desires.  Nope, speaker after speaker referred to Trump's words to critique his plans based on his own words.  After all, he said what he meant, and he meant what he said.  Trump owns his words and ridiculous rhetoric.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The main speakers were ALL supportive of Hillary and described her compassion to fight for progress.  Michelle Obama gracefully attacked Trump as bad for children, using her own thoughts while showcasing her passion for the country she loves.  Bernie Sanders declared Hillary as the only candidate to vote for despite their minor disagreements.  Bill Clinton used his folkish charm to describe his passion for Hillary and Obama strongly rebuked Donald Trump’s version of America as bogus.  Attack after attack on Donald Trump’s twisted world of hate and fear.  That’s the way to do it.  We also can't forget Joe Biden’s attack on Trump’s malarkey and Tim Kaine’s fatherly mocking of Donald Trump’s phrase: Believe Me.  Believe Trump? Not even in Bizarro World.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The DNC covered all factions of potential voters, even the Anti-Trump Republican's who know he’s plagued their Party for years to come.  Speakers like Independent Michael Bloomberg and Retired General John Hutson proclaimed that while Hillary isn't perfect (no one is perfect), she’s the only one remotely qualified for the job.  They reached out to Bernie Sanders biggest fans time and time again, and gave everyone an equal opportunity to represent their views.  None of that at the RNC.  It was all the same viewpoint they shared of doom and gloom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/crying-baby.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Crying Baby&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;I would cry too, poor kid.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love America, and I'm a proud American. That's why Hillary Clinton’s speech was the obviously better of the two.  It doesn't matter what anyone thinks of her.  She loves this country and will fight to make things better.  I can't say the same about Donald Trump.  He hates this country and thinks everyone a part of it is weak, stupid or detrimental to our society.  He puts himself above all, while Hillary will keep fighting for others.  This is why Republicans hate her so much; her fiery passion is detrimental to their way and her relentlessness is unmatched.  Truth be told, she has more balls than most men, especially easily offended Donald Trump.  No dwelling, just passion to do things the right way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Congressional gridlock is our biggest problem right now, and only one candidate even sees it as a problem to fix: Hillary Clinton.  Donald Trump thinks he can spit in all of Congress’s faces and do whatever he wants.  That's how he has lived his entire life.  Hillary Clinton is willing to work together to get things done.  Working with allies is a solution.  Donald Trump sees this as a problem, alienating everyone of our allies while praising dictators around the world as good leaders.  Obviously a crystal ball into Donald Trump’s leadership skills.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump is only right about one thing: We need change.  But we need good change, not bad change.  Good changes defeat terrorists with our allies, strengthens the economy bottom-up and prospers as one.  Trump’s change leads to economic crises, constant attacks from Terrorists using his own words as encouragement and a deeply divided country from which only he benefits from.  Donald Trump is a historically horrific candidate; anyone who actually believes one word out of his mouth is downright stupid.  That’s why the Election is that important and clear who must lead our country to survive. That's why I'm voting Hillary Rodham Clinton for President.  Thank you and good night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/07/31/rnc-vs-dnc</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/07/31/rnc-vs-dnc</guid>
        
        
        <category>politics</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Donald Trump, Vice President of Russia?</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Last week, just before the Democratic National Convention started, hackers released emails from the DNC pertaining to their head’s plans to push candidate Bernie Sanders out of the race.  The hacks were deemed by U.S. officials as likely the work of the Russians, perhaps in an attempt to sway the election towards Republican Donald Trump.  Now, Donald Trump himself has asked Russia to hack into Hillary Clinton’s emails and release them.  Clearly, Donald Trump prefers Russia over Democrats in the United States.  A man who has repeatedly praised Russia President Vladimir Putin as a great leader and capable of ‘getting stuff done,’ one question remains.  Is Donald Trump working to become President of the United States or the Vice President of Russia?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/donald-trump-vladimir-putin-kiss.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Donald Trump Vladimir Putin Kiss&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;An Iconic painting of Vladimir Putin and Donald Trump kissing in Lithuania.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Throughout history, Russia, the Soviet Union, whatever they have been called, have been our rivals.  From World War II to the Cold War, relations between us and the Soviet Russians have been frosty at best.  Even after the fall of Communism in the Soviet Union, Russia plays by its own rules and wants world power.  To have American pride, you must be proud of America and all of it, and not say great things about our so-called geo-political foes.  Donald Trump has repeatedly violated this by praising their President while saying nothing but awful things about our President.  If Donald Trump truly hates Obama, he needs to move to Russia where he can shower praise for their President.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Vladimir Putin is a bully and a tyrant, a man incapable of caring about anyone else and will use anyone that likes him as his play toy.  He is one of the few leaders in the world with less of a soul than Donald Trump.  So it’s not surprising that Donald Trump is kissing his ass.  Trump only cares about power, like Putin does.  It’s no surprise Putin would prefer him over Hillary Clinton.  While Clinton has and will stand up to Putin’s tyrannical ways, Trump will be taken along for a ride until the United States is sold to the Russians.  Trump would probably make billions.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;The fact that Trump would ask the Russians to help him is a clear sign that he’s working with the Russians, whether directly or indirectly, to win the Presidency here, but he’s too naive and stupid to realize that Russia wants us trampled, perhaps the better term would be ‘trumpled.’  Russia has been accused of killing rivals, trampling on human rights and other criminal activities, and while Trump believes every denial from Putin’s mouth, clearly they have similarities, as Trump defrauds, lies and hides everything there is to know about him.  Perhaps Donald Trump’s tax returns would show his true appreciation for Russia and his partnership he wishes to have with them.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;We need a President who puts America First.  Donald Trump claims he’s the only one who puts America first, but his actions have made it clear he’s putting Russia First.  He complains about Hillary and her emails but essentially praises the Russians for breaking the law and encourages them to break the law.  We need someone that will protect us and stand up for us, not a criminal.  This is not the man we need as President of the United States.  If Trump wants to be the Vice President of Russia, please vote Hillary Clinton for President and force him to move there.  He doesn’t belong here!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/07/27/donald-trump-vice-president-of-russia</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/07/27/donald-trump-vice-president-of-russia</guid>
        
        
        <category>politics</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pokemon Whoa!</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
li {
    font-size: 14px;
    font-family: &quot;Raleway&quot;, sans-serif;
    text-indent: 2em;
}
&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/no-pokemon.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;No Pokemon&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Do the right thing...say No to Pokemon Go&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt; For the past two weeks, I've heard the most bizarre stories, all relating to the new super-viral video game that has seemingly taken over the world, Pokemon Go.  Pokemon first hit the scene 20 years ago, but this game allows people to try to 'catch-em all' based on real-world locations, getting people out and about just to catch Pokemon on their game.  It's led to some bizarre stories; people catching criminals, getting stabbed by others, finding dead bodies, guns, etc., getting in car accidents, taking up police parking, fire parking, and other bizarre warnings all over Pokemon Go.  I played the original Pokemon games when I was a teenager, but now we're seeing adults playing the game; it's pure madness, all these ridiculous real-life events happening based solely on this game.  Imagine what else this game can lead to.  Here's a list of five things I wish this game could find.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-6&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/db-cooper.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;D.B. Cooper&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Who's D.B. Cooper?  Maybe Pokemon can find him.&lt;/h4&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-6&quot;&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;D.B. Cooper: The FBI just a few days ago officially stopped investigating the infamous D.B. Cooper case, a man who in 1971 hijacked a plane flying from Portland to Seattle, jumping out of the plane with $200,000 ransom.  No one has ever found him or any evidence he even survived the jump, but in 1980, an eight-year old boy found some of the ransom money washed up somewhere in southwest Washington near the town of Amboy.  Wouldn't it only be perfect for someone playing the game nearby to find additional money hidden in the ground, or perhaps, a body for the legendary D.B. Cooper.  Maybe some other additional evidence. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-6&quot;&gt;
	&lt;li&gt; Missing children: Children are our future, and anyone who would want to hurt, kidnap or kill a child is scum.  Maybe some lucky Pokemon Go player searching for that rare Pokemon can find a missing child, whether dead or alive, at least to bring closure for their loved ones.  One particular child I want found is Kyron Horman, who disappeared June 4, 2010 after being 'picked up' from school for an alleged doctor's appointment by that 'step-mother,' whose name isn't worth repeating.  Wouldn't that be the dream.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-6&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/kyron.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Kyron Horman&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Missing children like Kyron Horman need to be found.&lt;/h4&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-6&quot;&gt; 
	&lt;li&gt;O.J. Simpson's Murder gloves: In 1994, the nation was shocked when O.J. Simpson's wife, Nicole Brown Simpson was murdered, allegedly by O.J. Simpson himself.  From the infamous White Bronco car chase down I-405 in Los Angeles to the Trial of the Century that found him Not Guilty, people all around have wondered if O.J. Simpson was guilty or not.  One of the key points of that trial was his gloves.  If only some random Pokemon Go player could find the gloves he wore when he probably killed Nicole Brown Simpson and friend Ron Goldman while looking for that rare Pokemon.  To this day, it's still the most likely scenario, as no alternate scenario has come forth, it's likely that O.J. was guilty all along.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-6&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/oj-glove.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;O.J. Simpson&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Of course the glove didn't fit.&lt;/h4&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-6&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/grants-pass.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Grants Pass&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;I got rich in Grants Pass...just kidding.  It was only $40.00&lt;/h4&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-6&quot;&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Dropped Dolla Bill Y'all: If someone dropped some cash and no one was around, would you take it?  I'm not talking about thousands of dollars, more like $40.  That was the dilemma I faced when I visited Grants Pass, stopping for a picture of their Welcome sign.  I just happened to notice some loose twenties laying in the street.  Sure, if I saw someone actually drop it, that's different, but no one would identify the money as theirs, and if not me, someone else would.  So, I picked it up and went on with my day and my trip.  If only Pokemon Go could locate dropped dollar bills in the name of Pokemon, that would be sweet.  For the record, I don't condone stealing money.  Please don't.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-6&quot;&gt;
		&lt;li&gt;A secret meeting where Donald Trump discusses his REAL thoughts: Trump lies about everything.  Moral integrity is a foreign word to him.  No one knows what he's actually thinking or what he'd actually do to the United States if elected President (my guess involves his favorite number, 11).  Wouldn't it be great for some Pokemon Go player looking for a Pokemon to stumble upon a secret meeting he's having admitting to his people what a crock of shit he really is.  One thing's for sure, Pokemon Go won't find any proof of Hillary Clinton's alleged Benghazi lies; they don't exist...&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-6&quot;&gt;
		&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
			&lt;img src=&quot;/img/mike-pence-donald-trump.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Donald Trump and Mike Pence&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
			&lt;h4&gt;I don't know what's more disturbing, the fact that anyone would actually want to be Donald Trump's Vice Presidential candidate, as Mike Pence agreed to, or Donald Trump's chin.  What's wrong with that thing?&lt;/h4&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/entertainment/2016/07/14/pokemon-whoa</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/entertainment/2016/07/14/pokemon-whoa</guid>
        
        
        <category>entertainment</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Saison Love</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; When I was young, I only saw beer in black and white.  Obviously, I didn't drink beer, but my Mom occasionally drank beer, mainly when we went to the Oak Hills Brewpub, where she ordered the dark beers, the Porters and Stouts.  From then, I considered good beers to be dark, while crap beers like Bud, Miller and Coors as the bad beers.  It wasn't until I was 26 that I decided to try beer for the first time, as McMenamins on Allen and Murray. I had a sampler of dark and light beers, mainly interested in the Black Rabbit Porter and Terminator Stout.  From then on, I found myself trying all styles of beers, dark and light, where I learned there's more than just BMC crap (Bud-Miller-Coors for the uninformed).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/colette.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Colette.&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Colette, from Great Divide Brewing Company, who recently released Nadia Kali, a Hibiscus Saison I enjoyed quite a bit.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My mom though, was a tough cookie to crack to see the other side of beers.  She loved her Porters and Stouts, and with me drinking beer, we took the opportunity to have more beer.  But on a hot summer day on July 15, 2012 at the Raccoon Lodge, my Mom asked me what type of beer I had ordered and asked if she could taste it.  Naturally, I let her sample me beer of choice that night, the Saison Fume, and she was intrigued by it.  The seeds were set, and going out to Hood River for my birthday, we went to pFriem, a Belgian-style brewery along the waterfront. We sampled six beers, which I picked for myself, but my Mom found herself really loving two of the beers I picked.  They were both Saisons, a Black Saison and Lemon Saison.  Suddenly, I found a way to break through that black and white beer bubble.  Ever since, she's been fascinated with Saisons, perfect for the summertime.  So here are my thoughts on Saisons and why they are the perfect craft beer for all people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first Saison I tried was Great Divide Brewing Company's Collette, which stands out as one of the best readily available Saisons in these parts of the United States.  I immediately took a liking to it and was impressed with its light yet fruity/earthy/spiced tones to it.  To me, that's what makes a Saison an easy drinking craft beer.  On the one hand, you have the overly hoppy IPA's, which plenty of American's love, but they are admittedly not an easy style of beer to get into right away.  It took me a while to appreciate the hops.  On the other side of light beers is the bready floral Pilsner beers which the crappy BMC beers resemble lightly.  Saisons, a Belgian summer beer, doesn't quite have the hops (since Belgians don't like their beers hoppy) but also have a more robust flavor (not like Pilsners at all).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/tank-7.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Tank 7 Farmhouse Ale&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;I vote Tank 7 as the best Saison I've had.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another great Saison I would highly recommend, one that's also year-round in these parts, is Boulevard Brewing's Tank 7 Farmhouse Ale.  Of course, Farmhouse Ale is another term for Saison, so please keep that in mind.  In terms of Saison's for the masses across America, there aren't that many, mostly made by breweries during the spring-summer months.  It's unfortunate there aren't more readily available Saison's but with Collette and Tank 7, those to me are enough to get me by.  I do have to admit I have never tried a real Belgian Saison made in Belgium.  I know there is the Saison Dupont that's considered the best.  I may have to seek that one out since I got my mom on the Saison-train.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Living in Oregon, the hop capital of the United States, it isn't that surprising that Saisons get overlooked, again, only appearing as spring-summer seasonals for those who don't always stick to the script.  But there are specialty breweries that focus on specialty beer types, like Cascade Brewing's focus on the Sour Beer market.  Luckily, for Saison fans, there's Logsdon Farmhouse Ales in Hood River, which as the name suggests, offers plenty of Saisons and other Belgian beers.  I've only had one of their beers, the Seizoen Bretta, they are on the more expensive side and come in wine-bottle size, but I can assure you that Seizoen Bretta was quite delicious and worth the money.  I bought it as an anniversary beer, but for the life of me, can't remember what anniversary it was.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/seizoen-bretta.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Seizoen Bretta&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Seizoen Bretta, a Brett-alicious Saison&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a final note, I'd like to share what I consider to be the most interesting part of Saisons, Brett.  No, it has nothing to do with my Uncle, but Saisons with Brett are considered to be especially enjoyable and intriguing.  Who exactly is Brett?  It's short for Brettanomyces, a special kind of yeast that's found in Belgian beers that gives it a particularly earthy taste.  During my young research on Saisons, I always heard about Brett; which is why I sought out the Seizoen Bretta from Logsdon in the first place.  I hope anyone that likes Saisons or are just curious to seek about the Brett Saisons, or any Saison in general.  A perfect summer beer for those who like to be different, Saisons are often overshadowed by the hoppy IPAs and easily accessible Pilsners, but make a great choice for those looking for an easy to drink beer with complex fruity, earthy and spicy flavors. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/beer/2016/07/11/a-saison-love</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/beer/2016/07/11/a-saison-love</guid>
        
        
        <category>beer</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Enough is Enough</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Enough is enough.  For so long, our country has turned a blind eye on racism, proclaiming that it's not a big deal like it used to be, just because of Civil Rights and the elimination of Jim Crow laws.  But recent events, particularly the deaths of Alton Sterling in Baton Rouge, Philando Castile in Falcon Heights, Minnesota and the deaths of five police officers in Dallas have shown just how horrific racism in the United States really is.  Is there a coincidence that this is happening now at this current time?  Of course not.  This is a by-product of the anger and race baiting politics that Donald Trump has shoved down America's throats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/ferguson-free-hug.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Hugs for everyone&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;This is what America's all about...Coming together.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Listen to Donald Trump speak.  Read between the lines with his stupid tweets.  Whatever the case be, Donald Trump is ANGRY.  He claims he wants to make America great again, but all he does is pit people against one another.  This type of hate-filled angst causes people to be angry and lack the ability to control their emotions.  A level-headed person is far more likely to make rational decisions than angry people whose emotions take control.  We don't need to hear the thoughts of the angry few.  Most people aren't like that.  And those who are angry with violent tendencies are often the ones who want to cause physical and mental harm to us.  This has been brewing for years with the racist minority openly complaining about Obama and his worldview.  The racists blame Obama for everything wrong, yet it's them who are making things worse.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;This happened in Baton Rouge, where Alton Sterling was shot dead by police multiple times while he was pinned to the ground by two officers.  A man who didn't deserve to die, yet too many times in these instances, regardless of race, the Officers always try to pin the victim as a 'criminal' for past convictions.  Doesn't matter.  Regardless of whether there was an altercation or not, it's not reasonable to shoot a man in the chest at point blank range if you have him pinned to the ground.  Clearly, hate for another leads to mistrust and violence.  The Police often blame those they kill as bad guys while the victims and their loved ones proclaim the Police and others as being overly aggressive due to their appearance.  Police hide behind their badge to justify their actions, rarely, if ever facing conviction for killing innocent people.  Black people often feel targeted for their skin color and sometimes act irrationally due to false accusations.  This hate needs will never stop while others on the sidelines encourage others to act by making these things solely a race issue.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Too often people look solely at people's skin color and make judgments about them.  Some of it is blatant, while some of it is subconscious.  Some people may not realize it, but they are too focused on appearances when judging people.  This was clearly shown in the death of Philando Castile, who was pulled over in Falcon Heights, Minnesota for a 'broken tail-light.'  According to his girlfriend, who was seating next to him in the car, the Officer asked for license and registration (which is standard anytime someone gets pulled over, I know from personal experience), but then told him not to move the moment Philando mentioned having a gun.  No one who would want to shoot an Officer would openly tell them they're armed, but something must have clicked in the Officer's head, as suddenly he judged Philando Castile as 'a black man with a gun, he must be a gangster that wants to kill me,' rather than a complex human being who, contrary to those negative stereotypes, never had any trouble with the law.  This Officer had hate filled in his heart for whatever reason, and it led him to shoot Philando four times dead, while his girlfriend watched and cried in horror and recorded the aftermath.  No one deserves to die, especially over a 'broken tail-light.'  Even worse, the Officer and his backup showed no compassion for him or his girlfriend and 4 year old daughter in the car.  Instead, they watched him die, holding the gun pointed at him and arrested her.  Watching this video, it saddens me and only further supports my point.  The Officer was screaming, while the woman was shockingly calm yet upset.  That's not rational, that's anger for no reason.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Yet instead of trying to heal the wounds, others loudly complain about the 'other side' playing the blame game.  These people will try to blame everyone else except the person who actually committed the crime.  They'll make them look like victims of the Government's views on society.  This is not a fantasy world, and only encourages more anger from those who feel like they're being targeted.  This is exactly what happened in Dallas, where Micah Xavier Johnson, a 25 year old African American and former Army reservist, angry with police officers for killing Alton and Philando (among others), set out to kill as many White police officers as he could.  Perhaps if someone had calmed him down and reminded him that most people were upset like he was and violence wasn't the answer, this may not have happened.  Instead, we had plenty of voices who have and continue to blame Blacks for their own deaths.  They get what they deserve.  They're only interested in killing cops.  These are the voices of the racist extremists that overshadow the compassionate majority.  To him, his actions were justified by the minority, which led him to murdering cops in anger.  None of this is okay for most, yet the hate filled few openly play race wars and hate games.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Joe Walsh decided to delete this tweet. So let&amp;#39;s all retweet it. &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/BY03pLmTyp&quot;&gt;pic.twitter.com/BY03pLmTyp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Matthew Rosenberg (@AllMattNYT) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/AllMattNYT/status/751281426784329728&quot;&gt;July 8, 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;As I read about the deaths in Dallas, it disgusts me that some blame the African American's and even Obama himself for all of this mess.  It's downright racist to believe that somehow because Obama is black, that he somehow supports a black man killing multiple police officers.  Obama referred to the shooting as a “vicious, calculated, despicable attack.”  Yet racist people like former congressman Joe Walsh, congressman Steve King, and media joke Sarah Palin don't even bother to listen to a single word he says.  I doubt any of these racist extremists believe anything Obama says is true.  They are part of the problem, not the solution.  This is not the time to declare 'war' against Obama and Black Lives Matter as former Illinois congressman Joe Walsh tweeted in the aftermath.   Nor is it the time to claim the Obama's own words have led to blacks only interested in killing cops, as racist Iowa congressman and Number 1 Hispanic Hater Steve King proclaimed (which isn't even remotely true, some cops do act 'stupidly,' they're human).  And last but not least, Sarah Palin, a clueless joke of a former Governor of Alaska who quit to become a famous media whore, her comments aren't even worth repeating.  After all, she's the type of person that would blame Obama for having a bad hair day.  Spewing more hate speech is not going to solve anything; it's only going to create more of the same type of behavior if not worse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/DallasPoliceShooting?src=hash&quot;&gt;#DallasPoliceShooting&lt;/a&gt; has roots in first of anti-white/cop events illuminated by Obama...Officer Crowley. There were others.&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Steve King (@SteveKingIA) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/SteveKingIA/status/751490647799005184&quot;&gt;July 8, 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;This is not the time to say hurtful things that target African-Americans.  Nor is this the time to do the same against Police Officers.  Most African-Americans and Police Officers are good people.  In fact, saying hurtful things only encourages others to commit violence out of revenge, hate and spite.  It's not their fault any of this happens.  The problem is bigger than that.  So while most of America holds on to each other and comforts themselves, we are left to hear the voices of the extremists, who often complain the most and speak the loudest.  Unfortunately, our society notices negativity more than positivity as it attracts more attention.  Turn on the five o'clock news and dare to tell me that you will find anything positive on the news.  You might be lucky if you do, but most stories are the ones that resonate with viewers; the violence, the deaths, the rapes, the burglaries and the general hate we constantly hear about.  This is clear with those like Joe Walsh, who refuses to apologize for his opinions on Obama and the African American community, because to people like him, we can't blame the cops for anything, therefore, it's all the Blacks fault.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/joe-walsh.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Joe Walsh (the singer)&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;There's no reason to promote hate, so here's singer Joe Walsh instead.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;So why does it seem that this is happening more commonly than it used to in the past?  There are a variety of factors, amongst them: easier access to news via social media, easier access to guns, especially with assault weapons no longer banned like they used to be, and more extremist behavior leading to a widespread feeling of anger.  This is abundantly clear with Donald Trump, whose words are frequently blasted over the web within seconds.  A man who hardly says anything positive, most people see the hate-filled spew coming out of his mouth, and it makes everyone angry and filled with hate.  His supporters are angry over minorities they believe are the problem with America.  His detractors are angry for targeting minorities and blaming them for everything.  This is not the voice of the American majority, yet this is all we hear about, leading people to have a narrow impression of America.  It's only the few hate-filled people with violent tendencies that end up causing physical and mental anguish, a task done easier with easy access with guns.  This is not what America is really like, we need to focus on the voices who want to heal, not the few who want to 'go to war.'  &lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;America is better than this.  We're all upset by this, as we should be.  But the best solution to heal our wounds is to come together, not tear us apart.  Focus on the love and compassion, not the hate and anger.  I know that not all people are fueled by hate, and most aren't like this.  It's up to the passionate majority to dismiss the viewpoints of the racist minority by speaking up.  This is not the time to deny that anything's wrong, nor to stay silent.  That only allows the Donald Trump's and Joe Walsh's of the world to convince us that they're the truth.  They're not the voice of the America I love and cherish.  These voices must be minimized through rejection of their bigoted ways.  Only then can the healing process begin.  Enough is enough.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/07/08/enough-is-enough</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/07/08/enough-is-enough</guid>
        
        
        <category>politics</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Donald The Racist Ugly Misogynistic Pig</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; In an election where Donald Trump has seemingly offended just about everyone that's not an old white Christian, it was only inevitable that Donald Trump would be accused of Anti-Semitism.  With all the Islamophobia Donald Trump keeps spreading, it's hard to forget that the Jews have historically been hated on by the majority of non-Jews.  Recently, Donald Trump tweeted a picture of Hillary Clinton with money in the background and a Star of David symbol proclaiming  'Most Corrupt Candidate Ever.'  Trump took it down two hours later and replaced it with a circle replacing the Jewish Star.  Does this make Donald Trump Anti-Semitic or just plain stupid.  Here are my thoughts on Trump's history of Anti-Semitism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/frozen.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Frozen&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Offended yet?  You shouldn't be...&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's true that Donald Trump will say or do anything to get attention.  He'd be the first in line to criticize Jews if he felt he would get a voting advantage from it, just like he does to the Hispanics, Muslims, Blacks, Asians, Millennials, Women, Liberals, Disabled, Presidents, Secretary of State's, Governors, Senators, Congressmen and Congresswomen, Supreme Court Justice's, Catholics, Poor, LGBTers, well, just about everyone that's not white or Christian.  In this respect, it's hard to say whether Donald Trump is a genuine bigot or an acting bigot.  Either way, he's a bigot.  But while all this goes on, Donald Trump has shown a softness for White Supremacists and Dictators across the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump has always jumped on actions and/or words committed by minorities, whether it's ISIS inspired terrorists like the scoundrel who committed the Orlando and San Bernardino acts, or any black or Hispanic male that shoots and kills someone.  But when it comes to White Supremacists, Donald Trump often agrees with their ideas and retweets them.  Just like he did with that stupid Anti-Semitic Hillary picture.  He's liked their messages before, he showed little anger when being endorsed by the infamous former Grand Wizard of the KKK, David Duke.  But when an undocumented immigrant in Oregon who was deported six times kills a few people, a story that hardly made national news, Donald Trump was screaming about it in anger.  This seemingly Aryan viewpoint of Donald Trump's makes him look Anti-Semitic, but is he really Anti-Semitic?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/donald-trump-star.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Star&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Offended now?  Now that's more offensive.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump didn't create that image; a White Supremacist did.  But that doesn't stop the picture from being Anti-Semitic.  The loser who made this drawing clearly plays on negative Jewish stereotypes of Jews having money and being corrupt with money.  While it's true that there are other hexagrams (a word Donald Trump is probably too stupid to know what one is) used by other religions; Christians, Hindus, even Muslims; most people would probably identify it as associated with Judaism.  Clearly, Donald Trump was too stupid to see that the image was Anti-Semitic when he posted it, but took it down after receiving criticism.  All in a day's work for someone who claims to be Pro-Israel yet can't recognize an image as being anti-Semitic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trump and his idiot associates tried to claim the image was not Anti-Semitic, that the star in question was just an ordinary star or a Sheriff's star badge, but these dweebs fail to recognize that an ordinary star is most commonly associated with having five points, while a Sheriff's star can have anywhere from five to seven points.  Hardly universal for a Sheriff's star.  But what Donald Trump and his idiot associates are clueless to is that the star itself doesn't make it Anti-Semitic, it's the reinforcement of negative stereotypes associated with Jews and money.  He can't change the meaning of a drawing he didn't create.  As my Dad loves to say, &quot;consider the source.&quot;  Something Donald Trump never bothers to do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-6&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is why Donald Trump would make an absolutely ridiculous claim of Anti-Semitism against Disney for featuring a regular hexagram on a children's book for a children's movie; Frozen, an animated film released in 2013 about a princess who goes on a journey of some sort.  Anyone who thinks that image is offensive is clearly senile and demented.  There are no hidden messages in this book.  It's just a book cover.  This is the definition of an ordinary star, one that mentions &quot;with 50 stickers.&quot;  There's nothing slanderous nor racist about stickers from a kid's book made by Disney.  Sorry Donald, that's not a Star of David.  There's nothing Jewish about this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So is Donald Trump against my religion?  Probably not, but he's stupid and ignorant for not knowing something that's anti-Semitic.  He has a son-in-law who's Jewish, with Jewish grandchildren, so I seriously doubt Trump hates Jewish people.  But not condemning Anti-Semitism and blindly running a campaign for White Supremacists is a sure sign that Donald Trump doesn't love Jewish people either.  To this idiot, it's all about winning by any means necessary.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;tweet col-md-6&quot; style=&quot;padding: 30px;&quot;&gt;
	&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Where is the outrage for this Disney book? Is this the &amp;#39;Star of David&amp;#39; also? &lt;br /&gt;Dishonest media! &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/Frozen?src=hash&quot;&gt;#Frozen&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/4LJBpSm8xa&quot;&gt;pic.twitter.com/4LJBpSm8xa&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Donald J. Trump (@realDonaldTrump) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/750865499660091393&quot;&gt;July 7, 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
	&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/07/07/donald-the-racist-ugly-misogynistic-pig</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/07/07/donald-the-racist-ugly-misogynistic-pig</guid>
        
        
        <category>politics</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Halfway through 2016 - My Year in Review</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; We've reached the end of June, which essentially means we're halfway through the year.  I've had a successful year so far, and I'm aiming to continue that with an even better second half of the year.  So here's to me, but also to those who have supported me along the way, because I wouldn't be the person I am without the loving support of my family and friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/adam-barley.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Adam&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;I've won this quarter (and half).  Thanks for the encouragement today, Barley the Hop.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My year started off pretty bad; I was really sick.  It started just before my Dad's birthday on December 30th, and I don't know what got me, but it left me feeling awful.  I developed Walking Pneumonia, which helped me realize that there are far worse things than an Ear Infection.  I ended up with one of them afterwards, and that was no fun either.  It was not a good time for me, but it could have been a lot worse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But despite that, I had a lot to look for and a lot I knew I was rebound greatly.  The reason for that, I was aiming for a full time job at Seterus.  After submitting my application and going through the interview process, I finally got my first time job as a Correspondence Support Specialist.  All the hard work I put in finally paid off, as I officially became an IBMer.  My first official day as an IBMer was February 15th, and I haven't looked back since.  It's the beginning of the next stage of my master improvement plan I've been working on for the past five years or so.  Still a few steps left in that game but it's a significant milestone for me.  In fact, it was June 29th of last year that I began my career at Seterus.  It wasn't what I was expecting, but as my Mom always says, 'things happen for a reason,' and somehow, I ended up at the right place at this time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Being an official IBMer has its perks.  Asides from a better paycheck, better benefits and 401K, I also get lots of PTO.  That led to my biggest trip so far in the year, a drive to Walla Walla, Washington, where I visited the area and beyond, with the biggest prize at the end, the mesmerizing Palouse Falls.  Walla Walla was a nice charming little town with lots of shops, wineries and surrounding views of the mountains, but Palouse Falls, and the drive up to there was amazing in itself, with the funky Palouse hills that looked like another planet.  It was a fun trip overall, and made easier thanks to PTO.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/IBM.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;IBM&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;I'm an IBMer!&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another highlight has been my evolving programming skills, including this blog page.  I've made projects out of Ruby on Rails and various JavaScript techniques, along with converting this blog page through Jekyll.  I'm working on a project made from Ember.js, a lot of fun with that one.  Stay tuned.  I've also found a niche with my writing.  I'm able to express myself more freely and happily.  I particularly like the live blog posts I did for Kobe's last game and the NBA Draft.  Those to me are where I'm at my best, since I'm thinking on my toes to keep up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, the first half of the year contains my favorite day of the year, May 10, a.k.a. my birthday.  I took the day off from work, which I can now do without worrying about not getting paid, and like many of my birthdays, the weather was perfect!  I spent the day with my Mom in Hood River, my favorite hip town along the Columbia River Gorge.  For lunch, my Mom and I went to pFriem, a brewery along the riverfront.  The lunch was perfect, along with all the beers we tried.  I enjoyed the Belgian Strong Dark and Pêche.  My Mom really found her liking for Saisons, the Black Saison and Lemon Saison. Now my Mom talks about nothing but Saisons with beer.  I love it!  To me, that's the best part of it all.  After a nice trip to Hood River, taking pictures with my Olloclip I received for my birthday, and getting a pFriem t-shirt with the bear cheering Op Uw Gezondheid, we headed back home before having a nice dinner at Decarli with my sister and Dad.  I love my birthday, no matter how old I'm getting, and as an added bonus, my co-workers decorated my desk and gave me a birthday card.  Yippee!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/hood-river.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Hood River&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Hood River is nice!  Being there on my birthday made it nicer!&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first half of the year has also been good to my family.  My Mom had a successful event for Shir Tikvah called Shirlandia.  The people there just loved it!  She called it her best event ever.  I didn't go, but much praise to my Mom and the great work she does for Shir Tikvah.  Hearing all these people talk great about my Mom makes me a proud son.  My Dad has been hard at work too for Steam Engineering.  His hard work and dedication helped them get a big client, Harry's Fresh Foods.  I'm glad for my Dad.  Now if they can only catch that a**hole Dave, my Dad will be really good.  And how can I forget about my wonderful sister Jenn, whose work as a stay-at-home coder for PBS West continues to impress her bosses wherever they are.  Jenn's come a long way from her unhappy days at her old job and continues to amaze me with her knowledge of medical terminology and radiology skills.  Having my family happy makes me even happier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I've having a great year so far, despite the rocky start.  I feel good about myself and know that this is only the beginning for me.  I have plenty of stuff planned for the latter half of the year and I'm feeling great!  I hope all of you reading this are great as well.  Life is good!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/miscellaneous/2016/06/30/my-half-year-in-review</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/miscellaneous/2016/06/30/my-half-year-in-review</guid>
        
        
        <category>miscellaneous</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brexit 101</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; I wasn't going to say anything about the global phenomenon known stupidly as 'Brexit,' it doesn't really affect me personally since I don't live in the United Kingdom.  It's really an issue out of my league.  But after seeing the English soccer team lose an epic upset to Iceland in Euro 2016, I've decided to say a few words based solely so I can use the following joke: England just brexited Euro 2016.  The timing couldn't be any better.  Here are my thoughts on Brexit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/iceland.jpeg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Thanks Iceland and its game winning striker Kolbeinn Sigþórsson for a perfectly timed Brexit joke.&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Thanks Iceland and its game winning striker Kolbeinn Sigþórsson for a perfectly timed Brexit joke.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;A brief brundown on Brexit.  Britains braimed brat the Bruropean Brunion is brad.  48% broted to Remain and 52% broted to Leave.  Brow brome breople brave bregrets brecause the Leave brupporters brade their braims brased on Xenophobia and the Breconomy is brinking.  Brat's the brasics of Brexit.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Enough of the stupid portmanteaus.  I hate portmanteaus, but that's another blog post by itself.  The whole notion of Brexit is based on conservative based Immigrant fearmongering, blaming them for all our problems.  It's no different to what's going on here in the United States with Donald Trump's blatant Immigrant-bashing Xenophobia.  Heck, one of the driving forces behind Brexit, former London Mayor Boris Johnson, looks like a British knock-off of Donald Trump.  The similarities between the two are uncanny, minus the British appearance for Boris Johnson.  Maybe it's the look after all.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;If I lived in the United Kingdom, I would vote to remain in the European Union.  I believe in collaboration with the rest of Europe over North Korea-based isolation any day.  The people who believe the European Union was making them 'slaves' somehow don't understand what freedom truly is.  It's not about fear of Immigrants.  Yet some people continue to scare people into believing the Immigrants and Poor are the root of all our world's problems.  These people claim they're somehow affected by Immigrants.  Most people probably don't interact with Immigrants on a daily basis nor understand that most of them are harmless.  It's no different to our attitude here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/boris-johnson.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Donald Trump's British brother from another mother, Boris Johnson&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Donald Trump's British brother from another mother, Boris Johnson&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Of course, it's no surprise our Idiot 'Republican' Presidential Candidate Donald Trump supports this.  He claims 'The U.S. is next.'  But we're not part of the European Union.  We're not enslaved by anything, especially immigrants.  But Donald Trump wants to scare people.  That's his only game.  Immigrants aren't the problem for us.  They're not the problem for the U.K. or anywhere else in the world.  It's people like Trump who are the problem, greedy power-seeking egomaniacs wanting to do as they please with no regard for anyone else.  That won't change in the U.K. whoever becomes the Prime Minister now that David Cameron resigned.  It will be someone else like Boris Johnson abusing the power at the expense of the common-man instead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/trump-scotland.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Out in Scotland merely to promote his golf course, where the majority of Scotland voted to REMAIN in the European Union.&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Out in Scotland merely to promote his golf course, where the majority of Scotland voted to REMAIN in the European Union.  Has Donald Trump ever gotten the memo?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;From what I understand, Brexit is a bad idea.  It reeks of fear-mongering with no solutions to actually help the United Kingdom.  It won't free them from anything.  It makes them look weaker and more isolated from the rest of Europe.  The European Union was enacted to prevent World War III or any other World War.  The United Kingdom has always been our strongest ally and it's a shame that people would buy into this hate filled garbage.  It's a preview of what life would be like with Dictator Donald Trump as Supreme Overlord of the United States of Donald Trump.  Thank god for the little guy, like Iceland, to show the English how it's done.  Poetic justice couldn't have written a better metaphor than this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/06/27/brexit-101</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/06/27/brexit-101</guid>
        
        
        <category>politics</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
