<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adam's Blog</title>
    <description>A blog about whatever is on Adam's mind.</description>
    <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 14:51:36 -0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 14:51:36 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>What To Think Of Willie Taggart</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; The Oregon Ducks have a new football coach, as they announced the hiring of South Florida coach Willie Taggart to become the new coach.  The Ducks interviewed multiple candidates, but in the end, hired Taggart over Mississippi State coach Dan Mullen.  Did the Ducks make the right hire? Here are my thoughts on the new Ducks head coach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/willie-taggart.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Willie Taggart&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Willie Taggart&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once Mark Helfrich was let go and the interview process began, multiple names became linked to the position.  Some were okay (Boise State head coach Bryce Harsin), some were bad (Ohio State Defensive Coordinator Greg Schiano), others were not interested (UCF head coach Scott Frost) and others seemed like a bad match (Western Michigan head coach PJ Fleck), yet Willie Taggart stood out as a good fit and had many of the qualities necessary to succeed in college football.  Oregon wasn't going to get a home run candidate (former coach Chip Kelly) but instead chose a young coach with all the right tools to succeed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One quality Taggart has that makes for a successful coach is a great personality.  It's one of the many reasons he's received high praise from fellow coaches and former players.  Tony Dungy, one of the most respected men in football, had nothing but high praise for his coaching ability, as did Jim Harbaugh, whom Taggart served as an assistant at Stanford.  And the biggest recruit Taggart helped deliver during his time at Stanford, Andrew Luck, was also happy to give great reviews.  While coaches don't win on reviews, it's a positive sign to hear continued praise.  He showed it today in his introductory speech, showcasing a fiery and determined attitude that Oregon needs now more than ever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recruiting is an important part of coaching, and Taggart is considered to be a great recruiter.  He did get Luck to Stanford.  And equally important is being familiar with the big recruiting areas.  Taggart's familiarity with the state of California, where many of the best players hail from, is key.  It's also important for Oregon to recruit well in other regions far away, for example, Florida, where Taggart is also familiar with.  Can Oregon get a few great players from the Southeast or Texas like they have been doing, Oregon should be in good hands with Taggart.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The most important quality though, is winning.  Willie Taggart took two lousy teams, Western Kentucky and South Florida, and turned them into winners, improving win totals for each school for all but one of his eight seasons as a coach.  This past year, South Florida finished 10-2, the best record they've had in their short existence as a football program (1997), and accomplished this in just four years out from a program that was 3-9 the year before.  Likewise, at Western Kentucky, he turned a team that was winless the year before he arrived to a 7-5 team in two years, coaching them for three years.  At the end of the day, winning is what matters the most.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left; max-width: 400px&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/willie-taggart2.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Willie Taggart&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4 style=&quot;max-width: 400px&quot;&gt;Willie Taggart with a great introduction&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course, there are concerns, as there is for any coach from a smaller school making the leap to a big powerhouse.  Can he succeed against the bigger opponents?  Can he handle the hype Oregon has received the past decade?  And my biggest concern, can he fix Oregon's porous defense?  These are obviously big concerns for the Ducks, but there are plenty of questions ahead.  Will Brady Hoke even be around or can we mark this hire as a failed hire?  What kind of defensive scheme would Taggart bring in, knowing Oregon just switched defenses under Hoke to bad results.  Two of Oregon's best defensive players last season were Troy Dye and Brendan Schooler were true freshmen, giving them plenty of time to build up defensive talent.  The offense should be in good hands, as Justin Herbert is the starting Quarterback for the next two-three years if he continues to develop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Willie Taggart has all the right tools to succeed at Oregon.  His youthful personality, relatability to his players, recruiting chops, and most of all, his success on the field makes him the best realistic hire for Oregon.  But Oregon fans need to be patient, success won't come overnight.  The Ducks made a similar choice on the basketball court with Dana Altman, and the Ducks have not looked back on the hardwood.  In a few years, perhaps they'll be in the same place with Taggart. Until then, I will be proud to continue showing my support for the Green and Yellow O.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/12/08/what-to-think-of-willie-taggart</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/12/08/what-to-think-of-willie-taggart</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bowl Preview</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Today marked the announcement of all the colorful, albeit way too many, bowl games, most notably the College Football Playoff and New Year's Six games.  The Oregon Ducks weren't eligible, but the Gophers were, so I'll only have one game I need to watch.  Here are my thoughts on the more exciting bowls and playoffs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/alabama-washington.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Washington vs. Alabama&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Washington vs. Alabama&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;As expected, Washington was rewarded with its first appearance in the Playoff, facing the Number 1 team in the country, Alabama in the Chick-fil-A Peach Bowl.  That should be an entertaining matchup.  Washington has done a great done offensively and defensively this season, but Alabama is the best team in the country.  My first reaction is that Alabama will win by two touchdowns.  The other playoff matchup is between Clemson and Ohio State in the Playstation Fiesta Bowl.  Both teams have played strong schedules, but have at times played inconsistently, making one wonder what they would be like if they played to their full potential.  I expect this to be a close game in Clemson's favor.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
    		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/clemson-ohiostate.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Clemson vs. Ohio State&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
    		&lt;h4&gt;Clemson vs. Ohio State&lt;/h4&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;With the Big Ten being such a strong conference this year, the Minnesota Golden Gophers were bumped up to the Holiday Bowl, where they'll face Mike Leach and the Washington State Cougars.  This matchup should instantly bring back memories of the infamous 2006 Insight Bowl against Leach's Texas Tech squad.  Minnesota blew a 31 point lead in that game, much to the embarrassment of Gopher Nation, and then coach Glen Mason was fired the next day.  That alone should provide plenty of motivation.  With that said, the Gophers offense has been rather inconsistent, particularly with Mitch Leidner, which would pose problems with Wazzu's high flying offense.  Minnesota needs to play a perfect game, but I would be surprised if they could pull that off.  This game will be tough.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/mike-leach.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Mike Leach&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Mike Leach is a weirdo&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;There are plenty of other bowl games that look entertaining.  The Capital One Orange Bowl features Michigan against Florida State.  Michigan was one kick (Iowa) and fourth down stop (Ohio State) from being unbeaten and Big Ten champs, but will have to settle against Florida State.  The Buffalo Wild Wings Citrus Bowl features LSU against Louisville in two contrasting styles of play.  Louisville stumbled down the stretch, and although Lamar Jackson still looks like the Heisman winner, playing against LSU's hard nosed defense will be entertaining.  The Goodyear Cotton Bowl Classic, another big bowl game, features Wisconsin against Western Michigan (the winner of the Group of 5 bid).  Western Michigan is 2-0 against the Big Ten (against Northwestern and Illinois), but Wisconsin is a far tougher matchup than the two Illinois schools.  Can Western Michigan win the biggest game they've ever played?  Will PJ Fleck still be the coach or will he accept another job by January 2?  The Rose Bowl features two teams playing some of the best football right now, Penn State against the Cheaters.  Penn State just missed the playoffs, but have been playing quite well.  Hopefully they beat the Cheaters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But there are way too many bowl games, which dilutes the quality games.  Some of them have dumb names.  Here are a list of Bowl games which I think are meaningless and stupid.  I'm not sure what Camellia is but there's the Raycom Media Camellia Bowl, which pits Appalachian State against Toledo.  I'm not sure why Boca Raton needs its own bowl game, but Memphis plays against Western Kentucky in the Boca Raton Bowl.  There's always the Famous Idaho Potato Bowl, which has Idaho (go figure) against Colorado State.  Same thought for St. Petersburg as for Boca Raton, which has Miami (Ohio) vs. Mississippi State.  Zaxby's Heart of Dallas Bowl needs a better sponsor.  Army plays North Texas in that game.  Now Motel 6 is in the sponsorship, as the host the Motel 6 Cactus Bowl, pitting Boise State and Baylor.  And I'm puzzled as to what the Belk Bowl is or what it's about.  Arkansas plays Virginia Tech in that one.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/12/04/bowl-preview</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/12/04/bowl-preview</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Football Championship Week Thoughts</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Championship Week is here, as most playoff contenders (sorry Ohio State) have one more chance to make that big statement they need to be in the final four.  Who wins, who loses, and who gets left home wishing that they hadn't lost that one game?  Here are my thoughts on the matter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/jalen-hurts.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Jalen Hurts&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Alabama is clearly the best team in the country right now...again&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;The Pac-12 Championship Game was on Friday, between Washington and Colorado.  With the Huskies left as the only Pac-12 team with a realistic shot at making the playoffs, the Huskies dominated the game, beating Colorado 41-10 in a statement game they desparately needed.  The Huskies entered the game ranked 4th in the College Football Playoff ranking, and with a schedule not as strong as other contenders, Washington needed to set the best example against a high ranked Colorado team.  With an offense ranked 3rd in points for and 10th in points against, the Huskies have been consistently strong all season, and QB Jake Browning has played like a Heisman finalist most of the season.  With the chaos in the Big Ten, Washington may not be a lock to make the playoffs, but Washington, in my mind, is one of the top four teams in the country and definitely deserve to be there.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Big XII doesn't officially have a championship game yet, but today's matchup between Oklahoma and Oklahoma State serves as an unofficial championship game, as the winner of the game takes home the Big XII championship.  Unfortunately for the Big XII, the nonconference blemishes by both teams appear to have cost them a shot at the playoff.  Oklahoma played a tough nonconference schedule but lost to Houston and Ohio State.  They've been perfect in the Big XII, but those two losses, combined with an otherwise disappointing season for the other preseason favorites, led to the Sooners being unable to climb out of the hole they dug themselves into.  Oklahoma State, on the other hand, suffered a controversial loss to Central Michigan on a miracle play that should've never happened.  This might've been ignored had they not also lost to Baylor, who started the season 6-0 but have imploded since.  But at the end of the day, Oklahoma won the game 38-20.  I picked them at the beginning of the season to win the national championship, but they are not going to make the playoffs.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The SEC championship game features Alabama, the best team in the country and Florida.  Alabama is a lock to make it back to the playoffs for the third straight year and a chance to defend their title, perfect on the year so far.  Even if they lost to Florida, they would still make it.  Thankfully, we won't have to envision that scenario.  Alabama won easily, 54-16.  Alabama, which began the season ranked #1, will easily enter the playoffs ranked #1, going wire to wire in that department.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Big Ten championship game is the oddball of the bunch as the two best teams in the conference aren't playing for it.  Ohio State, ranked number two in the country, finished tied for the Big Ten East, but tied with the only team to beat them, Penn State.  They face Wisconsin, the Big Ten West champion whose only two losses on the year came against the two best teams in the conference, Ohio State and Michigan.  The bigger question is, can the winner of this game make it to the playoff?  Ohio State is probably the best team in the Big Ten, but they aren't going to win the Big Ten title.  In a thrilling game, Penn State, down in the first half, came back in the second to win the Big Ten title.  The big question now becomes, will Penn State make the playoffs?  Penn State is perhaps the hottest team in the country not named Alabama, but yet they lost twice, to Pitt and Michigan, who blew Penn State out 49-10.  The Playoff committee has a tough decision to make, but Penn State to me, is the hot team, but not one of the best four teams.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/jt-barrett.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;JT Barrett&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;What to do about Ohio State and the Big Ten?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The ACC Championship game between Clemson and Virginia Tech is as clear as any other conference championship game.  Clemson wins, they're in.  Clemson loses, they're out.  The game itself was a tough one for Clemson.  Virginia Tech proved to be a tough out and wouldn't go away.  But Clemson won a close game 42-35.  Clemson, although a little overrated in my opinion, has been one of the top four teams in the country and belong in the playoffs.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Of course, they are plenty of other story lines for bowl positioning, such as who make the Group of Six Bowls.  The highest ranked team in the Group of 5 (the smaller conferences) gets a team in, and the battle entering the week was close between Western Michigan and Navy.  Western Michigan, unbeaten in the regular season, had a tough game in the MAC Championship game against Ohio, but ended up winning 28-23 to cap an unbeaten season.  Some people believe Navy is the better team as they played tougher opponents than the Broncos, although they lost twice.  But Navy needed to win the AAC Championship to make their case, but they lost to Temple 34-10, making Western Michigan the winner of the Group of 5.  Regardless of the fact, Western Michigan deserves to be rewarded for being unbeaten, it's not easy to do no matter the conference.  A Cotton Bowl appearance will now likely be on the horizon for the Broncos and young coach PJ Fleck, who figures to be coaching a major conference team next year (Oregon, anyone?).  Coaching changes are on the horizon, also a big headline, mainly for me as the Ducks need a new coach.  So far, Ohio State defensive coordinator Greg Schiano and USF head coach Willie Taggart have been talked to, along with PJ Fleck.  With that said, Schiano, despite the defensive pedigree, would be an awful choice for the Ducks.  His tough style would be a poor fit for the Ducks, which led to his demise coaching the Tampa Bay Buccaneers, and has no West Coast ties.  Taggart, on the other hand, was the running backs coach at Stanford, and has made winners of Western Kentucky and South Florida, which is impressive, but I don't know that much else about him.  It will be a long coaching search. --- Louisiana Lafayette became the first team since 2012 to win a game without a single yard of passing.  Quarterback Anthony Jennings was 2-5 with zero yards passing and a QBR of 3.3 (and 2 INT's).  Even more messed up was that he had the higher QBR of the two quarterbacks, as Louisiana Monroe quarterback Caleb Evans had a QBR of 0.1, going 3-14 with 31 yards (also with 2 INT's).  It should be noted the Minnesota's new offensive coordinator, Jay Johnson, was the former offensive coordinator of the Ragin Cajuns of Louisiana Lafayette.  That explains everything. ---  With all that said, here are my picks to make the playoffs with seeds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alabama&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ohio State&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clemson&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Washington&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/12/03/college-football-championship-week-thoughts</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/12/03/college-football-championship-week-thoughts</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Brand New Lakers</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; It's only the end of November, and already, the young new Lakers have proven that not only is the Kobe era over, but that they're much further ahead of schedule than anyone anticipated.  The young Lakers just won a close game in Chicago tonight, with a 10-10 record, already more than half the wins they had all of last year.  The Lakers have been the biggest surprise in the league this year and there are plenty of reasons to love these Lakers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/luke-walton.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Luke Walton&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Luuuuuuuuuuke Walton&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Luke Walton was always a fan favorite when he played with the Lakers as a young'un, the passion and energy of his play made him an important asset.  It's what made Luke the first and only choice to take over the coaching job after Byron Scott was fired.  Luke Walton did wonders holding the talented Warriors afloat while Steve Kerr was out.  Yet his job with the Lakers has been so much better so far.  No real stars yet on this Lakers team, but plenty of talented young players who work hard and play hard.  These guys embody the style of play Luke Walton brought when he was a player, and he's an obvious choice for Coach of the Year right now.&lt;/p&gt;
       &lt;p&gt;One thing the Lakers have proven this year so far is that their bench is not only the best and most productive in the league, it's almost as good as their starting five.  The Lakers have the Sixth Man of the Year on the roster but is it Jordan Clarkson or Lou Williams?  Sweet Lou Williams has won the award before and is born to succeed off the bench.  He currently ranks third in the league in fourth quarter points.  That's what Lou Williams does, and he's helped give the Lakers bench an identity.  Jordan Clarkson, on the other hand, is new the the bench role, and has flourished in the role, bringing a bench sidekick for Lou but also provides toughness and swagger on the defensive side of the court.  And while Lou Williams is the veteran leader of the bench, it's Larry Nance Jr. and his hustle that defines the Lakers character more than anyone.  His ability to go after loose balls, fight on every play and bring down the house with every slam (all of which would make his dad proud) is just what makes the Lakers tough to play against.  They always come out with the energy.  Also on the bench is rookie Brandon Ingram, who's shown potential to be a great player down the road, and Tarik Black, who has been a quality backup center when needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float:left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/lou-williams.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Lou Williams&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Lou Williams&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
       &lt;p&gt;Before the season started, I thought D'Angelo Russell would be the most improved player.  While he has improved from his rookie season, it's his surprise backcourt mate, Nick Young, who has been the real most improved on the team.  When Nick Young, aka Swaggy P, first joined the team, he gave the Lakers some entertaining value with his offense and fun attitude.  He fit well with Mike D'Antoni, even though he was not the right coach for the team.  But he fell off the face of the Earth under Byron Scott; not a good fit at all, and some doubted Nick Young would even make the team.  But Luke Walton has managed to light a fire in Nick Young, not only offensively, but on the defensive side as well.  He's managed to do a complete 180 from before, where I thought the Lakers would be better off trading him, to suddenly being an important asset alongside the last player anyone thought he would ever share a backcourt with, D'Angelo Russell.  Truth be told, Nick Young was getting too 'Hollywood' while he was with Iggy Azalea.  The last thing the Lakers needed was another Lamar Odom.  So I'll salute Nick Young for his comeback.  Who knew he'd be the longest tenured Laker currently on the roster.&lt;/p&gt;
       &lt;p&gt;The rest of the Lakers starting lineup provides toughness and stability (when healthy, of course), as Julius Randle continues to improve his game at the Power Forward position, while Luol Deng, although not putting up the numbers in the past, provides a calming presence to the team.  His veteran leadership is important, especially for the growth of Brandon Ingram.  Even Timofey Mozgov, no matter how overpaid he is, has proven to be a good enough player for Luke Walton's system to sometimes make you forget that.  Definitely an improvement from Roy Hibbert last year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/nick-young.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Nick Young&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Swaggy P got that Swagger Back&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
       &lt;p&gt;The Lakers have the perfect attitude and style of play that makes opponents not want to play them.  They're young, hungry, hard-working and passionate whenever they play.  It gives Laker fans like me hope for the future.  They've already beaten Golden State, Oklahoma City, Atlanta (twice, sucks to be you Dwight Howard!) and Chicago.  They've come back from 10+ point deficits, gone wire to wire, and never quit.  The Lakers aren't title-ready yet; they lack a closer like Kobe in his prime, but the Lakers are well ahead of schedule.  Thankfully, the Lakers are in good position to finally give up that first round pick they gave to Phoenix (now with Philadelphia) for the bad deal for Steve Nash.  The future is now for Luke Walton's Lakers, and it's about time the league started to fear the Lakers again.  The past few years were painful and sad, and the league better watch out.  The only thing to make it even better would be to have Larry Nance Jr. enter the Slam Dunk contest steal the title from Zach LaVine.  That would be really sweet, he was born to win it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/basketball/2016/11/30/the-brand-new-lakers</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/basketball/2016/11/30/the-brand-new-lakers</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>basketball</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The End of the Rich Brooks Era</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; For as long as I’ve been a fan of the Oregon Ducks, which started with their 2001 Fiesta Bowl blowout against Colorado and blossomed when I went to school there for three years, I’ve always respected the football team’s family-styled approach to coaching.  Starting with Rich Brooks, who coached the Ducks from 1977 to 1994, when he brought the Ducks to respectability and a Rose Bowl appearance before departing for the NFL, the Ducks always had, for the most part, a close knit family tree of coaching, as the ‘Next Man Up’ mantra reigned supreme.  But that era has ended today as the Oregon Ducks fired Mark Helfrich as their head coach after a disappointing 4-8 season.  Whether he was the right coach or whether the Ducks will replace him with someone better remains to be seen, but one thing is for sure, the Ducks are now just another program looking to win.  So what happened?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/mark-helfrich.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Mark Helfrich&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Mark Helfrich&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Back in the day, it didn't matter how mediocre to bad Rich Brooks was as a coach; this year was their worst record since 1991 when Rich Brooks went 3-8.  But while the Ducks were patient back then with average expectations, times have changed and the Ducks are now impatient with extremely high expectations after reaching new heights with two National Championship appearances in the past six years.  After Rich Brooks left, the Ducks remained confident with the Rich Brooks way, bringing offensive coordinator Mike Bellotti as the coach.  And Oregon continued to blossom from a mediocre team to one that consistently made bowl games and competed for (then) Pac-10 titles.  But even the Ducks needed a boost, and Mike Bellotti managed to flip the program on its heels by bringing in a miracle guru from New Hampshire, Chip Kelly.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;The Ducks became the talk of the country when Chip Kelly, an unknown offensive coordinator from New Hampshire, took over as offensive coordinator and turned the offense on its heels.  And a couple of years later, Bellotti retired and handed the reigns to Chip, where the Ducks became the top team of the Pac-10 (later the Pac-12).  Suddenly, Oregon was a national powerhouse, with a high-flying offense that was difficult to stop and all the rage.  But despite keeping the family intact, Chip Kelly didn't share that ideal himself; feeling destined for greater things and bored of college football (along with minor violations that would’ve cost him anyhow), Chip took his talents to the NFL and like before, it was the next man up as Mark Helfrich, the offensive coordinator, was hired as the new head coach.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;But what started out as Mark's greatest strengths led to his downfall: Marcus Mariota.  Like Larry Coker, who led the great 2001 Miami Hurricanes to a National Championship in his first season as coach after taking over for Butch Davis, Helfrich inherited a lot of great talent, led by the man who became Oregon's first Heisman Trophy winner, Marcus Mariota.  Of course, Helfrich got all the praises for leading Oregon to the first National Championship in the playoff era, with the perfection of Marcus Mariota leading the way, but it's easy to win when you have a player perfectly built for a great offense.  It's maintaining that success that cost Helfrich, exemplified by their defensive woes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/rich-brooks.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Rich Brooks&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Simpler times with Rich Brooks&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even in their prime, Oregon was not an elite defensive team, but their offense made up for the defensive woes the Ducks faced. Things were decent with Nick Alliotti as their defensive coordinator, who was at least able to make the best of it, but after he retired, it went downhill. Again, Oregon kept it in family by promoting Don Pellum from Linebackers coach. But after Marcus Mariota left, the Ducks struggled on defense, and their offense couldn't sustain consistency, which was explained perfectly in the Alamo Bowl, where the Ducks blew a 31-0 halftime lead after losing talented QB Vernon Adams to injury to lose the game 34-31, where the team had to hold on for dear life and couldn't. Pellum was demoted and in came Brady Hoke, the former Michigan coach serving as a coordinator for the first time. Unfortunately, a lack of talent combined with a defensive scheme change helped led the Ducks to their worst season since 1991.  That was not an issue with Chip but more on Helfrich.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;It's easy to see why Mark Helfrich was fired.  He couldn't grow the program like Chip Kelly had.  The defensive players they brought in weren't as good as advertised and their highly-rated QB recruits didn't pan out, leading to using talented transfers Vernon Adams and Dakota Prukop to come along.  For the first time since Mariota left, the Ducks appear to have the QB of the future in Justin Herbert, who showed lots of potential as a true freshman, but with a porous defense and young offensive line, the Ducks couldn't overcome the lousy defense to win.  And like Mariota, Justin Herbert is a diamond in the rough, from Sheldon High School and not highly recruited.  Unfortunately, the Ducks weren't lucky like that on the defensive side.  In the end, that's what cost Helfrich the job. Would I given Helfrich one more chance?  Sure I would’ve.  Is it surprising the Ducks didn't?  Of course not.  The cracks were showing, and unfortunately, they aren’t likely to get better now.  So where does Oregon go from here?&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;The Ducks are in uncharted territory now. The basketball team dealt with this when Ernie Kent got fired after a long run. The Ducks thought they could throw money at big-time coaches, but that failed miserably and they were laughed at when they finally made their decision to hire Creighton head coach Dana Altman. Fortunately, the Ducks were lucky to get him, as he’s done a great job with the basketball squad. So with that in mind, Oregon shouldn’t have too high of expectations with their coaching search. Les Miles? Highly unlikely to come out west. Lane Kiffin? I’d be embarrassed to give him another coaching opportunity. PJ Fleck from Western Michigan? Perhaps but I don’t see it happening. Chip Kelly? That’s a pipe dream. Will they keep their offense the same? Will they bring someone with defensive skills? One things for sure, there are rough waters upon the horizon and it’s not going to get fixed overnight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/11/29/the-end-of-the-rich-brooks-era</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/11/29/the-end-of-the-rich-brooks-era</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Football Week Thirteen Thoughts</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; It's officially rivalry week, where the Civil War and the Battle for Paul Bunyan's Axe is in full effect, along with a slew of other important games, including Michigan-Ohio State, Colorado-Utah and Alabama-Auburn.  If you're not ready for college football this week, then you shouldn't be watching football at all.  Conference champion bids on the line today in an exciting week for college football.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/jim-harbaugh.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Jim Harbaugh&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Jim Harbaugh breaking his headset, and he looks less intimidating with those glasses&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;I have seen both sides of college football rivalries.  On the one hand, Oregon hasn't lost the Civil War since 2007, throughly dominating the Beavers in the process.  But I know what it's like to be the Beavers, as Minnesota hasn't won Paul Bunyan's Axe since 2003, as Wisconsin has clearly dominated the series.  So safe to say, I know both the good and the bad in rivalry games.  Will this be the year the Gophers chop down the goal post with the Axe, something I've never seen before?  Will Oregon maintain its dominance against Oregon State, with this being their last game in an otherwise disappointing season?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Playing against the Big West champion Wisconsin wasn't going to be easy by any means, and Minnesota, time and time again, while playing against competitive teams, start off well enough but lose steam in the second half.  And this is exactly what happened to the Gophers today.  Mitch Leidner looked brilliant in the first half, his best performance of the season, leading the Gophers to a 17-7 lead.  The second half, not so much, as Mitch Leidner ended up throwing four interceptions in a 31-17 loss (again) to Wisconsin.  Pretty much what I expected from Mitch Leidner and the Gophers.  The regular season's over; they finished 8-4, which is exactly what I predicted from them, but the Big Ten West was stronger than expected, which got them in fourth place.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Civil War, this year featuring two losing teams, had nothing but pride on the line.  Oregon came in as the favorite by 3, but on the road against an Oregon State team that can run the ball consistently, Oregon had their hands full with Ryan Nall at the helm, who had his coming out party against the Ducks last year.  And scoring four touchdowns, the Beavers finally beat Oregon in the Civil War.  A perfect ending to a bad season from the Ducks, who I thought would still be a winning team at 9-3, but their defense was far worse than advertised.  Oregon's season is over, and now for the big question, will Mark Helfrich still be the head coach?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Big Game for the playoff hunt was of course, Michigan at Ohio State, and the game matched the hype, as the two teams went back and forth, and for the first time in the series, the game went into overtime.  But Ohio State ended up on top, winning 30-27 in double OT.  But with Ohio State's win, now comes the big question?  Does Ohio State, with just one loss to Penn State, get into the playoffs with Penn State, not Ohio State, winning the Big Ten East by virtue of giving the Buckeyes their only loss?  And if so, does the Big Ten title winner also make it to the Playoffs?  Wisconsin and Penn State are both ranked in the top 8 right now and have only two losses on the year.  Alabama and Clemson are locks to return assuming they win their conference champion, and Washington, should they win the Pac-12 title, would also have only one loss.  I would have to believe at this point that the Big Ten will have two teams.  Washington, unfortunately, didn't play a strong schedule, and that will cost them (assuming they win the Pac-12 title) along with the good old East Coast Bias.  Had they beaten USC, it would be a different story.  This also means Oklahoma is out of the race. That leaves the following teams: Alabama, Ohio State, Clemson, Washington, Wisconsin and Penn State.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/pitt-syracuse.JPG&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Pitt-Syracuse&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Defenses need not apply with Pitt vs. Syracuse&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;    
    &lt;p&gt;As previously suspected, Texas really wanted Charlie Strong fired and they did.  Record aside, he never had a chance to succeed at Texas.  What a shame.  As for the Texas Longhorns, Houston head coach Tom Herman has agreed to take over.  A very logical choice for Texas. --- Speaking of coaching vacancies, Ed Orgeron was promoted as head coach for LSU, absolutely the right decision for LSU.  USC made a mistake choosing Steve Sarkisian over then interim Ed Orgeron, and he's a fighter, which LSU clearly proved after firing Les Miles. --- Pittsburgh and Syracuse had an extreme shoot-out, with Pitt winning 76-61, setting a record for the most points in a game between two teams.  Speaking of Pitt, they've beaten two of the six teams still with a shot at the playoffs, Clemson and Penn State.  --- Navy also reached to 70 point club today, with a 75-31 win over SMU. --- Now that the regular season's over, my pick for the Heisman is still Louisville QB Lamar Jackson, despite Louisville's late season slump; they lost to instate rival Kentucky 41-38.  I can't think of anyone else more deserving.  --- Congrats to Colorado, who went from winning just five games the past three years to winning the Pac-12 South with a 10-2 regular season record.  Remarkable turnaround from a program who really needed it.  Mike MacIntyre deserves to be the national coach of the year for this stunning turnaround.  And they kept USC out of the Pac-12 title game.  A Double Winner in my book. --- With that said, so here are my picks for Top Ten:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alabama&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ohio State&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clemson (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wisconsin (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Washington (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michigan (-3)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Penn State (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Colorado (+2)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oklahoma (-1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oklahoma State (NR)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/11/26/college-football-week-thirteen-thoughts</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/11/26/college-football-week-thirteen-thoughts</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Football Week Twelve Thoughts</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; The season's almost over, and there's no margin for error when it comes to finishing the season strong and ending the year on a positive note.  Oregon's not going to make a bowl, but they have two games left to try to pick up the pieces and finish the year on a positive note.  For Mark Helfrich, that could make the difference between remaining as head coach or not.  For the Golden Gophers, seven wins is not enough, eight would be better.  And the playoff race is down to the final stretch, and those who lose will face elimination.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/darren-carrington.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Darren Carrington&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;By the slimest of margins, Darren Carrington's touchdown pushed Oregon to victory&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Oregon faced off against Utah, bringing back memories of their last trip to Salt Lake City two years ago, memorable for two reasons.  First was the ridiculous and infamous Kaelin Clay fumble just BEFORE he crossed the goal line, which Oregon recovered and ran a convoy to a touchdown while Utah was celebrating their 'touchdown.'  That is something I'll never forget.  Second was the unfortunate injury to Pharaoh Brown, who returns to Salt Lake City for the first time since.  Unfortunately, Oregon has had a bad season, while Utah is ranked #12 and has an outside shot of winning the Pac-12 title.  But there's a reason they play the game, and Oregon had its best defensive performance of the year, playing with their hearts, as they managed to hold Utah to just 28 points.  And needing something to go their way, Justin Herbert completed an improbable pass to Darren Carrington, who just managed to get his foot inbounds for an acrobatic catch to get the improbable win, a stunner to say the least.  Perhaps this will get Mark Helfrich one more chance, which I believe he deserves.  Next week is Oregon's last game of the season, but it's always an entertaining matchup when it's the Civil War.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;It's Senior Day for Minnesota, and on a chilly November afternoon, its their last home game of the year against the most bizarre of teams, Northwestern.  The Wildcats started the year on an awful note, losing to Western Michigan and Illinois State, but recovered in Big Ten play, beating Iowa.  Of course, this means it will be Mitch Leidner's last home game for the Gophers.  Leidner has been a decent quarterback, but too much inconsistency in the passing game kept Leidner from reaching the next level.  Fortunately, Rodney Smith and Shannon Brooks figure to be back next year (assuming neither one goes to the NFL...), and they have been the bread and butter for the Gophers this year, along with their defense.  As for Northwestern, their offense never got comfortable against Minnesota's pressure, with multiple sacks and turnovers.  The Gophers took a while to get their offense going (aside from a perfect opening drive) as Mitch Leidner finally threw a touchdown pass (his first in seven weeks).  The Gophers put together a good performance against Northwestern, and have reached eight wins for the season.  They're not going to make it to the Big Ten title game, but Minnesota has played better this year than last (although their schedule this season was far easier than last year's gauntlet).  The final game of the regular season, a battle for Paul Bunyan's Axe, as I would love to see the Gophers win it just once.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Thursday night proved to be big for the playoff race, as Louisville got blown out by Houston, probably ending their hopes.  It's hard to say what the race would've been like had Houston not lost to Navy and (especially) SMU, with two big wins against Oklahoma and now Louisville.  Clemson is heading to the ACC Title game against whoever wins the ACC's other division (Virginia Tech?), so a win in the ACC title game would put them back in the playoffs.  Ohio State barely got by Michigan State, 17-16, and Michigan needed a good fourth quarter to put Indiana away, but next week the Wolverines and Buckeyes face off in what could determine who wins the Big Ten.  But Penn State still has a shot at crashing that party.  Watch out... That leaves the following teams: Alabama, Ohio State, Michigan, Clemson, Washington, Wisconsin, Penn State and Oklahoma.  Penn State could make it to the Big Ten title game over both Ohio State and Michigan (assuming they beat Michigan State) if Ohio State beats Michigan.  Watch out...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/sc-state.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Joe Thomas Sr.&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;55 years young walk-on Joe Thomas Sr. getting hoisted by his young teammates&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;    
    &lt;p&gt;South Carolina State made history today as 55-years-young Joe Thomas Sr. (whose son plays for the Green Bay Packers), became the oldest player to play in a Division I college football game.  Proof that it's never too late to play.  Kudos for Joe Thomas Sr. --- At the beginning of the season, who would've thought that Washington State vs. Colorado could both be playing with the Pac-12 championship on the line?  Colorado has been in the dumps for a while but has finally found a way out, while Washington State finally found a defense as good as its Air Raid offense.  Kudos for both of them, but more for Colorado, who won 38-24.  Colorado is a win away from making the Pac-12 Title game.  As for Mike Leach, I still don't like him though he's good at what he does. --- Remember when Texas was ranked in the Top Ten earlier this year after beating Notre Dame?  How times have changed.  Notre Dame was not very good, and now that Texas just lost today to Kansas (for the first time since 1938), there's a lot of reasons to be upset in Texas.  Word around town is that they really want to fire Charlie Strong.  Good coach with values, but Texas has ridiculously high standards, he was never going to succeed with all the pressure. ---  LSU running back Leonard Fournette wasn't supposed to play today against Florida due to injury, but after a brawl before the game, he asked to be put in.  Toughness aside, it's probably not the best idea to be inspired by a feud. --- With that said, so here are my picks for Top Ten:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alabama&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ohio State&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michigan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clemson(+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wisconsin(+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Washington(+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oklahoma(+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Penn State(+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oklahoma State(+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Colorado (NR)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/11/19/college-football-week-twelve-thoughts</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/11/19/college-football-week-twelve-thoughts</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Football Week Eleven Thoughts</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; It's survival week in Week 11 for the Oregon Ducks, who played against Stanford to have one last shot at turning around their season and making a bowl game, which seemed like a forgone conclusion at the beginning of the season.  For Minnesota, it's the start of Minnesota's true challenges to determine their worth in the Big Ten West, heading to Nebraska to see if they still have an outside shot of winning the West.  How well would this turn out for each team?  How would the playoff chase take shape, in what turned out to be a crazy Playoff Saturday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/pharaoh-brown.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Pharaoh Brown&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Pharaoh Brown: The Definition of Tough&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Oregon faced Stanford, who's had a bit of a down season compared to years past, but finds themselves healthy at the right time as Christian McCaffrey, battling some injuries, looked ready to avenge Stanford's only Pac-12 loss last year against Oregon.  And with Oregon's defense being so terrible and their offensive line banged up and full of freshmen, Stanford easily won 52-27.  It was their last home game for the season, as their last two games will be at the road against Utah and Oregon State, with no bowl game for Oregon.  One nice thing to see was TE Pharaoh Brown in his last game at Autzen Stadium being honored on Senior Day before the game.  Pharaoh Brown has come a long way from his gruesome leg injury two seasons ago at Utah.  It's a miracle that not only has he recovered from nearly having his leg amputated, but has contributed to about the same level of play that he had before the injury.  Next week, Pharaoh Brown and the Ducks head back to Utah for the first time, which will surely be an emotional game for Brown.  The good news for the Ducks: Basketball season begins with the Ducks highest preseason ranking ever at #5.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Gophers faced their toughest opponent of the season so far in a rare Big Ten evening matchup against Nebraska.  The Cornhuskers, who have lost their last two games after an unbeaten start (albeit against Ohio State and Wisconsin), still have a shot at the Big Ten West title.  Minnesota was obviously the underdogs, in a tough environment, and for the most part, they hung tough, but like the Penn State game, Minnesota could not produce in the second half, after having a 17-10 halftime lead.  In the end, Nebraska won 24-17, as Tommy Armstrong led the way for the Cornhuskers, accounting for most of their offense.  A typical performance for Mitch Leidner, who showed his typical good moments and bad moments, an interception on the last drive sealed the win for Nebraska.  The Gophers have some talent, but lack the umph to get them to the next step.  &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;After Texas A&amp;amp;M took a bow, Washington entered in the top four where it originally belonged.  But they blew an opportunity to stay there (or go higher), getting stunned by the Cheaters.  It isn't that shocking considering how easy Washington's schedule has been up to this point, but still stunning nonetheless.  Even more shocking and less expected was Clemson, who lost to Pittsburgh at home, with Pitt winning it with a field goal at the end of the game.  Clemson won a bunch of close games, but their luck ran out tonight.  And to top it off, Michigan also lost, with Iowa stunning them with a field goal in a 14-13 upset.  With the way the season's going, Michigan, Washington and Clemson are still alive in the playoff hunt, but one thing is clear; Alabama is clearly the best team in the country and the odds-on favorite to repeat as National Champions; the only major unbeaten team left of the bunch (Western Michigan is unbeaten as well but not a major contender).  Of course, their Iron Bowl rival Auburn lost to Georgia, eliminating them from the chase. That leaves the following teams: Alabama, Michigan, Clemson, Washington, Ohio State, Louisville, Wisconsin and Oklahoma.  The final three teams have been added to the list but the former six are the best shots at this point.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/d9219de64719067415526bb881de5822.gif&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Kansas&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;It's Karma Chameleon Time for Kansas WR LaQuvionte Gonzalez&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;    
    &lt;p&gt;In what might be the funniest trick play I've ever seen, Kansas WR LaQuvionte Gonzalez laid down in the endzone on a kickoff return in an attempt to camouflage in the blue field, only to get up and catch a backwards lateral from kick returner Steven Sims Jr. for a 29 yard gain. --- Division III powerhouse Mount Union saw their 112 game regular season winning streak end today against John Carroll, losing 31-28.  The streak, which began in 2005, stands as one of two regular season losses for Mount Union, as they had previously gone 222-1 since 1994, the last season they didn't win their conference championship.  Very impressive, no matter the level of competition. --- Sad story out of Florida International, as their starting TE Jonnu Smith suffered multiple burns on his body, allegedly from his girlfriend pouring water on him in a fight.  I really hate stories like this, I hope he has a speedy recovery and can play again.  His career at FIU is over, but he's listed as a potential NFL prospect.  --- With that said, so here are my picks for Top Ten:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alabama&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ohio State (+3)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michigan (-1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Louisville (+2)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clemson (-2)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wisconsin (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Washington (-3)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oklahoma (+2)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Penn State&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oklahoma State (NR)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/11/12/college-football-week-eleven-thoughts</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/11/12/college-football-week-eleven-thoughts</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Thank You Intolerant Republicans for Ruining our Country</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Thank you Intolerant Republicans for ruining the country I used to think was fair and open minded.  Thanks to your extreme intolerance, you all have turned our country into a cesspool of fear, hate and bigotry.  Anyone with a differing view from you Intolerant Republicans is deemed problematic, awful and un-American.  Now that America has voted Dictator Donald Trump as President, I no longer feel safe or welcomed by the Federal Government.  As such, this will be my last political post, which is fine because Dictator Trump has completely ruined the country as we know it.  I am done with believing the Government will ever work for all Americans.  Extremism is the problem, not the solution, and anyone who thinks this type of change is good for us is biased and ignorant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/barack-obama.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Barack Obama&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Barack Obama will be my President, Dictator Trump is not my President and will never be my President&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Some people call it change:  I call it intolerance.  The people who voted for Dictator Trump are the same people who adamantly refused to work with President Obama or consider him their President.  To these people, it was all about race.  Everything is a race issue with them, and having an African American President was unacceptable to them.  Their attacks on him were extremely personal and racist to boot.  From Day One, Republicans in Congress refused to work with Obama, as they made it their mission to make him a one-term president (which failed), imply that his heritage disqualified him (which Dictator Trump led that racist accusation) and obstruct everything Obama had to offer, clearly believing the country was better off horrible than enacting one of his ideas for him to take credit.  Obama reached out to them; they said no, and their supporters were happy with that because they expect things their way and now.  They treated him like shit, called him ‘un-American’ simply for not having the same view as them and refused to believe the obvious facts that he was a Christian from Hawaii, because according to them, if he has a Muslim name, he must be a Muslim.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, these intolerant Republicans don’t care about what anyone else thinks.  They have no problem expressing their “First Amendment” rights, but anyone else that does to argue against them apparently don’t have the same rights.  They’ll discredit them, call them un-American, tell them to leave, and find new and inventive ways to keep their voices from being heard, whether it’s voter suppression or claiming the people actually have a say in the vote for Supreme Court Justice.  What America needs is for all voices to be heard.  But the Intolerant Republicans only want their voice to be heard, and expect everyone else to follow them.  It’s their way or the highway.  Again, it’s not real change; it’s the other side wanting their beliefs and ignore everyone else’s.  Real change actually fixes problem.  Bad change simply changes the burden from one half to the other.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Being a Jewish minority, I can no longer feel safe due to these intolerant Republicans who assume or expect me to be Christian.  It's sickening enough for people to wish me a Merry Christmas because I look like them.  Religion is not skin-color based and these Intolerant Republicans hate it when people say Happy Holidays, ignorant to the fact that people in the United States have different beliefs and religions.  It's even worse to know those who genuinely hate Jews are all of the sudden more empowered to 'take their country back' from the minorities.  After all, these Ignorant Republicans only get mad when minorities do something wrong.  A white man killing two cops?  Not a problem for them, that guy has gun rights.   A black man killing two cops?  He must be a cop-killer, a gangster and part of Black Lives Matter, a racist organization that promotes violence against cops (it doesn't).   It’s all about white power to them and it disgusts me that this type of behavior is not only not discouraged by them, but rewarded.  Bullying is not something that should be rewarded.  I would get fired by my job, like millions of honest Americans, for saying the racist crap Dictator Trump said during his campaign.  It's pathetic that he had to use this to get attention, as he didn't really need it to begin with.  How can I trust someone who has belittled, insulted and bad-mouth most of America simply to win a race.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks to the Intolerant Republicans out there, I’m just a young Liberal who hates white people for supporting minorities and Jewish, so I must be greedy with money and not a Christian, and since Anthony Weiner is a pervert, I must be a pervert too because I'm Jewish.  I’m a perfectly normal human being who's a model citizen, not greedy nor a pervert.  But the intolerant people who rule this country don’t care what ideas I’d bring to the table; they just see me as a stereotype.  They don’t care about any of the Liberal ideas that mixed with Conservative ideas would actually help this country heal together.  Rather, they’ve started a dangerous back and forth game of who goes the lowest and destroys the country.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So again, thank you Intolerant Republicans for ruining this country.  With complete control, 100% of everything bad that happens to us, and it will be really bad, will be all on your shoulders.  Republicans are the reason our country is in ruins.  True, there are some decent Republicans; Ohio Governor John Kasich, Arizona Senator Jeff Flake and former Secretary of State Colin Powell (who btw did the same thing as Hillary Clinton with those stupid emails) are example of Republicans who give a damn, but the majority hate anyone who opposes them.  They make their opinions before their opponents actually pass their laws, and now that they have all the control to do what they want, they will have to own up to their stupid ideas.  They won't be able to blame Obama, although they will try their damn hardest to blame him for everything like they have been before.  They'll live in their fantasy world where everything they do is right and everything everyone else thinks is wrong.  They want to go to war, they got one, but this is not over and Intolerant Republicans are the problem with this country, not the solution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/11/09/thank-you-intolerant-republicans</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/11/09/thank-you-intolerant-republicans</guid>
        
        
        <category>politics</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Football Week Ten Thoughts</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; It's 'I Hate USC' week as the Oregon Ducks head down to SoCal for the first time since 2012.  I really hate USC, and I make it no secret, but you can read all about that &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2015/11/21/usc-my-anti-christ&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.  But there are more important things than bashing all things USC.  The Gophers played Purdue and with the official playoff rankings out, the chase really begins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/western-michigan.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Western Michigan&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Western Michigan QB Zach Terrell&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;The Gophers hosted Purdue, a team that's been at the bottom of the pole the past few years but has nothing to lose.  Their style of play, more pass-heavy than the traditional Big Ten team makes Purdue a potentially sneaky team.  And in the first half, Purdue kept it close, taking the lead just before the half after a dumb interception from Mitch Leidner.  But the second half was a different story, as Rodney Smith led the way on the ground and the Gophers defense took over, winning 44-31.  Shannon Brooks was injured and not much is known why, or for how long.  They need him back to complement Rodney Smith, as the schedule gets tougher for the last three games: Nebraska, Northwestern and rival Wisconsin.  The Gophers have won four straight and have surpassed their win total last year, but the meat of their schedule is now.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;That leads into the game against the Cheaters.  Of course, Oregon hasn't been themselves this year and their defense is young and broken.  But perhaps an upset is in the books.  Unfortunately, that was not the case as the Cheaters won 45-20.  Not much to say here, but we can solace in the fact that the Cheaters are still overrated and unworthy of the hype.  They were blown out by Alabama, blown out by Stanford, and most importantly, lost a close game to Utah, the latter which will probably keep them out of the Pac-12 title game.  So the Cheaters are still an overrated piece of crap.  Next up for Oregon, the only other dominant team in the Pac-12 North up until this year; Stanford.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The official College Football Playoff Rankings have begun, and surprise surprise, Texas A&amp;amp;M finds itself ranked ahead of Washington.  First ranking aside, another sign of SEC-bias.  But obviously, it's the final ranking that matters.  But they won't be ranked fourth in the next poll, they lost to Mississippi State, losing their QB Trevor Knight in the process.  That's what we call a big jinx.  Also of note is Clemson jumping ahead of Michigan.  With wins against Louisville and Florida State, Clemson has definitely had a tougher schedule to this point.  As Baylor, Texas A&amp;amp;M and Nebraska lost, we can eliminate them.  That leaves the following teams: Alabama, Michigan, Clemson, Washington, Ohio State, Louisville, Auburn, Wisconsin and Oklahoma.  The final three teams have been added to the list but the former six are the best shots at this point.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/sf27.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Sam Foltz&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Proof that kindness in humanity still exists, courtesy of Ohio State.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;    
    &lt;p&gt;Baylor was completely obliterated against TCU.  Thank god, I've never liked Baylor and their imitation high speed offense.  And unlike Oregon, who made two national title games this decade, Baylor couldn't win the big game. Goodbye Baylor.  --- Washington State is now ranked and won big against Arizona, 69-7.  Who knows how high they'd be ranked if not for their loss to Eastern Washington.  But much kudos to them.  And they're still unbeaten in conference play.  If they keep up the pace, they could finally get the ESPN GameDay crew to come to Pullman, as the Apple Cup is at Pullman this year. --- I've always enjoyed the smaller schools, so I got my eye on Western Michigan, as the only unbeaten team left amongst the non-major conference schools.  They are clearly the second best team in the state of Michigan, as Michigan State lost again to Illinois.  How did the Spartans fall so far off the face of the planet?  But Western Michigan, who beat Northwestern in the first game of the season and beat Illinois as well, two more Big Ten opponents than Michigan State has beaten, has a shot to finish unbeaten.  We'll see what happens. --- Hearing about the death of Nebraska punter Sam Foltz and all the tributes their opponents have given them reminds me of how great humanity can be.  Mike Riley is absolutely the right coach for Nebraska and despite his mistakes in the past, is man enough to admit his errors and make things right. It should be noted that this was the only nice thing Ohio State did against Nebraska; they blew them out of the water, 62-3. --- With that said, so here are my picks for Top Ten:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alabama&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michigan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clemson&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Washington&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ohio State&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Louisville&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wisconsin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Auburn (NR)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Penn State (NR)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oklahoma (NR)&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/11/05/college-football-week-ten-thoughts</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/11/05/college-football-week-ten-thoughts</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
