<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adam's Blog</title>
    <description>A blog about whatever is on Adam's mind.</description>
    <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 09:36:34 -0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 09:36:34 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Biggest A**holes of 2016</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
    .row {
        border-bottom: none;
        margin-bottom: 0px;
        padding-bottom: 0px;
    }
&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 2016 has been a big year for a**holes.  Certain people purposely act like a**holes to destroy the very fabric of society for their own personal gain.  Others act like a**holes sorely for the attention.  And of course, there are plenty of people who do stupid things and end up being a**sholes as a consequence.  Of course, in order to be an a**hole, you must be around to know that you're an a**shole.  Those who die being an a**hole don't qualify.  With that said, here is my list of biggest a**holes of the year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Honorable mention:&lt;/strong&gt; FBI Director James Comey, the guy who stole from the brother of late Nebraska Punter Sam Foltz's home, former New York City Mayor Rudy Giuliani, New England Patriots Quarterback Tom Brady, New Jersey Governor Chris Christie, white-supremacist Steve Bannon, the Duckbill vandals, 'rapper' Lil' Yachty, Maine Governor Paul LePage, Vice-President Elect Mike Pence, Former congressman Anthony Weiner, Charleston shooter Dylann Roof, R&amp;amp;B singer Drake, Twitter whores Azaelia Banks and Milo Yiannopoulos, white supremacist Richard Spencer, KKK loser David Duke, University of Alabama head coach Nick Saban, North Korea dictator Kim Jong Un, Hot Car Dad Justin Ross Harris, Philippines President Rodrigo Duterte, all genuine Donald Trump supporters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/grayson-allen.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Grayson Allen&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Grayson Allen&lt;/h4&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;h3&gt;15. Grayson Allen&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The star point guard of the Duke basketball team sure knows how to become a villain, as he’s become well known for intentionally tripping basketball players.  After his third trip against Elon (did he really need to trip a player from a small school), Duke finally disciplined him, suspending him indefinitely.  If only Mike Krzyzewski would have taken the time to discipline him earlier instead of going after Oregon guard Dillon Brooks after Duke’s season ended in the Sweet Sixteen last year, none of this might have happened this year. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/julian-assange.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Julian Assange&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Julian Assange&lt;/h4&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;h3&gt;14. Julian Assange&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Mr. WikiLeaks claims he leaked classified info because people have a right to know all information known to mankind, but Assange is nothing more than a partisan hack, being pawned by the Russian government to do their dirty work.  There’s nothing legal nor right about stealing people’s private information and releasing it to the public.  Assange is the lowest of the low, and has done little to prove his point.  Instead, as the messenger, he’s controlled by the real hackers who have an agenda.  Way to be stupid Assange.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/kanye-west.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Kanye West&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Kanye West&lt;/h4&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;h3&gt;13. Kanye West&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;What a fuckin' blowhard he is.  Kanye West makes all these ridiculously obnoxious statements and goes on all these stupid rants, it makes people forget he even makes music in the first place.  His music has completely fallen off, but I can't even buy his album The Life of Pablo because he started the stupid streaming-only trend for hip-hop albums.  But who cares about his music anyways.  Possibly the only man more narcissistic than Donald Trump, Kanye took the time to praise him and then went into a hospital.  I’ll listen to his old music, but now he’s just pathetic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/kellyanne-conway.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;kellyanne-conway&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Kellyanne Conway&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;12. Kellyanne Conway&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The definition of a complete bitch, Kellyanne Conway had the very tough task of making Donald Trump seem like a caring person, which he is clearly not.  It didn't matter how ridiculous Donald Trump was acting, Kellyanne Conway acted like he didn't do anything wrong at all and played the deflect game to the extreme, acting completely oblivious to the fact that Donald Trump said something racist and bigoted while pushing some alternative reasoning that clearly wasn't the main point of said argument.  And for someone who could care less about minorities being victims of hate-crimes, Conway managed to take the time and complain about the death threats she received.  Selfish!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/sweet-cakes-by-melissa.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Aaron and Melissa Klein&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Aaron &amp;amp; Melissa Klein&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;11. Aaron &amp;amp; Melissa Klein&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This story should have been resolved by now, but the loser homophobes keep complaining about their right to discriminate against gays and lesbians, which isn’t an actual right in the business world.  Their attitude towards their shameful act and subsequent actions is extremely Un-Christian, from leaking the lesbian couple's personal information online to claiming to be broke despite all the money they’ve received from stupid minded saps like themselves.  There’s a big difference between the right to believe something and the right to enforce your views on someone else, yet Christian lunatics like the Kleins fail to see that.  They need to pay the fine, stop their legal bullshit and go away; clearly, they are in the wrong business and the wrong state.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/kevin-durant-2.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Kevin Durant&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Kevin Durant&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;10. Kevin Durant&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kevin Durant went from being the most liked superstar to one of the most hated by leaving the Oklahoma City Thunder to join the Western Conference champs, the Golden State Warriors, proving that 'if you can’t beat them, join them.'  Plenty of people thought Durant was determined to win a Championship on his own and not followed LeBron's route, but sadly, Durant is just like everyone else, desperate to win at all costs.  These super-teams are making the NBA quality deteriorate and Durant is part of the problem.  Thankfully we have players like Russell Westbrook who know a thing or two about loyalty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/john-stumpf.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;John Stumpf&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;John Stumpf&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;9. John Stumpf&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The now former CEO of Wells Fargo fell from grace after Wells Fargo’s long standing and disgusting practices of signing customers up for phony accounts without their approval to rack up money on fees became public.  Wells Fargo got slapped a large fine by the CFPB, but it’s not nearly large enough.  Their business practices and unrealistic sales goals are the reason why big banks are so reviled and greedy big shots like Stumpf never seem to get punished.  It’s always the low-level employees being forced to do this that got punished, and those who tried to report the unethical behavior who got fired for doing the right thing.  They wouldn’t even let their employees use the bathroom...One thing is for sure, I’m glad I don’t work for Wells Fargo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/terri-moulton.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Terri Moulton&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Terri Moulton&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;8. Terri Moulton&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Will Terri Moulton ever go away?  It's been six years since Kyron Horman went missing, and the last person to see him is still desperate to live the normal life she doesn't deserve.  Of course, living a normal life doesn't include interviewing with People and Dr. Phil with phony sob stories in a clear attempt for money.  Nor does it involve stolen gun, domestic violence and stolen car charges in a span of a year.  She obviously knows something about Kyron Horman and they really need to find him.  If they could get the scumbag who kidnapped and killed Jacob Wetterling to fess up after 27 years, they can certainly find something to get her to finally tell the truth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/vladimir-putin.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Vladimir Putin&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Vladimir Putin&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;7. Vladimir Putin&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All hail glorious dictator Vladimir Putin, who bullies his way into doing whatever he wants to do.  Fortunately for him (and unfortunate for us Americans), he managed to find a sucker in the United States to do his dirty work, Mr. Donald Trump, who thinks Putin is a great leader and making mincemeat of President Obama.  Putin is nothing more than a big bully who craves power and silences all opposition.  That’s not quality leadership, that’s pure dictatorship, and with Putin eager to make a mess of our election, it’s obvious that he and his Russian goons will do anything to get what they want.  We know they hacked into the Democrats emails.  Vladimir Putin is pure evil and Donald Trump is sucking at his teat because he’s stupid. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/ryan-lochte.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Ryan Lochte&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Ryan Lochte&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;6. Ryan Lochte&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;US Olympic swimmer Ryan Lochte had a lot going for him, but one night in Rio, he and three other swimmers acted stupidly and probably had too much to drink when they for no reason vandalized a gas station bathroom.  None of this wouldn’t have been as bad if Lochte and the other three hadn't made the false claim of being robbed at gunpoint.  Video evidence proved them wrong and now Ryan Lochte and pals have to live with the lie they stupidly created.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/brock-turner.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Brock Turner&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Brock Turner&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;5. Brock Turner&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A former swimmer from Stanford University who violently raped an unconscious woman, yet insists the only mistake he made was drink too much that night, Brock Turner is the epitome of a privileged brat who thinks the law’s above him.  Even worse, the Judge in his case gave him a slap on the wrist, ending up with three months in prison, because the Judge felt protecting him was more important than the victim.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/ammon-and-ryan-bundy.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Ammon and Ryan Bundy&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Ammon and Ryan Bundy&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;4. Citizens for Constitutional Freedom&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The militiamen became infamous early in 2016 when they took over the Malheur National Wildlife Refuge in Oregon, spending 40 days before the FBI arrested them.  These clowns are nothing more than anti-government whack-jobs who just want money and freedom to do whatever they want without any consequences.  The antics of these men, especially the leadership of the Bundy Dimwits, showcase just how hypocritical and stupid they are.  Do these losers even remember the two men that they claimed they were fighting for in the first place?  But yet, these losers were acquitted of all charges, by clueless jurors who gave them the right to enter government property and hold it hostage for an indefinite period of time in the name of protest.  They wouldn’t even convict them of having guns on federal property even though they recorded themselves with guns on federal property.  Pathetic.  Yet the Native Americans protesting the Dakota Access Pipeline in North Dakota have been treated far worse for doing far less.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/pat-mccrory.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Pat McCrory&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Pat McCrory&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;3. Pat McCrory&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt; The worst kind of Governor, a religious lunatic with no grasp of reality and an appetite for vengeance.  Pat McCrory set off a big firestorm with the single worst piece of legislation ever written: HB2, a homophobic bill preventing transgenders from using their preferred bathrooms (amongst other things).  Claiming transgenders aren’t real and merely sexual predators after children, Pat McCrory is clueless and bigoted, willing to crush North Carolina’s economy for his war on bathroom use.  Even worse, his defense for passing the bill was that the city of Charlotte overreached their boundaries by giving LGBT human rights, creating this disastrous bill in about a day, while claiming he can’t get rid of it as quickly.  Fortunately, he won’t be on this list next year, as he lost his reelection race, but the damage is done, and McCrory and his Republican friends in the state will do everything they can to control their state without a damn of the majority of voters.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/ted-cruz.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Ted Cruz&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Ted Cruz&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;2. Ted Cruz&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ted Cruz is the worst Senator since Joseph McCarthy, perhaps the worst senator ever.  He's never given a crap about anything but himself. So of course, he ran for President, the first major candidate in.  During that time, Ted Cruz did his typical hate filled routine, complete with religious garbage, lie after lie after lie, and rivaled Donald Trump toe to toe in making outrageously pathetic statements made for Reality TV.  But the only saving grace is that only one loser would win the nomination, and Ted Cruz wasn't it.  The best thing about this loser was his horrible speech at the RNC, which hopefully will lead to his downfall.  Plus for someone who loves freedom, he has no clue what freedom actually is, essentially arguing the Federal Government should cease to exist...except for banning abortions and LGBT rights, of course. In any other year, he'd be by far the worst Presidential candidate, but 2016 is obviously a special year for a**holes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/troll.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Troll&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Donald Trump&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;1. Donald Trump&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for ruining America Donald Trump.  Why anyone would be stupid enough to actually think the most narcissistic man in the planet would actually want to help people with their problems?  It's a shame he's been given the keys to do what he wants with America and divide it for his personal gain.  I already miss the days of having a President who actually represents all Americans, rather than siding with our enemies over the majority of Americans. FDT.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/miscellaneous/2016/12/31/biggest-aholes-of-2016</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/miscellaneous/2016/12/31/biggest-aholes-of-2016</guid>
        
        
        <category>miscellaneous</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Holiday Bowl Wrap-Up</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Entering the Holiday Bowl, all of the attention was on the Gophers and their pregame drama.  They were down 10 players, 4 in the secondary that were essential to stopping Washington State's Air Raid offense.  It seemed like all the cards were in Wazzu's favor.  But yet, there's a reason they actually play the game.  And there's also a reason that Wazzu and Mike Leach have never been conference contenders.  So what happened at the Holiday Bowl?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/holiday-bowl.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Shannon Brooks&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Shannon Brooks scores on the offensive play of the game&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first half of the game went exactly as Minnesota would have liked it to.  Their defense made things very difficult for QB Luke Falk, as he couldn't find his groove.  Their running game, which is obviously not a big part of their offense, couldn't provide any balance, as Minnesota allowed nothing to get through.  Their first drive was okay but settled for a field goal.  Minnesota's offense was predictably slow, but despite the lack of output, it was a field goal game in the first half, with Big Ten kicker of the year Emmitt Carpenter boinking a field goal in off the post.  It was 6-3 at the half, definitely not the score Wazzu, averaging about 40 points a game, wanted at the half.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mike Leach referred to his offense as 'Anemic' at halftime.  Anemic wasn't a strong enough word.  Despite the Gophers pregame drama, they played like they wanted to be there.  Washington State didn't look like it cared to be there.  The third quarter was much of the same for the Cougars.  Luke Falk still couldn't find any groove, and the Gophers were at least able to capitalize offensively, with a combination of smart plays, timely catches and one very lucky deflection, with Shannon Brooks catching a touchdown pass that was deflected by a Wazzu defender right into his hands.  Touchdown Gophers, they took a 10-6 lead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the end, Wazzu had by far its worse offensive performance of the year.  The Gophers, even without 4 key secondary players, made the Cougars looked uncomfortable the entire game.  Even with a true freshman at Cornerback, whom Leach tried to pick on but failed to take advantage of, the Gophers stayed strong.  And for his last game as a Gopher, Mitch Leidner played well enough to lead the Gophers to a 17-12 win.  He didn't get a lot of yards in the air, but Leidner didn't make any major mistakes and arguably the Gophers had their best performance of the year.  They were the ones who showed up to the game.  The Cougars did not.  It took them until the last minute of the game to score a touchdown, and by the time then, it was a little too late.  Advantage: Gophers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/celebration.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Celebration&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;And the winner of the 2016 National Funding Holiday Bowl: The Minnesota Golden Gophers.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Gophers finish the year 9-4, with their best win in the Holiday Bowl.  They exacted revenge on Mike Leach, who beat the Gophers in the infamous Insight Bowl of 2006.  And it just confirms to me what a blowhard Mike Leach is.  He's more of a gimmick coach than anything else.  Great defenses turn Leach into the gimmick he really is, and Minnesota in particular, was embarrassing for the Cougars, who ended the year losing three straight to three talented defensive teams.  Most importantly, the Gophers stuck together and showcased their team spirit, despite the mess from the week before.  One team wanted to be there, and it wasn't the Cougars.  Despite the disagreement between Tracy Claeys and AD Mark Coyle over the suspensions, I hope they can see eye to eye and work together for the long haul.  Claeys had a good first year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wake-forest.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Wake Forest&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Wake Forest deserves kudos.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As for the rest of the bowl games right now, there's only one team that could've used a win more the Minnesota, and like Minnesota, they too won last night.  That team was Wake Forest, who has been the unfortunate victim of what is being called 'WakeyLeaks,' thanks to a radio analyst and former assistant coach who was selling team plays to opponents.  No team should ever have to deal with crap like this.  The players and coaching staff worked hard to play their game, and someone connected to them betrayed them.  For whatever reason it was, whether out of spite for losing an assistant job, or for a possible gambling addiction, sharing private information is awful and wrong.  It's unfortunate that partisan hacks like Julian Assange continue to get away with this, and it's unfortunate that certain people paid little attention to the crimes being committed, rather than focusing on the information found.  It shouldn't happen anywhere.  But the Demon Deacons had their best season since 2008, beat a Top-25 ranked team in Temple, and gave their fans a reason to be happy.  Kudos for them.  As of yesterday, I am currently 9-12 with my bowl picks.  I'd gladly trade a Gophers win then have a perfect prediction record.  &lt;/p&gt;


&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/12/28/holiday-bowl-wrap-up</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/12/28/holiday-bowl-wrap-up</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Gophers are heading to the Holiday Bowl - Take Two</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Bowl season has begun, and Minnesota, sitting at 8-4, has one more chance to prove they're on the right direction.  But all that took a backseat early in the week when 10 players were suspended indefinitely for an alleged sexual assault that took place in September.  The rest of the team, upset with the decision, boycotted the decision and threatened to skip the Holiday Bowl unless the 10 players were reinstated.  The boycott lasted two days, and while they're still down 10 players, the message is still as confusing and complex as ever.  What exactly have we learned from all of this?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/drew-wolitarsky.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Drew Wolitarsky&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Drew Wolitarsky took charge for the Gophers&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sexual assault is not something to take lightly.  It's certainly a big problem on college campuses all throughout the world.  In that regards, such accusations shouldn't be swept under the rug.  Baylor has learned this the hard way with their football team.  And this was investigated for the Gophers back in September.  Four of the players were suspended and couldn't play at home until a restraining order was lifted.  In that regards, the Gophers took the allegations seriously, which was obviously the appropriate thing to do.  Whether a crime was committed or not, it's not something to joke about.  But at the same time, there are three types of sexual assault cases that happen: Those where it's clearly sexual assault, those where it's clearly not sexual assault, and the murky 'he said, she said' cases where it's not clear whether sexual assault occurred or not.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;This case, like many, likely falls in the latter category.  The woman claims sexual assault, while the men claimed consent.  It's hard to say what happened, as like plenty of cases, there was plenty of alcohol/drugs involved.  The police declined to press any charges against any of the players, without any proof a crime happened.  While it's not to say any of these men are definitely innocent or guilty, in cases like this, it's easy to conclude that these men probably acted stupid and irresponsible.  It's never a good idea to have sex with someone who's drunk.  For that reason, these ten players were suspended for breaking school values.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The problem with this decision, is that although it's understandable, it wasn't handled well on the school's behalf, due to the fact that the players weren't given a chance to defend themselves in front of the school leadership.  There are plenty of people who commit sexual assault, but there are also those who are falsely accused of sexual assault.  The infamous Duke lacrosse case from 2006 is a great example of this, as the players accused and the team weren't able to play that year all over a crime that did not happen.  Those who are falsely accused of sexual assault are victims as well, and have to suffer humiliation just like those who are sexually assaulted, even though it's a different kind of public humiliation.  People who are falsely accused of crimes deserve to be treated with respect as well, rather than be the victim of jumping to conclusions without any strong evidence.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;One positive for the Gophers in all of this is that it brought the team together in a way, to stand as one and have each others backs.  But even as it was clear that they weren't going to get their suspended teammates reinstated, they worked to get the best deal they could; a chance for the players to get fair due process.  This isn't a case of taking sides.  Victims of sexual assault deserve to be treated with respect, like the woman who was sexually assaulted by former Stanford swimmer Brock Turner.  People falsely accused of sexual assault also deserve to be treated with respect, like former high school football star Brian Banks, who spent years in prison and publicly shamed as a sex-offender for a crime he never committed.  And those cases in the middle, where it's a he-said/she-said situation, all deserve to be treated fairly as well.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Now that this incident can be put behind us for the moment, the Gophers have a game to play.  It certainly will be tough for the Gophers to beat Washington State.  Their defense can only slow down Washington State's offense so much, and their offense isn't capable of keeping up.  They haven't played anyone this year like Washington State, and arguably their two best defensive backs, KiAnte Hardin and Antoine Winfield Jr., are amongst the ten players suspended. On paper, the question of whether Minnesota would even play in the game or not, will provide more fireworks than the actual game itself.  The one thing going for the Gophers, perhaps, is that Washington State may not be as motivated to play as Minnesota, the Cougars were in the Rose Bowl hunt until they got beat by Colorado and Washington.  It's possible this will fire up the Gophers a little bit, but it's clear Washington State is not an ideal matchup.  But then again, Washington State has lost its last two games to FCS teams (Eastern Washington and Portland State), so anything can happen.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
    		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/donnel-pumphrey.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Donnel Pumphrey&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
    		&lt;h4&gt;Donnel Pumphrey is now the FBS's all time leading rusher.&lt;/h4&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The first bowl games were played yesterday, and though all of the matchups were between teams outside the major conferences, there was one game that featured star power: The Las Vegas Bowl between Houston and San Diego State.  Both teams beat major conference teams, Houston beating Oklahoma and Louisville, and San Diego State beating Cal.  But neither team was able to make a major push in their conference needed to make the New Year's Six Bowls or Playoffs, which undefeated Western Michigan received.  The main storyline of this game, however, belonged to San Diego State running back Donnel Pumphrey, who entered the game just 108 yards away from breaking the all time record owned by former Wisconsin running back Ron Dayne.  Houston bottled Pumphrey up in the first quarter, but Pumphrey exploded afterwards, ending up with 115 yards to break the record.  More games played aside than Dayne, an impressive feat from Pumphrey, who at 5'9&quot;, is one of the smaller running backs in the FBS.  Currently, I'm 2-4 with my bowl picks.  Grambling beat NC Central 10-9 thanks to a blocked extra point from a miracle NC Central touchdown.  New Mexico won its second bowl game in 55 years, winning the New Mexico Bowl over UTSA.  But San Diego State, Appalachian State, Southern Miss and Arkansas State all won yesterday.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/12/18/the-gophers-are-heading-to-the-holiday-bowl-take-two</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/12/18/the-gophers-are-heading-to-the-holiday-bowl-take-two</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Football Thoughts - Army Navy Special</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; The last official regular season game is always between Army and Navy, as Army entered the game with a 14 game losing streak against Navy dating back to 2001.  This year, Army has looked better than they have, entering the game above .500, which has happened only once in the past 20 years.  Navy entered the game limping at 9-3, with some key injuries and losing the Temple in the AAC championship game.  Would this be the year Army finally beats Navy?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/army-navy.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Army-Navy&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Army finally beat Navy&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fortunately for Army, the answer is yes, as Army won a hard fought game, beating Navy 21-17.  You always have to appreciate those who fight for us, not only Army and Navy, but also Air Force, which also went 9-3 and won the Commander-in-Chief's Trophy by beating both Army and Navy.  --- Tonight is the Heisman Trophy presentation, with five finalists: Lamar Jackson (QB Louisville), DeShaun Watson (QB Clemson), Baker Mayfield (QB Oklahoma), Dede Westbrook (WR Oklahoma), and Jabril Peppers (LB Michigan).  Lamar Jackson was absolutely dynamite early in the season and quickly jumped out as a front-runner by a wide margin.  But his last two games, losses to Houston and Kentucky, exposed him and left a opening for one of the other candidates to win.  So was that enough for Lamar Jackson to win the Heisman?  It was.  Congratulations to Lamar Jackson for winning the Heisman Trophy this year.  Despite the late season struggles, no one even came close to the production Lamar Jackson brought to the field.  So with all that said, now I'm going to predict every bowl game, from the worst to the best, to my Gophers to the most irrelevant of teams (I'll pick North Texas).  Here we go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Air Force Reserve Celebration Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;North Carolina Central vs. Grambling&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 17th&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Two HBCU's (historically black colleges &amp;amp; universities) from the FCS play in the Air Force Reserve Celebration Bowl.  My pick is &lt;strong&gt;Grambling&lt;/strong&gt; because their only loss was to Arizona by 10.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
    		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/utsa.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;UTSA&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
    		&lt;h4&gt;Any team with the nickname Roadrunners is cool with me&lt;/h4&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gildan New Mexico Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;New Mexico vs. UTSA&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 17th&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;As much as I'd love to see the Texas San Antonio Roadrunners win this game, due to their nickname, I'm picking &lt;strong&gt;New Mexico&lt;/strong&gt; to win the New Mexico Bowl.  It only makes sense.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Las Vegas Bowl presented by Geico&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Houston vs. San Diego State&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 17th&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Houston may have beaten Oklahoma and Louisville, but had a disappointing season losing to Navy, Memphis and SMU, while losing coach Tom Herman to Texas.  They made a great hire to promote offensive coordinator Major Applewhite to the job.  They'll have their hands full against Donnel Pumphrey, who along with Texas RB D'Onta Foreman, rushed for 2000 plus yards in the regular season, currently ranked second on the all-time NCAA list and needs 108 yards to break Ron Dayne's all time record. The most fascinating of the bowl games of the day, but I'm picking &lt;strong&gt;Houston&lt;/strong&gt; to win it with their defense, holding Pumphrey short of the record.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Raycom Media Camellia Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Appalachian State vs. Toledo&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 17th&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Appalachian State, which won this bowl game last year, will always hold a special place in my heart for their historic upset against Michigan in 2007.  With that said, Toledo will be plenty to handle with their high flying offense.  This game can go either way, but I'll pick &lt;strong&gt;Toledo&lt;/strong&gt; in a close high scoring game.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/appalachian-state.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Appalachian State&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;No one will forget Appalachian State's historic upset of Michigan in 2007&lt;/h4&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AutoNation Cure Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;UCF vs. Arkansas State&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 17th&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Former Oregon Offensive Coordinator Scott Frost led UCF to a 6-6 record after the Knights finished winless the year before.  Arkansas State is 7-5 whose best win came against Troy.  I'm picking &lt;strong&gt;UCF&lt;/strong&gt; to win this game.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;R+L Carriers New Orleans Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Southern Mississippi vs. Louisiana-Lafayette&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 17th&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;With all due respect, they should just cancel this game.  Both teams went 6-6, a rather hum-drum matchup between two schools that are only playing in a bowl game because of the plethora of games.  But I'll pick the &lt;strong&gt;Ragin' Cajuns of Louisiana-Lafayette&lt;/strong&gt; for having one of the best nicknames in college football.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Miami Beach Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Central Michigan vs. Tulsa&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 19th&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Karma is a B**ch, and it will catch up to the Chippewas of Central Michigan, whose controversial exciting upset of Oklahoma State should have never happened in the first place.  If not for that, the 6-6 Chippewas wouldn't even be here.  I'm picking &lt;strong&gt;Tulsa&lt;/strong&gt; to win this game.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
    		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/big-red.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Big Red&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
    		&lt;h4&gt;I'm still not sure what Big Red is supposed to be&lt;/h4&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Boca Raton Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Memphis vs. Western Kentucky&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 20th&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Two under the radar teams face off in the Boca Raton Bowl as Memphis and Western Kentucky have quietly become good football teams, after years of being irrelevant losers.  I'm still not sure what Western Kentucky's mascot's big-red is all about, but I'm picking &lt;strong&gt;Western Kentucky&lt;/strong&gt; to win a close game, despite their head coach Jeff Brohm recently taking the job at Purdue.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;San Diego County Credit Union Poinsettia Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;BYU vs. Wyoming&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 21st&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Wyoming has been a pleasant surprise, coach Craig Bohl has done a good job turning the program around after a successful job at North Dakota State.  With that said, BYU is more experienced, so while I'll root for the Cowboys, I'll pick &lt;strong&gt;BYU&lt;/strong&gt; to win.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Famous Idaho Potato Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Idaho vs. Colorado State&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 22nd&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The Vandals of Idaho have never been good historically, but enter the Potato Bowl with a home-field advantage.  But Colorado State has played a tougher schedule.  This one can go either way, but I'll pick &lt;strong&gt;Colorado State&lt;/strong&gt; to win.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Popeyes Bahamas Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Eastern Michigan vs. Old Dominion&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 23rd&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Eastern Michigan, never a good football team, are in their first bowl game since 1987.  On the other side is Old Dominion, playing in their first bowl game ever after joining the FBS in 2014 and restarting their football program in 2009.  And what a better place to play in a bowl than the Bahamas.  I'll pick &lt;strong&gt;Old Dominion&lt;/strong&gt; to win because they've accomplished a lot in such little time.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lockheed Martin Armed Forces Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Louisiana Tech vs. Navy&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 23rd&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Navy started off well, and were close to making a discussion for the Group of 5 winner based on their schedule, but losses to Temple in the AAC Championship game and rival Army for the first time since 2001 leave the Midshipmen wounded and sinking.  I'm picking &lt;strong&gt;Louisiana Tech&lt;/strong&gt; to win this game.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dollar General Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Ohio vs. Troy&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 23rd&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;It's the battle of short names as Ohio plays against Troy.  Ohio had a close loss to Western Michigan in the MAC Championship game and nearly beat Tennessee while Troy nearly beat mighty Clemson in a close 30-24 Clemson win.  I'll pick &lt;strong&gt;Ohio&lt;/strong&gt; to win coming off a hard fought championship game.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hawai'i Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Hawai'i vs. Middle Tennessee&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 24th&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The only team getting any joy from being in Hawai'i is Middle Tennessee, as 6-7 Hawai'i always gets to enjoy the fun of Hawai'i.  Though the Rainbow Warriors have the home-court advantage, they face a better offense as &lt;strong&gt;Middle Tennessee&lt;/strong&gt; wins this game.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St. Petersburg Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Miami (Ohio) vs. Mississippi State&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 26th&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Another bowl game that shouldn't be played as Miami (Ohio), with a 6-6 record, faces Mississippi State, who enters the game with a losing 5-7 record, only qualifying with no winning teams available to select.  Last year, all three 5-7 teams won their bowl games, and Mississippi State, who pulled an upset against Texas A&amp;amp;M late in the season, faces a smaller-conference Miami (Ohio), who are on a six game winning streak after starting the season 0-6.  I'll pick &lt;strong&gt;Mississippi State&lt;/strong&gt; to win this game.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Quick Lane Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Maryland vs. Boston College&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 26th&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;A battle between two former ACC Rivals who improved after bad seasons, neither Maryland nor Boston College are exciting to watch.  The Gophers won the Quick Lane Bowl last year, and I'll pick the Big Ten to continue to win a boring bowl game as &lt;strong&gt;Maryland&lt;/strong&gt; gets the victory against Boston College.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Camping World Independence Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;NC State vs. Vanderbilt&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 26th&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;No 6-6 team had as big of an effect on the College Football Playoff hunt as NC State did, after missing a potential game-winning field goal against Clemson that would've completely altered the landscape of the season for not only the ACC but for the Playoff race in general.  Vandy played better to end the season, and has LB Zach Cunningham, who's one of the top defensive players in the country.  I'm picking &lt;strong&gt;Vanderbilt&lt;/strong&gt; to win this matchup of 6-6 teams.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zaxby's Heart of Dallas Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Army vs. North Texas&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 27th&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Army, now having beaten Navy, enters the Heart of Dallas Bowl with a 7-5 record, holding their heads up high.  They face North Texas, who finished 5-7 and got in thanks to the plethora of bowl games and not enough positions to fill them with.  I'm picking &lt;strong&gt;Army&lt;/strong&gt; to win this game.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Military Bowl Presented by Northrop Grumman&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Temple vs. Wake Forest&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 27th&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Temple enters the game as perhaps the hottest team outside the Power 5 conferences, winning the AAC and currently on a 7 game winning streak, impressive considering that they were once kicked out of the former Big East conference for being such a bad football team.  But their coach Matt Thule recently accepted the job at Baylor.  Wake Forest, 6-6, hasn't done anything particularly impressive.  So I'll give &lt;strong&gt;Temple&lt;/strong&gt; the nod here.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;National Funding Holiday Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Minnesota vs. Washington State&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 27th&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;My Gophers finished the season 8-4, but yet they couldn't beat anyone better than them.  They won all the games they were supposed to, but couldn't quite pull up an upset, with their defense holding fort but their offense sputtering in the second half.  They face Washington State, whose Air Raid offense will keep the Gophers secondary on its toes all night.  A quasi-rematch of sorts from Minnesota's disastrous 31-point lead in the Insight Bowl against Mike Leach's Texas Tech that was blown to lose the game, this game will have the same setup as that game.  Minnesota's defense is up for the task against Washington State, who like Minnesota, struggled against the top teams in their conference, losing their last two games against Colorado and Washington.  But as typical of the Gophers season, in fact, the past few seasons, the game will be decided by QB Mitch Leidner.  Luke Falk has been consistent in his game as Wazzu's QB, but Mitch Leidner has struggled to find any consistency in his play, often using his feet to keep the Gophers in play.  Chances are, Leidner will never change, as &lt;strong&gt;Washington State&lt;/strong&gt; will win.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Motel 6 Cactus Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Boise State vs. Baylor&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 27th&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Baylor started the season under a lot of controversy over the Art Briles firing and the handling of Title IX issues, going 6-0.  Then QB Seth Russell got injured for the season and Baylor went from being a possible Playoff team to an average 6-6.  Boise State has had some good football teams in the past, and if not for stinging losses against Wyoming and Air Force, might've been playing in the Cotton Bowl.  I expect &lt;strong&gt;Boise State&lt;/strong&gt; to win this game.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
    		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/james-conner.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;James Conner&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
    		&lt;h4&gt;One of the best stories this year, the comeback of James Conner&lt;/h4&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Era Pinstripe Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Pittsburgh vs. Northwestern&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 28th&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Pittsburgh is one of the feel good teams in the country, led by running back James Conner, whose return to the game from battling Hodgkins Lymphoma last year has been one of the best stories in college football, plays against weird Northwestern in his final game, as Conner is heading to the NFL.  Pitt, having beaten both Penn State and Clemson, comes into the game playing their best football, while Northwestern has been difficult to figure out.  I'm sticking with consistency, as &lt;strong&gt;Pittsburgh&lt;/strong&gt; wins this game.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Russell Athletic Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;West Virginia vs. Miami&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 28th&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Former Big East rivals West Virginia and Miami play in the Russell Athletic Bowl, as West Virginia, having finished with a 10-2 record, were close to winning the Big XII title but didn't get the attention they deserved.  Miami also had the hype, but stumbled in Mark Richt's first season coaching the Hurricanes.  I'm picking &lt;strong&gt;West Virginia&lt;/strong&gt; to win this game.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Foster Farms Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Indiana vs. Utah&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 28th&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Utah entered the season as a possible Pac-12 championship contender, but faltered down the stretch, losing to Oregon.  Indiana finally learned to play defense under coach Kevin Wilson, but couldn't win the big game, as Kevin Wilson resigned after allegations of player misconduct surfaced.  Both teams enter this game wounded, but Utah still has the superior team.  With apologies to my cousin, I'm picking &lt;strong&gt;Utah&lt;/strong&gt; to win easily.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AdvoCare V100 Texas Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Texas A&amp;amp;M vs. Kansas State&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 28th&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Another matchup of former conference foes, this one from the Big XII, as Texas A&amp;amp;M, who was ranked #4 in the first playoff rankings, stumbled after losing to Alabama, with their only wins during that stretch against non-conference foes New Mexico State and UTSA.  Kansas State had another solid season, with coach Bill Snyder proving how unflappable he is.  Though Texas A&amp;amp;M is the better team, I pick &lt;strong&gt;Kansas State&lt;/strong&gt; in an upset, as they always play with their hearts.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Birmingham Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;South Florida vs. South Carolina&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 29th&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;South Florida enters the game with its best record since the program began in 1997, but Willie Taggart is now the coach for the Oregon Ducks.  They play South Carolina, who looked pretty average this year, finishing 6-6.  I'm picking &lt;strong&gt;South Florida&lt;/strong&gt; to win.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Belk Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Arkansas vs. Virginia Tech&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 29th&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Recently retired coach Frank Beamer was always a class act during his time at Virginia Tech.  Arkansas coach Bret Bielema is a meathead.  For that reason alone, I'm picking &lt;strong&gt;Virginia Tech&lt;/strong&gt; to beat Arkansas.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Valero Alamo Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Oklahoma State vs. Colorado&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 29th&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Perhaps the best Non-Playoff/New Year's Six bowl game is the always entertaining Alamo Bowl between another set of former Big XII rivals Oklahoma State and Colorado.  The Buffaloes have been the biggest surprise of the season, coming from the bottom of the Pac-12 barrel since their entrance in the conference to win the Pac-12 South.  Mike MacIntrye should be the coach of the year.  Oklahoma State, on the other hand, can play the disrespect card after that controversial loss to Central Michigan, as they were in the hunt for the Big XII title until the season finale against Oklahoma.  Colorado has perhaps the best secondary in the country, which could be enough to slow down Oklahoma State's offense.  &lt;strong&gt;Colorado&lt;/strong&gt; wins to complete a successful turnaround they've long deserved.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AutoZone Liberty Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Georgia vs. TCU&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 30th&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The Liberty Bowl features two of the more disappointing teams in the country as neither Georgia nor TCU lived to their potential.  TCU has talented but inconsistent QB Kenny Hill, while Georgia was unable to take advantage of the talented RB Nick Chubb.  I'll pick &lt;strong&gt;TCU&lt;/strong&gt; to win this game because Gary Patterson always finds a way to win (especially true last year at the Alamo Bowl).&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hyundai Sun Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Stanford vs. North Carolina&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 30th&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;This will be the end of the exciting career for all-world Running Back Christian McCaffrey, as he's off to the NFL after this game.  North Carolina, on the flipside, has QB Mitch Trubisky, who is rated as the top QB in next year's NFL Draft (I'm not sure why, I don't know enough about his game).  Either way, &lt;strong&gt;Stanford&lt;/strong&gt; wins this game, giving McCaffrey a win to end his celebrated career.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Franklin American Mortgage Music City Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Nebraska vs. Tennessee&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 30th&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;A battle for two teams who had higher hopes in the season, Nebraska played well to begin the season, while going through the emotions of losing their punter Sam Foltz in a bus accident, but faltered down the stretch against the top Big Ten teams (Ohio State, Wisconsin).  Tennessee started the season ranked in the Top Ten and was seen as a lock to win the SEC East, but after multiple comeback wins, faltered down the stretch.  This game may come down to quarterback play, as Tommy Armstrong is battling a hamstring injury for the Cornhuskers and may not be able to play in this one.  Assuming he doesn't play, &lt;strong&gt;Tennessee&lt;/strong&gt; will win this game.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nova Home Loans Arizona Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;South Alabama vs. Air Force&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 30th&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;South Alabama may be 6-6, and truth be told, they only won two conference games, but they did beat Mississippi State and San Diego State.  Air Force, on the other hand, finished 9-3 but finished 4th in the Mountain West West division.  Despite their name, Air Force almost exclusively runs the ball.  &lt;strong&gt;Air Force&lt;/strong&gt; wins this game.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Capital One Orange Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Michigan vs. Florida State&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 30th&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Two plays turned out to be the difference between Michigan winning the Big Ten and playing in the Playoffs, to winding up in the Orange Bowl and not even being selected for a New Year's Six game.  Florida State has played well late in the season, but was embarrassed by Louisville and lost to Clemson, knocking them out of the Playoff race.  Michigan has one of the best defenses in the country, which poses problems for FSU and their start running back Dalvin Cook.  Michigan is pissed for that reason, I'm picking &lt;strong&gt;Michigan&lt;/strong&gt; to win this one.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Buffalo Wild Wings Citrus Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;LSU vs. Louisville&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 31st&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;A classic battle between an offensive juggernaut and defensive stalwart takes place in the Citrus Bowl as Louisville, led by Heisman winner Lamar Jackson, faces off against the highly regarded defense of LSU.  Louisville played like a Playoff contender with their shakedown of Florida State, but stumbled late in the season with losses to Houston and Kentucky, making Lamar Jackson look average.  This should be one of the most entertaining bowl matchups, but defense wins champions, so I'm picking the rejuvenated &lt;strong&gt;LSU&lt;/strong&gt; to win a close game.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TaxSlayer Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Georgia Tech vs. Kentucky&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 31st&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Kentucky has been a pleseant surprise this year, riding a big upset against in-state rival Louisville.  Georgia Tech, of course, loves to run the ball with the triple-option offense.  This game can go either way, but I'll pick &lt;strong&gt;Kentucky&lt;/strong&gt; to win a close game.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Outback Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Florida vs. Iowa&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;January 2nd&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;You can forget about scoring in this game, as neither Florida nor Iowa are high-scoring teams.  Iowa always seems to play in the Outback Bowl, so I'm not quite sure how motivated they are in this one.  I'm picking &lt;strong&gt;Florida&lt;/strong&gt; to win this game.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Goodyear Cotton Bowl Classic&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Western Michigan vs. Wisconsin&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;January 2nd&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The Cotton Bowl will have the most compelling matchup as Group of 5 winner Western Michigan, who finished the regular season undefeated, gets their reward by playing in the Cotton Bowl in the biggest game of their school's history, playing against Wisconsin.  The Broncos beat two Big Ten teams en route to an unbeaten season, but Wisconsin is far better defensively than Northwestern and Illinois.  But that's not an excuse to sleep on Western Michigan.  Zach Terrell has done a great job this season at the QB position, which has been Wisconsin's weak point, shuffling between Alex Hornibrook and Bart Houston at QB.  But a running game led by Corey Clement has carried Wisconsin throughout the season.  Meanwhile, Western Michigan Wide Receiver Corey Davis is now the all-time NCAA leader in receiving yards.  There's plenty to like about this matchup, but defense wins, so while I'm rooting for Western Michigan to pull the upset, I have to pick &lt;strong&gt;Wisconsin&lt;/strong&gt; to win.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rose Bowl Game Presented by Northwestern Mutual&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;USC vs. Penn State&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;January 2nd&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Maybe the two hottest teams not named Alabama play in the Rose Bowl as USC plays surprise Big Ten Champion Penn State.  If not for early season struggles, these two teams could've played in the Playoffs, but will have to settle for a Rose Bowl bid, which seemed improbable for Penn State this season.  With everything that's happened with their awful Sandusky scandal, is nothing short of a miracle for them to recover so quickly.  The Cheaters of course, lost badly to Alabama 52-6 to begin the season, ending up 1-3 before winning out the season with QB Sam Darnold.  Penn State may have the best QB-RB combo with Trace McSorley and Saquon Barkley and have looked very impressive.  But will that hot streak continue with all that time off?  With that said, there's definitely no way I can't pick &lt;strong&gt;Penn State&lt;/strong&gt; to win this game.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Allstate Sugar Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Auburn vs. Oklahoma&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;January 2nd&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;For all the talk about the SEC being the best conference in college football, it should be noted that besides unbeaten Alabama, the next best team is 8-4 Auburn.  Turns out, the SEC is overrated, and it will show here in the Sugar Bowl.  Oklahoma, who won the Big XII but wasn't seriously considered as a Playoff team due to two nonconference losses to Houston and Ohio State, have the best QB-WR combo in the country, with Baker Mayfield and Dede Westbrook, both of whom are Heisman finalists.  The Sooners have a chip on their shoulder, that's why I'm picking &lt;strong&gt;Oklahoma&lt;/strong&gt; to beat Auburn easily.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;College Football Playoff semifinal at the Chick-fil-A Peach Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Washington vs. Alabama&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 31st&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The big games, of course, are the Playoff games.  The first playoff game is between unbeaten Alabama and Washington.  The Crimson Tide, with their elite defense, and dynamic offense led by freshman QB Jalen Hurts, have clearly been the best team in the nation from the start to the finish of the season.  I certainly don't like Alabama, but yet, they have dominated this season.  Their closest margin of victory came against Ole Miss, a team that has given Alabama fits the past few years.  Yet Alabama beat them 48-43, needing a comeback to win that game.  Washington, of course, is always a rival of Oregon's, and they finally beat the Ducks, emphatically with an embarrassing 70-21 win.  It also stings to wonder what would have happened if Oregon had at least tried to hire Chris Petersen as their coach.  He's a great coach, and losing Steve Sarkisian to USC was the best thing to ever happen to the Huskies.  Washington has been great all season offensively and defensively, but their only loss was to USC, whose defense has improved since they got whomped by Alabama.  Alabama's defense is far better than USC's will ever be, which is why &lt;strong&gt;Alabama&lt;/strong&gt; will return to the National Championship game.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;College Football Playoff semifinal at the PlayStation Fiesta Bowl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Ohio State vs. Clemson&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;December 31st&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The other semifinal game, between Ohio State and Clemson, appears to be more evenly matched.  Both teams have been great on the defensive side of the ball.  Yet their offense, at times, have appeared to be inconsistent, especially Ohio State.  They each lost one game by a field goal or less, with Penn State beating Ohio State by 3 and Pittsburgh beating Clemson by 1.  Each of them beat some pretty tough teams.  Clemson has wins against Auburn, Florida State and Louisville, while Ohio State beat the likes of Oklahoma, Wisconsin and Michigan.  The two teams are evenly matched and either one can win, but who has the edge.  I'm giving the slight edge to DeShaun Watson and &lt;strong&gt;Clemson&lt;/strong&gt; for having a more consistent quarterback.  JT Barrett has been great for the Buckeyes but yet their offense hasn't been nearly as dynamic as it was two years ago when the won the National Championship with Ezekiel Elliott and company.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;College Football Playoff National Championship&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Washington/Alabama vs. Ohio State/Clemson&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;January 9th&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;I've obviously predicted a rematch of last year's National Championship game between the two teams.  The difference this time is that Alabama is unbeaten and Clemson has the one loss, a role reversal to say the least.  But Clemson is a little worse than last year, while Alabama is a little better.  I'll go more in depth when the actual matchup arises, but right now, I don't see anyone capable of beating &lt;strong&gt;Alabama&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;


&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/12/10/college-football-thoughts-army-navy-special</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/12/10/college-football-thoughts-army-navy-special</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What To Think Of Willie Taggart</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; The Oregon Ducks have a new football coach, as they announced the hiring of South Florida coach Willie Taggart to become the new coach.  The Ducks interviewed multiple candidates, but in the end, hired Taggart over Mississippi State coach Dan Mullen.  Did the Ducks make the right hire? Here are my thoughts on the new Ducks head coach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/willie-taggart.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Willie Taggart&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Willie Taggart&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once Mark Helfrich was let go and the interview process began, multiple names became linked to the position.  Some were okay (Boise State head coach Bryce Harsin), some were bad (Ohio State Defensive Coordinator Greg Schiano), others were not interested (UCF head coach Scott Frost) and others seemed like a bad match (Western Michigan head coach PJ Fleck), yet Willie Taggart stood out as a good fit and had many of the qualities necessary to succeed in college football.  Oregon wasn't going to get a home run candidate (former coach Chip Kelly) but instead chose a young coach with all the right tools to succeed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One quality Taggart has that makes for a successful coach is a great personality.  It's one of the many reasons he's received high praise from fellow coaches and former players.  Tony Dungy, one of the most respected men in football, had nothing but high praise for his coaching ability, as did Jim Harbaugh, whom Taggart served as an assistant at Stanford.  And the biggest recruit Taggart helped deliver during his time at Stanford, Andrew Luck, was also happy to give great reviews.  While coaches don't win on reviews, it's a positive sign to hear continued praise.  He showed it today in his introductory speech, showcasing a fiery and determined attitude that Oregon needs now more than ever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recruiting is an important part of coaching, and Taggart is considered to be a great recruiter.  He did get Luck to Stanford.  And equally important is being familiar with the big recruiting areas.  Taggart's familiarity with the state of California, where many of the best players hail from, is key.  It's also important for Oregon to recruit well in other regions far away, for example, Florida, where Taggart is also familiar with.  Can Oregon get a few great players from the Southeast or Texas like they have been doing, Oregon should be in good hands with Taggart.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The most important quality though, is winning.  Willie Taggart took two lousy teams, Western Kentucky and South Florida, and turned them into winners, improving win totals for each school for all but one of his eight seasons as a coach.  This past year, South Florida finished 10-2, the best record they've had in their short existence as a football program (1997), and accomplished this in just four years out from a program that was 3-9 the year before.  Likewise, at Western Kentucky, he turned a team that was winless the year before he arrived to a 7-5 team in two years, coaching them for three years.  At the end of the day, winning is what matters the most.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left; max-width: 400px&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/willie-taggart2.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Willie Taggart&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4 style=&quot;max-width: 400px&quot;&gt;Willie Taggart with a great introduction&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course, there are concerns, as there is for any coach from a smaller school making the leap to a big powerhouse.  Can he succeed against the bigger opponents?  Can he handle the hype Oregon has received the past decade?  And my biggest concern, can he fix Oregon's porous defense?  These are obviously big concerns for the Ducks, but there are plenty of questions ahead.  Will Brady Hoke even be around or can we mark this hire as a failed hire?  What kind of defensive scheme would Taggart bring in, knowing Oregon just switched defenses under Hoke to bad results.  Two of Oregon's best defensive players last season were Troy Dye and Brendan Schooler were true freshmen, giving them plenty of time to build up defensive talent.  The offense should be in good hands, as Justin Herbert is the starting Quarterback for the next two-three years if he continues to develop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Willie Taggart has all the right tools to succeed at Oregon.  His youthful personality, relatability to his players, recruiting chops, and most of all, his success on the field makes him the best realistic hire for Oregon.  But Oregon fans need to be patient, success won't come overnight.  The Ducks made a similar choice on the basketball court with Dana Altman, and the Ducks have not looked back on the hardwood.  In a few years, perhaps they'll be in the same place with Taggart. Until then, I will be proud to continue showing my support for the Green and Yellow O.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/12/08/what-to-think-of-willie-taggart</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/12/08/what-to-think-of-willie-taggart</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bowl Preview</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Today marked the announcement of all the colorful, albeit way too many, bowl games, most notably the College Football Playoff and New Year's Six games.  The Oregon Ducks weren't eligible, but the Gophers were, so I'll only have one game I need to watch.  Here are my thoughts on the more exciting bowls and playoffs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/alabama-washington.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Washington vs. Alabama&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Washington vs. Alabama&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;As expected, Washington was rewarded with its first appearance in the Playoff, facing the Number 1 team in the country, Alabama in the Chick-fil-A Peach Bowl.  That should be an entertaining matchup.  Washington has done a great done offensively and defensively this season, but Alabama is the best team in the country.  My first reaction is that Alabama will win by two touchdowns.  The other playoff matchup is between Clemson and Ohio State in the Playstation Fiesta Bowl.  Both teams have played strong schedules, but have at times played inconsistently, making one wonder what they would be like if they played to their full potential.  I expect this to be a close game in Clemson's favor.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
    		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/clemson-ohiostate.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Clemson vs. Ohio State&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
    		&lt;h4&gt;Clemson vs. Ohio State&lt;/h4&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;With the Big Ten being such a strong conference this year, the Minnesota Golden Gophers were bumped up to the Holiday Bowl, where they'll face Mike Leach and the Washington State Cougars.  This matchup should instantly bring back memories of the infamous 2006 Insight Bowl against Leach's Texas Tech squad.  Minnesota blew a 31 point lead in that game, much to the embarrassment of Gopher Nation, and then coach Glen Mason was fired the next day.  That alone should provide plenty of motivation.  With that said, the Gophers offense has been rather inconsistent, particularly with Mitch Leidner, which would pose problems with Wazzu's high flying offense.  Minnesota needs to play a perfect game, but I would be surprised if they could pull that off.  This game will be tough.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/mike-leach.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Mike Leach&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Mike Leach is a weirdo&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;There are plenty of other bowl games that look entertaining.  The Capital One Orange Bowl features Michigan against Florida State.  Michigan was one kick (Iowa) and fourth down stop (Ohio State) from being unbeaten and Big Ten champs, but will have to settle against Florida State.  The Buffalo Wild Wings Citrus Bowl features LSU against Louisville in two contrasting styles of play.  Louisville stumbled down the stretch, and although Lamar Jackson still looks like the Heisman winner, playing against LSU's hard nosed defense will be entertaining.  The Goodyear Cotton Bowl Classic, another big bowl game, features Wisconsin against Western Michigan (the winner of the Group of 5 bid).  Western Michigan is 2-0 against the Big Ten (against Northwestern and Illinois), but Wisconsin is a far tougher matchup than the two Illinois schools.  Can Western Michigan win the biggest game they've ever played?  Will PJ Fleck still be the coach or will he accept another job by January 2?  The Rose Bowl features two teams playing some of the best football right now, Penn State against the Cheaters.  Penn State just missed the playoffs, but have been playing quite well.  Hopefully they beat the Cheaters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But there are way too many bowl games, which dilutes the quality games.  Some of them have dumb names.  Here are a list of Bowl games which I think are meaningless and stupid.  I'm not sure what Camellia is but there's the Raycom Media Camellia Bowl, which pits Appalachian State against Toledo.  I'm not sure why Boca Raton needs its own bowl game, but Memphis plays against Western Kentucky in the Boca Raton Bowl.  There's always the Famous Idaho Potato Bowl, which has Idaho (go figure) against Colorado State.  Same thought for St. Petersburg as for Boca Raton, which has Miami (Ohio) vs. Mississippi State.  Zaxby's Heart of Dallas Bowl needs a better sponsor.  Army plays North Texas in that game.  Now Motel 6 is in the sponsorship, as the host the Motel 6 Cactus Bowl, pitting Boise State and Baylor.  And I'm puzzled as to what the Belk Bowl is or what it's about.  Arkansas plays Virginia Tech in that one.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/12/04/bowl-preview</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/12/04/bowl-preview</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Football Championship Week Thoughts</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Championship Week is here, as most playoff contenders (sorry Ohio State) have one more chance to make that big statement they need to be in the final four.  Who wins, who loses, and who gets left home wishing that they hadn't lost that one game?  Here are my thoughts on the matter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/jalen-hurts.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Jalen Hurts&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Alabama is clearly the best team in the country right now...again&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;The Pac-12 Championship Game was on Friday, between Washington and Colorado.  With the Huskies left as the only Pac-12 team with a realistic shot at making the playoffs, the Huskies dominated the game, beating Colorado 41-10 in a statement game they desparately needed.  The Huskies entered the game ranked 4th in the College Football Playoff ranking, and with a schedule not as strong as other contenders, Washington needed to set the best example against a high ranked Colorado team.  With an offense ranked 3rd in points for and 10th in points against, the Huskies have been consistently strong all season, and QB Jake Browning has played like a Heisman finalist most of the season.  With the chaos in the Big Ten, Washington may not be a lock to make the playoffs, but Washington, in my mind, is one of the top four teams in the country and definitely deserve to be there.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Big XII doesn't officially have a championship game yet, but today's matchup between Oklahoma and Oklahoma State serves as an unofficial championship game, as the winner of the game takes home the Big XII championship.  Unfortunately for the Big XII, the nonconference blemishes by both teams appear to have cost them a shot at the playoff.  Oklahoma played a tough nonconference schedule but lost to Houston and Ohio State.  They've been perfect in the Big XII, but those two losses, combined with an otherwise disappointing season for the other preseason favorites, led to the Sooners being unable to climb out of the hole they dug themselves into.  Oklahoma State, on the other hand, suffered a controversial loss to Central Michigan on a miracle play that should've never happened.  This might've been ignored had they not also lost to Baylor, who started the season 6-0 but have imploded since.  But at the end of the day, Oklahoma won the game 38-20.  I picked them at the beginning of the season to win the national championship, but they are not going to make the playoffs.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The SEC championship game features Alabama, the best team in the country and Florida.  Alabama is a lock to make it back to the playoffs for the third straight year and a chance to defend their title, perfect on the year so far.  Even if they lost to Florida, they would still make it.  Thankfully, we won't have to envision that scenario.  Alabama won easily, 54-16.  Alabama, which began the season ranked #1, will easily enter the playoffs ranked #1, going wire to wire in that department.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Big Ten championship game is the oddball of the bunch as the two best teams in the conference aren't playing for it.  Ohio State, ranked number two in the country, finished tied for the Big Ten East, but tied with the only team to beat them, Penn State.  They face Wisconsin, the Big Ten West champion whose only two losses on the year came against the two best teams in the conference, Ohio State and Michigan.  The bigger question is, can the winner of this game make it to the playoff?  Ohio State is probably the best team in the Big Ten, but they aren't going to win the Big Ten title.  In a thrilling game, Penn State, down in the first half, came back in the second to win the Big Ten title.  The big question now becomes, will Penn State make the playoffs?  Penn State is perhaps the hottest team in the country not named Alabama, but yet they lost twice, to Pitt and Michigan, who blew Penn State out 49-10.  The Playoff committee has a tough decision to make, but Penn State to me, is the hot team, but not one of the best four teams.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/jt-barrett.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;JT Barrett&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;What to do about Ohio State and the Big Ten?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The ACC Championship game between Clemson and Virginia Tech is as clear as any other conference championship game.  Clemson wins, they're in.  Clemson loses, they're out.  The game itself was a tough one for Clemson.  Virginia Tech proved to be a tough out and wouldn't go away.  But Clemson won a close game 42-35.  Clemson, although a little overrated in my opinion, has been one of the top four teams in the country and belong in the playoffs.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Of course, they are plenty of other story lines for bowl positioning, such as who make the Group of Six Bowls.  The highest ranked team in the Group of 5 (the smaller conferences) gets a team in, and the battle entering the week was close between Western Michigan and Navy.  Western Michigan, unbeaten in the regular season, had a tough game in the MAC Championship game against Ohio, but ended up winning 28-23 to cap an unbeaten season.  Some people believe Navy is the better team as they played tougher opponents than the Broncos, although they lost twice.  But Navy needed to win the AAC Championship to make their case, but they lost to Temple 34-10, making Western Michigan the winner of the Group of 5.  Regardless of the fact, Western Michigan deserves to be rewarded for being unbeaten, it's not easy to do no matter the conference.  A Cotton Bowl appearance will now likely be on the horizon for the Broncos and young coach PJ Fleck, who figures to be coaching a major conference team next year (Oregon, anyone?).  Coaching changes are on the horizon, also a big headline, mainly for me as the Ducks need a new coach.  So far, Ohio State defensive coordinator Greg Schiano and USF head coach Willie Taggart have been talked to, along with PJ Fleck.  With that said, Schiano, despite the defensive pedigree, would be an awful choice for the Ducks.  His tough style would be a poor fit for the Ducks, which led to his demise coaching the Tampa Bay Buccaneers, and has no West Coast ties.  Taggart, on the other hand, was the running backs coach at Stanford, and has made winners of Western Kentucky and South Florida, which is impressive, but I don't know that much else about him.  It will be a long coaching search. --- Louisiana Lafayette became the first team since 2012 to win a game without a single yard of passing.  Quarterback Anthony Jennings was 2-5 with zero yards passing and a QBR of 3.3 (and 2 INT's).  Even more messed up was that he had the higher QBR of the two quarterbacks, as Louisiana Monroe quarterback Caleb Evans had a QBR of 0.1, going 3-14 with 31 yards (also with 2 INT's).  It should be noted the Minnesota's new offensive coordinator, Jay Johnson, was the former offensive coordinator of the Ragin Cajuns of Louisiana Lafayette.  That explains everything. ---  With all that said, here are my picks to make the playoffs with seeds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alabama&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ohio State&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clemson&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Washington&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/12/03/college-football-championship-week-thoughts</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/12/03/college-football-championship-week-thoughts</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Brand New Lakers</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; It's only the end of November, and already, the young new Lakers have proven that not only is the Kobe era over, but that they're much further ahead of schedule than anyone anticipated.  The young Lakers just won a close game in Chicago tonight, with a 10-10 record, already more than half the wins they had all of last year.  The Lakers have been the biggest surprise in the league this year and there are plenty of reasons to love these Lakers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/luke-walton.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Luke Walton&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Luuuuuuuuuuke Walton&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Luke Walton was always a fan favorite when he played with the Lakers as a young'un, the passion and energy of his play made him an important asset.  It's what made Luke the first and only choice to take over the coaching job after Byron Scott was fired.  Luke Walton did wonders holding the talented Warriors afloat while Steve Kerr was out.  Yet his job with the Lakers has been so much better so far.  No real stars yet on this Lakers team, but plenty of talented young players who work hard and play hard.  These guys embody the style of play Luke Walton brought when he was a player, and he's an obvious choice for Coach of the Year right now.&lt;/p&gt;
       &lt;p&gt;One thing the Lakers have proven this year so far is that their bench is not only the best and most productive in the league, it's almost as good as their starting five.  The Lakers have the Sixth Man of the Year on the roster but is it Jordan Clarkson or Lou Williams?  Sweet Lou Williams has won the award before and is born to succeed off the bench.  He currently ranks third in the league in fourth quarter points.  That's what Lou Williams does, and he's helped give the Lakers bench an identity.  Jordan Clarkson, on the other hand, is new the the bench role, and has flourished in the role, bringing a bench sidekick for Lou but also provides toughness and swagger on the defensive side of the court.  And while Lou Williams is the veteran leader of the bench, it's Larry Nance Jr. and his hustle that defines the Lakers character more than anyone.  His ability to go after loose balls, fight on every play and bring down the house with every slam (all of which would make his dad proud) is just what makes the Lakers tough to play against.  They always come out with the energy.  Also on the bench is rookie Brandon Ingram, who's shown potential to be a great player down the road, and Tarik Black, who has been a quality backup center when needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float:left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/lou-williams.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Lou Williams&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Lou Williams&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
       &lt;p&gt;Before the season started, I thought D'Angelo Russell would be the most improved player.  While he has improved from his rookie season, it's his surprise backcourt mate, Nick Young, who has been the real most improved on the team.  When Nick Young, aka Swaggy P, first joined the team, he gave the Lakers some entertaining value with his offense and fun attitude.  He fit well with Mike D'Antoni, even though he was not the right coach for the team.  But he fell off the face of the Earth under Byron Scott; not a good fit at all, and some doubted Nick Young would even make the team.  But Luke Walton has managed to light a fire in Nick Young, not only offensively, but on the defensive side as well.  He's managed to do a complete 180 from before, where I thought the Lakers would be better off trading him, to suddenly being an important asset alongside the last player anyone thought he would ever share a backcourt with, D'Angelo Russell.  Truth be told, Nick Young was getting too 'Hollywood' while he was with Iggy Azalea.  The last thing the Lakers needed was another Lamar Odom.  So I'll salute Nick Young for his comeback.  Who knew he'd be the longest tenured Laker currently on the roster.&lt;/p&gt;
       &lt;p&gt;The rest of the Lakers starting lineup provides toughness and stability (when healthy, of course), as Julius Randle continues to improve his game at the Power Forward position, while Luol Deng, although not putting up the numbers in the past, provides a calming presence to the team.  His veteran leadership is important, especially for the growth of Brandon Ingram.  Even Timofey Mozgov, no matter how overpaid he is, has proven to be a good enough player for Luke Walton's system to sometimes make you forget that.  Definitely an improvement from Roy Hibbert last year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/nick-young.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Nick Young&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Swaggy P got that Swagger Back&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
       &lt;p&gt;The Lakers have the perfect attitude and style of play that makes opponents not want to play them.  They're young, hungry, hard-working and passionate whenever they play.  It gives Laker fans like me hope for the future.  They've already beaten Golden State, Oklahoma City, Atlanta (twice, sucks to be you Dwight Howard!) and Chicago.  They've come back from 10+ point deficits, gone wire to wire, and never quit.  The Lakers aren't title-ready yet; they lack a closer like Kobe in his prime, but the Lakers are well ahead of schedule.  Thankfully, the Lakers are in good position to finally give up that first round pick they gave to Phoenix (now with Philadelphia) for the bad deal for Steve Nash.  The future is now for Luke Walton's Lakers, and it's about time the league started to fear the Lakers again.  The past few years were painful and sad, and the league better watch out.  The only thing to make it even better would be to have Larry Nance Jr. enter the Slam Dunk contest steal the title from Zach LaVine.  That would be really sweet, he was born to win it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/basketball/2016/11/30/the-brand-new-lakers</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/basketball/2016/11/30/the-brand-new-lakers</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>basketball</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The End of the Rich Brooks Era</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; For as long as I’ve been a fan of the Oregon Ducks, which started with their 2001 Fiesta Bowl blowout against Colorado and blossomed when I went to school there for three years, I’ve always respected the football team’s family-styled approach to coaching.  Starting with Rich Brooks, who coached the Ducks from 1977 to 1994, when he brought the Ducks to respectability and a Rose Bowl appearance before departing for the NFL, the Ducks always had, for the most part, a close knit family tree of coaching, as the ‘Next Man Up’ mantra reigned supreme.  But that era has ended today as the Oregon Ducks fired Mark Helfrich as their head coach after a disappointing 4-8 season.  Whether he was the right coach or whether the Ducks will replace him with someone better remains to be seen, but one thing is for sure, the Ducks are now just another program looking to win.  So what happened?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/mark-helfrich.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Mark Helfrich&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Mark Helfrich&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Back in the day, it didn't matter how mediocre to bad Rich Brooks was as a coach; this year was their worst record since 1991 when Rich Brooks went 3-8.  But while the Ducks were patient back then with average expectations, times have changed and the Ducks are now impatient with extremely high expectations after reaching new heights with two National Championship appearances in the past six years.  After Rich Brooks left, the Ducks remained confident with the Rich Brooks way, bringing offensive coordinator Mike Bellotti as the coach.  And Oregon continued to blossom from a mediocre team to one that consistently made bowl games and competed for (then) Pac-10 titles.  But even the Ducks needed a boost, and Mike Bellotti managed to flip the program on its heels by bringing in a miracle guru from New Hampshire, Chip Kelly.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;The Ducks became the talk of the country when Chip Kelly, an unknown offensive coordinator from New Hampshire, took over as offensive coordinator and turned the offense on its heels.  And a couple of years later, Bellotti retired and handed the reigns to Chip, where the Ducks became the top team of the Pac-10 (later the Pac-12).  Suddenly, Oregon was a national powerhouse, with a high-flying offense that was difficult to stop and all the rage.  But despite keeping the family intact, Chip Kelly didn't share that ideal himself; feeling destined for greater things and bored of college football (along with minor violations that would’ve cost him anyhow), Chip took his talents to the NFL and like before, it was the next man up as Mark Helfrich, the offensive coordinator, was hired as the new head coach.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;But what started out as Mark's greatest strengths led to his downfall: Marcus Mariota.  Like Larry Coker, who led the great 2001 Miami Hurricanes to a National Championship in his first season as coach after taking over for Butch Davis, Helfrich inherited a lot of great talent, led by the man who became Oregon's first Heisman Trophy winner, Marcus Mariota.  Of course, Helfrich got all the praises for leading Oregon to the first National Championship in the playoff era, with the perfection of Marcus Mariota leading the way, but it's easy to win when you have a player perfectly built for a great offense.  It's maintaining that success that cost Helfrich, exemplified by their defensive woes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/rich-brooks.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Rich Brooks&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Simpler times with Rich Brooks&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even in their prime, Oregon was not an elite defensive team, but their offense made up for the defensive woes the Ducks faced. Things were decent with Nick Alliotti as their defensive coordinator, who was at least able to make the best of it, but after he retired, it went downhill. Again, Oregon kept it in family by promoting Don Pellum from Linebackers coach. But after Marcus Mariota left, the Ducks struggled on defense, and their offense couldn't sustain consistency, which was explained perfectly in the Alamo Bowl, where the Ducks blew a 31-0 halftime lead after losing talented QB Vernon Adams to injury to lose the game 34-31, where the team had to hold on for dear life and couldn't. Pellum was demoted and in came Brady Hoke, the former Michigan coach serving as a coordinator for the first time. Unfortunately, a lack of talent combined with a defensive scheme change helped led the Ducks to their worst season since 1991.  That was not an issue with Chip but more on Helfrich.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;It's easy to see why Mark Helfrich was fired.  He couldn't grow the program like Chip Kelly had.  The defensive players they brought in weren't as good as advertised and their highly-rated QB recruits didn't pan out, leading to using talented transfers Vernon Adams and Dakota Prukop to come along.  For the first time since Mariota left, the Ducks appear to have the QB of the future in Justin Herbert, who showed lots of potential as a true freshman, but with a porous defense and young offensive line, the Ducks couldn't overcome the lousy defense to win.  And like Mariota, Justin Herbert is a diamond in the rough, from Sheldon High School and not highly recruited.  Unfortunately, the Ducks weren't lucky like that on the defensive side.  In the end, that's what cost Helfrich the job. Would I given Helfrich one more chance?  Sure I would’ve.  Is it surprising the Ducks didn't?  Of course not.  The cracks were showing, and unfortunately, they aren’t likely to get better now.  So where does Oregon go from here?&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;The Ducks are in uncharted territory now. The basketball team dealt with this when Ernie Kent got fired after a long run. The Ducks thought they could throw money at big-time coaches, but that failed miserably and they were laughed at when they finally made their decision to hire Creighton head coach Dana Altman. Fortunately, the Ducks were lucky to get him, as he’s done a great job with the basketball squad. So with that in mind, Oregon shouldn’t have too high of expectations with their coaching search. Les Miles? Highly unlikely to come out west. Lane Kiffin? I’d be embarrassed to give him another coaching opportunity. PJ Fleck from Western Michigan? Perhaps but I don’t see it happening. Chip Kelly? That’s a pipe dream. Will they keep their offense the same? Will they bring someone with defensive skills? One things for sure, there are rough waters upon the horizon and it’s not going to get fixed overnight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/11/29/the-end-of-the-rich-brooks-era</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/11/29/the-end-of-the-rich-brooks-era</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Football Week Thirteen Thoughts</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; It's officially rivalry week, where the Civil War and the Battle for Paul Bunyan's Axe is in full effect, along with a slew of other important games, including Michigan-Ohio State, Colorado-Utah and Alabama-Auburn.  If you're not ready for college football this week, then you shouldn't be watching football at all.  Conference champion bids on the line today in an exciting week for college football.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/jim-harbaugh.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Jim Harbaugh&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Jim Harbaugh breaking his headset, and he looks less intimidating with those glasses&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;I have seen both sides of college football rivalries.  On the one hand, Oregon hasn't lost the Civil War since 2007, throughly dominating the Beavers in the process.  But I know what it's like to be the Beavers, as Minnesota hasn't won Paul Bunyan's Axe since 2003, as Wisconsin has clearly dominated the series.  So safe to say, I know both the good and the bad in rivalry games.  Will this be the year the Gophers chop down the goal post with the Axe, something I've never seen before?  Will Oregon maintain its dominance against Oregon State, with this being their last game in an otherwise disappointing season?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Playing against the Big West champion Wisconsin wasn't going to be easy by any means, and Minnesota, time and time again, while playing against competitive teams, start off well enough but lose steam in the second half.  And this is exactly what happened to the Gophers today.  Mitch Leidner looked brilliant in the first half, his best performance of the season, leading the Gophers to a 17-7 lead.  The second half, not so much, as Mitch Leidner ended up throwing four interceptions in a 31-17 loss (again) to Wisconsin.  Pretty much what I expected from Mitch Leidner and the Gophers.  The regular season's over; they finished 8-4, which is exactly what I predicted from them, but the Big Ten West was stronger than expected, which got them in fourth place.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Civil War, this year featuring two losing teams, had nothing but pride on the line.  Oregon came in as the favorite by 3, but on the road against an Oregon State team that can run the ball consistently, Oregon had their hands full with Ryan Nall at the helm, who had his coming out party against the Ducks last year.  And scoring four touchdowns, the Beavers finally beat Oregon in the Civil War.  A perfect ending to a bad season from the Ducks, who I thought would still be a winning team at 9-3, but their defense was far worse than advertised.  Oregon's season is over, and now for the big question, will Mark Helfrich still be the head coach?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Big Game for the playoff hunt was of course, Michigan at Ohio State, and the game matched the hype, as the two teams went back and forth, and for the first time in the series, the game went into overtime.  But Ohio State ended up on top, winning 30-27 in double OT.  But with Ohio State's win, now comes the big question?  Does Ohio State, with just one loss to Penn State, get into the playoffs with Penn State, not Ohio State, winning the Big Ten East by virtue of giving the Buckeyes their only loss?  And if so, does the Big Ten title winner also make it to the Playoffs?  Wisconsin and Penn State are both ranked in the top 8 right now and have only two losses on the year.  Alabama and Clemson are locks to return assuming they win their conference champion, and Washington, should they win the Pac-12 title, would also have only one loss.  I would have to believe at this point that the Big Ten will have two teams.  Washington, unfortunately, didn't play a strong schedule, and that will cost them (assuming they win the Pac-12 title) along with the good old East Coast Bias.  Had they beaten USC, it would be a different story.  This also means Oklahoma is out of the race. That leaves the following teams: Alabama, Ohio State, Clemson, Washington, Wisconsin and Penn State.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/pitt-syracuse.JPG&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Pitt-Syracuse&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Defenses need not apply with Pitt vs. Syracuse&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;    
    &lt;p&gt;As previously suspected, Texas really wanted Charlie Strong fired and they did.  Record aside, he never had a chance to succeed at Texas.  What a shame.  As for the Texas Longhorns, Houston head coach Tom Herman has agreed to take over.  A very logical choice for Texas. --- Speaking of coaching vacancies, Ed Orgeron was promoted as head coach for LSU, absolutely the right decision for LSU.  USC made a mistake choosing Steve Sarkisian over then interim Ed Orgeron, and he's a fighter, which LSU clearly proved after firing Les Miles. --- Pittsburgh and Syracuse had an extreme shoot-out, with Pitt winning 76-61, setting a record for the most points in a game between two teams.  Speaking of Pitt, they've beaten two of the six teams still with a shot at the playoffs, Clemson and Penn State.  --- Navy also reached to 70 point club today, with a 75-31 win over SMU. --- Now that the regular season's over, my pick for the Heisman is still Louisville QB Lamar Jackson, despite Louisville's late season slump; they lost to instate rival Kentucky 41-38.  I can't think of anyone else more deserving.  --- Congrats to Colorado, who went from winning just five games the past three years to winning the Pac-12 South with a 10-2 regular season record.  Remarkable turnaround from a program who really needed it.  Mike MacIntyre deserves to be the national coach of the year for this stunning turnaround.  And they kept USC out of the Pac-12 title game.  A Double Winner in my book. --- With that said, so here are my picks for Top Ten:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alabama&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ohio State&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clemson (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wisconsin (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Washington (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michigan (-3)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Penn State (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Colorado (+2)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oklahoma (-1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oklahoma State (NR)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/11/26/college-football-week-thirteen-thoughts</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/11/26/college-football-week-thirteen-thoughts</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
