<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adam&#39;s Blog</title>
    <description>A blog about whatever is on Adam&#39;s mind.</description>
    <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2016 16:50:45 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2016 16:50:45 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>NBA Draft - The Future is Now</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;4:32 pm - &lt;/strong&gt;Tonight is the 2016 NBA Draft, where the young stars join their new teams.  For my team, the Lakers, with the number 2 pick, hope to pick their next star...just like they did last year with D&#39;Angelo Russell.  While Russell wasn&#39;t an immediate superstar, only time will tell if he lives up to the hype.  Who will the Lakers take with the number 2 picks.  All signs point to Duke forward Brandon Ingram, but the Lakers pick will be announced in 10 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/brandon-ingram.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Brandon Ingram.&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Here&#39;s hoping Brandon Ingram is the next Lakers All-Star&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4:37 pm - &lt;/strong&gt;The first pick is announced, and no surprise, it&#39;s Ben Simmons, the Australian sensation from LSU.  I would have loved for the Lakers to get this kid, has lots of potential, but no surprise he goes to Philadelphia.  Maturity issues aside, this kid has great skills.  With Philadelphia done with its rebuilding project, he can be the anchor for a franchise desperate for some wins.  They deserve some brotherly love, lol.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4:43 pm - &lt;/strong&gt;The Lakers have the second pick, and they take Brandon Ingram, with little surprise.  Ingram is a natural replacement to Kobe with his size and length, along with his shooting and perimeter skills.  Though I think Buddy Hield has potential to be a superstar and would have loved to see him taken by the Lakers, Ingram is the safer pick.  He&#39;s a little skinny, but so was Durant as a young&#39;un.  It&#39;s too early to give up on D&#39;Angelo Russell.  Hearing ESPN take about a fantasy trade of Russell for Okafor is quite ironic.  Most people thought they would take Okafor but took Russell instead.  Equally ironic that Philadelphia is trying to trade him now, and rumbles about Russell with both two having character issues.  Boston has the third pick, a huge steal from Brooklyn from the Pierce-Garnett trade.  They&#39;re trying to get a veteran for the pick.  Now the drama begins.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4:51 pm - &lt;/strong&gt;Danny Ainge is known for trades in the drafts, they have a bright future with Isaiah Thomas at the point guard, a great coach with Brad Stevens and plenty of cap room to make deals.  Kris Dunn, Buddy Hield, Jamal Murray, someone else.  Yep, it&#39;s Jaylen Brown from California.  A surprise to some, but I think Brown has potential to be a star.  Boston doesn&#39;t need a point guard and big men are missing at the top of the draft list.  I suspect Boston will keep him.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4:53 pm - &lt;/strong&gt;Phoenix has the fourth pick, and it&#39;s unknown which direction they will go.  Eric Bledsoe is talented but injury-prone, while they traded the wrong point guard by sending Isaiah Thomas to acquire Brandon Knight.  Random Boston thought, Jaylen Brown was the captain of his chess team in middle school?!?  Wow!  But back to Phoenix, they have decent players but weren&#39;t healthy.  I think Buddy Hield would be great for Phoenix, but Phoenix needs size, so a bigger man might be on the horizon.  Marquese Chriss from Washington, Dragan Bender, the Croatian Man of Mystery?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/dragan-bender.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Dragan Bender.&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Bonus points for playing in Israel, Dragan Bender.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4:58 pm - &lt;/strong&gt;And with the fourth pick, Phoenix selects...Dragan Bender, the Croatian Man of Mystery, who last played for Maccabi Tel Aviv, Israel&#39;s best team.  He&#39;s only 18, so he didn&#39;t play that much according to the ESPN announcers.  Bonus points for playing in Israel.  Will he be the next Kristaps Porzingis (the fourth pick last year) or the next Darko Milicic?  We&#39;ll have to wait and see.  Either way, Minnesota has the fifth pick, and they need a point guard with a shot.  Buddy Hield is realistic, but Providence point guard Kris Dunn is the highest rated point guard in the draft, with defensive capabilities, which is new coach Tom Thibodeau&#39;s calling card.  We&#39;ll find out after the break.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5:06 pm - &lt;/strong&gt;Minnesota&#39;s pick is in, and they select...Kris Dunn, the guard from Providence.  Sorry John Calipari, but Kris Dunn is the perfect choice for Tom Thibodeau.  Whether he becomes a star, who knows, I don&#39;t know much about his game, but Minnesota has a bright future with Andrew Wiggins, Karl-Anthony Towns and Zach Lavine.  Now New Orleans has the sixth pick.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5:09 pm - &lt;/strong&gt;New Orleans needs some guards to complement Anthony Davis.  A disappointing season last year, Davis clearly needs someone else who can perform consistently.  Aaron Gordon, Tyreke Evans and Jrue Holiday have been all inconsistent.  Oh, and Kris Dunn has some shiny shoes courtesy of JC Penneys.  Yippee.  But sad childhood story for Dunn, he deserves credit.  Hope he helps the Timberwolves out.  Back to New Orleans, they need Buddy.  And watching the NBA Reporter Alert on ESPN, it appears that&#39;s the direction they&#39;re going.  Official announcement waiting.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5:13 pm - &lt;/strong&gt;And they took Buddy Hield with the sixth pick.  Great pick for New Orleans, and a perfect fit for them.  I like this kid&#39;s shooting and spunk.  Steph Curry-like potential, clearly the player New Orleans needs to complement Anthony Davis.  And he&#39;s a Senior, so there&#39;s plenty of experience there.  They just compared him to Voshon Lenard, there&#39;s a name I haven&#39;t heard in years.  Gotta love the Bahamas spirit the Buddy Hield brings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/dunn-kris-gucci.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Kris Dunn&#39;s Shoes&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Look at Kris Dunn&#39;s shoes.  Wow!&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5:17 pm - &lt;/strong&gt;Denver has the seventh pick, and they have no direction.  They don&#39;t have a star, a bunch of talented B star players like Kenneth Faried and Danilo Galinari.  They haven&#39;t had a star since they traded Carmelo Anthony (this pick was part of that trade).  The jury&#39;s still out on Emmanuel Mudiay, so Denver can go anywhere with this pick, but appear set on Kentucky&#39;s Jamal Murray (now John Calipari can stop lobbying this kid).  He almost went to Oregon, but ended up at Kentucky with Coach Cal.  Yet Oregon made it to the Elite Eight and was a #1 seed.  But anyways...&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5:21 pm - &lt;/strong&gt;Denver took Jamal Murray, the best rated player left in the draft.  Calipari believes he will lead all rookies in scoring.  We&#39;ll see, but I can&#39;t stand Calipari.  I&#39;ve mentioned him more times than any other coach in this blog.  For Denver, nice pick, but they need direction and a cornerstone.  His comparison, Michael Redd, another player who I haven&#39;t heard about in a long time.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5:23 pm - &lt;/strong&gt;Now we come to the most dysfunctional team in the NBA, the Sacramento Kings.  Anyone who thought George Karl would mesh with DeMarcus Cousins is clearly stupid, as their issues clouded everything with that franchise.  Cousins is the best pure center in the NBA, Sacramento made a mistake firing Michael Malone two years ago.  But David Joerger makes sense as a coach for Cousins.  Rajon Rondo looked decent as their point guard, and they still have Rudy Gay, though he&#39;s likely trade bait.  WIth a nice new simple logo, who should Sacramento take?&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5:26 pm - &lt;/strong&gt;Sacramento takes Marquese Chriss, the power forward from the Washington Fuskies.  He gets the stay in purple, but I don&#39;t know much about him or his game, since Washington is still lagging behind Oregon.  But they&#39;re trading this pick to the Phoenix Suns, who are getting Marquese Chriss and Dragan Bender, according to ESPN&#39;s Andy Katz.  Phoenix has purple too.  First trade of the night!  According to the stats, Marquese Chriss got more fouls than anyone else in the history of the world it seems.  No one ever talks about foul stats.  No wonder I don&#39;t know about him.  I doubt he would&#39;ve done much for Sacramento, and I would be surprised if he becomes anything more than an average player.&lt;/p&gt;
	
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5:31 pm - &lt;/strong&gt;Toronto, fresh off their best season ever, has the ninth pick, courtesy of the New York Knicks via Denver.  If DeMar DeRozan doesn&#39;t bolt, their first priority, Toronto will still contend in the East.  They shockingly beat the Cavs two times in the Eastern Conference Finals.  They select Jakob Poeltl, the University of Utah Austrian sensation.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5:33 pm - &lt;/strong&gt;Jakob Poeltl played well at Utah, but didn&#39;t do much against Oregon in the Pac-12 Conference Championship game.  He was the Pac-12 Player of the Year.  Toronto is a good place for him; they don&#39;t need immediate contributions from &#39;the best Austrian import since the Von Trapp family.&#39;  International player going to Toronto, perfect!  Now the tenth pick, Milwaukee.  Commercial!&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5:40 pm - &lt;/strong&gt;Milwaukee has the tenth pick, another disappointment this year, the Bucks need some shooters but the highest rated players are bigs, and they need rebounding as well.  Steph Curry made more three pointers in 2016 than the entire Milwaukee Bucks team in 2016.  Milwaukee can go anywhere, and they select...Thon Maker, the super mysterious Power Forward from Australia, whose age is in question.  Born in Sudan and escaped at the age of 6, moved to Australia for 8 years, moved to the United States at 14, then moved to Canada.  That&#39;s a mouthful.  A high risk-high reward type of player, with the mystery angle the biggest issue.  The buzz word the analysts said is &#39;unique.&#39;  He definitely appears unique from everything they&#39;ve said about him.  Similar to Giannis Antetokounmpo, the Greek Freak, Thon Maker is technically the only high school player in the draft, albeit a very odd way.  It&#39;s 5:44 pm and I&#39;m hungry for dinner, so now it&#39;s time for hot dogs.  I&#39;ll be back soon…&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;h3&gt;I&#39;m back!&lt;/h3&gt;
	
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7:05 pm - &lt;/strong&gt; I&#39;m back for a rundown of all the things I missed while I was making dinner, eating dinner, doing the dishes, and because it&#39;s trash night, took out the trash.  Here we go:  Orlando took Arvydas Sabonis&#39;s kid Domantas Sabonis with the 11th pick.  If only he was like his Dad in his prime.  Another reminder of what could have been for the Blazers with Arvydas Sabonis.  Even more shocking, Orlando traded him, Victor Oladipo and Ersan Ilyosava to Oklahoma City for Serge Ibaka!  The first major trade of the night.  I always felt OKC needed to trade Ibaka to become truly elite.  They fell just short against Golden State, and whether Kevin Durant comes back or not is the biggest mystery in the NBA period.  But Ibaka, though talented, was expendable for OKC.  He became a jump shooter when he would have been better as an interior player for OKC&#39;s sake.  They traded James Harden just to keep Ibaka...Chicago took Denzel Valentine with the 14th pick.  Nice tough kid from Michigan State who cost me street cred for losing to Middle Tennessee State in the NCAA tournament.  But Chicago is rebuilding, with Derrick Rose being traded to the Knicks...Atlanta took DeAndre Bembry from St. Joseph&#39;s with the 21st pick.  I liked his game when he played against Oregon in the NCAA Tournament, a street-smart player with the best afro since Josh Childress back in 2004 (who was also taken by the Atlanta Hawks).  A surprisingly high number of international players taken, including...Georgios Papagiannis (Greece), Juan Hernangomez (Spain), Guerschon Yabusele (France), Ante Zizic (Croatia), and just taken by Philadelphia with the 24th pick, Timothé Luwawu-Cabarrot (France) - &lt;strong&gt;7:18 pm&lt;/strong&gt;  - I&#39;ve never heard of any of these players, I figured these are the types of players taken in the second round.  If one of those players pans out, I&#39;ll be the first to salute them, guarantee.  Oh, and Furkan Korkmaz (Turkey) with the 26th pick by wait for it...Philadelphia again!&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
			&lt;img src=&quot;/img/deandre-bembry.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;DeAndre Bembry&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
			&lt;h4&gt;Look at DeAndre Bembry&#39;s Afro!&lt;/h4&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7:39 pm - &lt;/strong&gt; Three picks left in the first round, who wants to bet at least one of them will be an International player?  With the last three picks from Phoenix, San Antonio and Golden State, chances are high.  8 (true) International players already in the first round, tying an NBA record, with a chance to be broken.  The draft hosts are talking about college freshman being able to come back to school if they aren&#39;t taken in the first round.  Bad idea, then everyone would enter the NBA Draft, leaving their schools in the balance.  Players should own their decisions of leaving and staying in the draft.  Now we get a Raef LaFrentz reference for Phoenix&#39;s 28th pick, Skal Labissiere from Kentucky.  Ouch!  His family survived the Haiti earthquake, how sad.  And he&#39;s wearing a pink suit too.  Is pink the new black?  The last time the Spurs had a second-to-the-last first round pick, they took Tony Parker.  They always find steals, except Ian Mahmimi.  As for tonight, they selected Dejounte Murray, point guard for the Fuskies.  Seriously?  Oregon made it to the Elite Eight and it&#39;s Washington with two first round picks?  I digress.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
			&lt;img src=&quot;/img/timothe-luwawu-cabarrot.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Timothé Luwawu-Cabarrot&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
			&lt;h4&gt;Pink uniforms?!?  Only a Frenchman can pull it off.  Thanks Timothé Luwawu-Cabarrot!&lt;/h4&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7:51 pm - &lt;/strong&gt; One more pick in the first round, one more chance for a foreign player to be selected to set the record.  And it&#39;s Golden State, who lost the same amount of games in the postseason as they did in the regular season, 9.  All the hard work in the regular season, one win away from winning the championship, and they lost three straight to Cleveland, without an answer to stop superhuman LeBron James and Kyrie Irving.  They threw their chance away like Steph Curry did his mouthguard after fouling out and getting ejected from Game 6 of the Finals.  They acted overconfident and played overconfident.  Cleveland deserved the title and outplayed them.  Brief note, Dejounte Murray&#39;s shoes looked like girls shoes, but it&#39;s to honor a cousin who died last summer.  I&#39;ll give credit for that.  But the final pick of the first round is in, and it&#39;s..................Damian Jones, a center from Vanderbilt.  So much for my International player.  Time for the second round.  And I&#39;m done for the night.  Will Oregon&#39;s Elgin Cook get selected?  Who will the Lakers take in the second round?  Those questions aren&#39;t blog worthy.  Good night!&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Editors Note: The University of Washington&#39;s nickname is purposely misspelled as Fuskies, that was by choice from the old days at Oregon when people would say &quot;Huck the Fuskies.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/basketball/2016/06/23/nba-draft-the-future-is-now</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/basketball/2016/06/23/nba-draft-the-future-is-now</guid>
        
        
        <category>basketball</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Big Short vs. Spotlight - Which Movie was better</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; I was asked to compare two recent movies and Oscar nominated and winning movies from this years Academy Awards.  The challenger on the left is The Big Short, which won Best Adapted Screenplay.  The champion on the right is Spotlight, which won Best Original Screenplay and Best Picture.  So which movie did I think was better?  Here are my thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/oscar.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;The Oscars&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Which movie should have won the Oscar?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Both movies are well done, featuring well known actors and are based on fairly recent events.  The Big Short, starring Steve Carell, Christian Bale, Brad Pitt and Ryan Gosling, is based on the housing crisis that led to the recession, while Spotlight, starring Michael Keaton, Mark Ruffalo and Rachel McAdams, is based on the Boston Globe’s Spotlight team uncovering the mass coverup of child sexual abuse by the numerous Catholic Priests in Boston (and all over the world).  Both have the realistic angle since the events actually happened (I’m not going to argue whether the facts are completely true, but that’s irrelevant at this point.  It’s not The Martian to say the least.  But their approach is quite different.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;One thing I really liked about The Big Short was its light-hearted approach.  Though the drama was there, it showcased some lightly comedic efforts in presenting the film.  With this approach, director Adam McKay, more known for comedy films, is able to reach a different audience for those who strictly like dramas.  In addition, scenes from various celebrities explaining some of the concepts presented in the film, such as CDO’s (consolidated debt organizations) and synthetic CDO’s.  I didn’t particularly know the celebrities that well and some of them seem odd to explain them (i.e. Selena Gomez, who was like 15 when the actual events happened), but it helped the audience better understand what exactly was going on.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Spotlight, on the other hand, takes a more traditional approach of raw emotional storytelling.  Clearly, their story didn’t require that much explanation, so instead, director Tom McCarthy was able to focus on the story and emotions of the characters in the film.  The amount of detail featured in the investigation deserves praise.  Spotlight takes a safer route with its presentation, while The Big Short took a slightly less serious approach.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/the-big-short.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;The Big Short&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;The Big Short&lt;/h4&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;The acting in The Big Short is well done, particularly Christian Bale’s role as Michael Burry, an eccentric hedge fund manager who looks like a slacker yet is able to determine the housing market is crumbling before anyone sees it.  Bale is well known for taking on a variety of roles and his extreme dedication to each role he takes, and his performance showcases this as he perfectly shows the slacker who’s quite intelligent yet dresses like a slob.  Steve Carell and Ryan Gosling also played their characters well, with Carell playing a hedge fund manager with distaste for the industry while Gosling plays a trader that’s cunning, smart and caring at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;The acting in Spotlight is also superb, with Mark Ruffalo and Rachel McAdams deserving the most praise.  Ruffalo plays reporter Michael Rezendes, whose dedication to finding the truth and emotional mission to help the victims makes him stand out, along with McAdams character, who provides a female touch.  The way the reporters handled talking to the victims was particularly touching.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;The one thing that I didn’t care for about The Big Short was its transition from ‘Oh my god, we’re going to get rich off of this!’ to ‘Oh my god, the market has completely crashed, woe is me.’  It kind of seemed too abrupt to me after building the movie up as a ‘heist’ movie.  Overall, the scenes depicting the change were well done but it left me kind of depressed after the movie ended.  The two young characters looked like schmucks with their lack of appreciation for this, until Brad Pitt’s character criticizes them for it.  Done well, but it made some of the characters kind of unlikeable for being greedy.  Spotlight, on the other hand, featured moral characters that weren’t driven by greed, but by the truth.  Michael Keaton’s character, the editor of the Spotlight team, stands out for past digressions (which I won’t reveal for those not wanting spoilers).&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/spotlight.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Spotlight&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Spotlight&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;On the flipside, Spotlight’s plot didn’t particularly stand out.  I’ve seen other newspaper conspiracy type films with better and more interesting; Zodiac, the 2007 film about the Zodiac Killer had a far more interesting plot of the newspaper conspiracy trying to figure out who the Zodiac Killer was.  That to me was a far better and more fascinating film than the uncovering of the Catholic church protecting its pedophile priests.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Despite neither movie being perfect and having its flaws, I found The Big Short to be more interesting and better of the two films.  Working in the mortgage servicing industry, I learned a thing or two about mortgage loans and the housing market in general.  It was a more original approach to give it the light-hearted touch rather than Spotlight, the more conventional film.  Spotlight is still better than the previous Best Picture, Birdman, a movie I found to be odd, but not as good as some of the past Best Picture winners; Slumdog Millionaire (2008), No Country for Old Men (2007), The Departed (2006) and Million Dollar Baby (2004) are four films from this millennium that won Best Picture that I loved.  Great emotional acting is always great to have, but at the end of the day, I’m driven by plot and originality more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/movies/2016/06/19/the-big-short-vs-spotlight</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/movies/2016/06/19/the-big-short-vs-spotlight</guid>
        
        
        <category>movies</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Three Little Words</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; I woke up Sunday morning, as I usually do, looking at my iPhone to check the news.  Like millions of others who woke up today, I was disgusted and saddened to hear that 49 people had been killed in a terrorist attack at an Orlando gay nightclub, Pulse.  Like most, I despise terrorism and hate whenever it occurs.  But stopping terrorism here in the United States and the world requires our nation and our allies to come together.  But instead, we have our Republican congressmen and wannabe congressmen furthering dividing us and claiming defeating Terrorism is as easy as saying three little words...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/orlando.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Stand strong with Orlando.&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Stand strong with Orlando.  That&#39;s what love is all about.  Not words.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Stopping terrorism cannot be defined simply by the words you use to describe it.  So when Donald Trump and his idiot Republican friends suggest that President Obama and Hillary Clinton need to use three little words in order to stop it, it is both ridiculous and counterproductive to believe that the United States and our world powers are going to win the war on terror simply by uttering the phrase &quot;Radical Islamic Terrorist.&quot;  No time in the history of the world has anything been changed simply by uttering a phrase.  It involves actions and cooperation, not divide, to defeat evil.  Obama is aware of this, and doesn&#39;t need to say it just to defeat them&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Terrorism is terrorism, attacks designed to scare and hurt many and all who love.  There are all type of terrorism, and Obama correctly identified the attacks as terror and hate, but the Republicans think that doesn&#39;t do anything.  They claim Obama is soft and doesn&#39;t have a clue about what&#39;s going on, as if the only way to stop these attacks is to utter the phrase &quot;Radical Islamic Terrorist.&quot;  There is no need to use this phrase, and in reality, causes more harm than good, as anti-Islam Republican&#39;s have long been part of the problem, not the solution.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Terrorist groups like ISIS and al-Qaeda claim to be driven by Islam, but all they really want is power.  They merely use the teachings of Islam and pervert them to justify their actions, even though they&#39;re not driven by religion, but rather power.  So to suggest that these terrorist groups are Radical Muslims is in insult to those who preach Islam.  As Muhammad Ali, who recently passed away stated, &quot;True Muslims know the ruthless violence of so-called Islamic Jihadists goes against the very tenets of our religion.&quot;  So using these three little words defeats the whole purpose of stopping terrorist groups like ISIS or al-Qaeda; rather it legitimizes their beliefs that the West is at war with Islam as a whole.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;True Muslims know the ruthless violence of so-called Islamic Jihadists goes against the very tenets of our religion.&lt;footer&gt;Muhammad Ali&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;After the 9/11 attacks, President George W. Bush proclaimed that &quot;we are not at war with Islam,&quot; and this is the way it should be.  But Republicans today, too eager to blame the Muslims for everything and full of hate, are the ones clearly at war with Islam, willing to use them as a scapegoat.  That&#39;s why they insist that we utter three little words to describe them, as if that alone will make a difference in our fight.  It&#39;s no surprise that their words are being used by Terrorists to convince them to join their groups.  To a society that&#39;s more Islamophobic by the day with those who preach Islam being targeted for their religion and being mocked as &#39;terrorists,&#39; the Republicans are making things worse by uttering those three little words and targeting Muslims as a whole, implying a religious war that doesn&#39;t exist.  The effect they have on their constituents is clear in that regard.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;We will never win the war on terror here while Republicans keep dividing us and encouraging hatred against Muslims, or groups that are mistaken for Muslims based on their appearance, i.e. Sikhs, Buddhists.  For every major attack committed by someone who claims support or has actual ties to terrorist groups like ISIS or al-Qaeda, there are hundreds of people here hurling insults at Muslims, attacking them for their appearance and looking at them with disgust.  As Republican&#39;s are largely interested in political power themselves by attracting the white population that hates minorities, Muslims included, it can be said that they are happy with their war on Islam.  That&#39;s why it&#39;s important for them to use three little words.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/orlando2.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Orlando&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Obama criticized Trump for those three little words.  Didn&#39;t stop Terrorism when Obama uttered them.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Terrorism is something we all must stop, and childish name calling is not going to be the difference between winning and losing that battle.  It&#39;s never accomplished anything more than encourage those to continue their fight.  We win our fights with action and collaboration, not through petty words and mudslinging.  So while the Republicans live in a fantasy world where words wins battle, anyone with an actual brain knows how our greatest battles have been actually won.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;When it&#39;s all said and done, leadership, more than anything, is what holds us together and defeats evil.  Instead, we have Republican&#39;s playing the blame game, refusing to accept anything Obama even says as true and criticizing him every chance they have, even over the littlest things.  This lack of leadership and obstructionism is sickening and demeaning to those who have died.  They feign their condolences but clearly are more interested in attacking Obama for his choice of words.  This is not how we get things done.  We accomplish things through actions, not words.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/06/12/three-little-words</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/06/12/three-little-words</guid>
        
        
        <category>politics</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rape - A Nasty Side Effect of Society&#39;s Mistreatment of Women</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Much buzz on the news is about a rapist name Brock Turner, a former Stanford swimmer who raped an unconscious woman and received just six months in prison for it, despite being convicted of three felony sexual assault charges.  Though the defendant claims he understands what he did was wrong, he has managed to show how little responsibility he has actually taken for his crimes, feeling like he is the victim just as much as the woman he raped. Cases like this show just how little regard some men have for women in general and how that, more than anything, leads to rape.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/stanford.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Stanford&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;It can happen anywhere, Stanford University is no exception.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Blame it on the Alcohol. Many young college kids love to drink alcohol, even when they&#39;re not supposed to.  There&#39;s nothing anyone can do to stop that.  But drunken frat parties and binge drinking don&#39;t always led to rape.  Nor does it give anyone a reason to act like it&#39;s the woman&#39;s fault for getting raped because she was drunk and made bad decisions.  No one ever shames the man when he gets drunk and makes bad decisions.  Brock Turner had no problem blaming his actions on the alcohol, as if once you&#39;re drunk, you&#39;re incapable of making a decision.  That is not the truth.  You own your decisions whether you&#39;re drunk or not.  And Brock Turner chose to rape a woman while she was unconscious.  He chose to flee when two men stopped him from his attack.  These are actions of someone who chose to make a horrible decision, not someone who is incapable of making a decision. It&#39;s not the alcohol&#39;s fault.  Surely, there&#39;s something else that contributes to rape by a drunk man.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Blame it on the Culture.  Young college kids are learning to be adults for the first time in their lives.  They often act irresponsibly with frats, sororities and anything that involves partying in general.  But people have a choice to do those things.  I never did in college, and many other people often say no.  Brock Turner felt he had to go after women no matter the cost.  He claims peer pressure made him do it.  But is it worth the so-called peer pressure when you know what you&#39;re doing is wrong.  It&#39;s not culture that leads to rape.  It&#39;s those who make the decision to rape that leads to rape.  After all, party culture does not equal rape culture.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Blame it on the Victim.  Of course, if a woman is flirting and sending you signs that she wants you, you have to say yes no matter what happens.  Brock Turner claims she started it, that she wanted to have sex with him, that is was all consensual.  Problem was, the woman was unconscious.  Nowhere in Brock Turner&#39;s version of events did it mention that the woman was unconscious.  Sure, if a woman suggests sex at that time, you can have sex at the time.  But try asking her if she&#39;s unconscious.  If the answer is not yes, it&#39;s not consensual, end of story.  If a woman says no, it&#39;s not consensual, end of story.  If a woman says nothing, it&#39;s not consensual, end of story.  It&#39;s not the victim that leads to rape. It&#39;s the perpetrator alone who makes that decision.  Otherwise, it&#39;s consensual.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/hero.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Hero&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;This is what a real man looks like, one of the two who stopped a rape in progress.  Showing the rapist&#39;s picture is a waste of time.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;So where does the blame lie?  Misogynistic attitudes towards women is the primary cause.  Men who see women as objects, as if it&#39;s a game to win their heart, without any emotional feelings for their emotions or well being.  These are the types of attitudes that rapists have.  Men like Brock Turner, whom prosecutors argued in court made numerous attempts inappropriately seeking out women, touching them in the wrong places, being way too persistent.  If anyone felt for a woman&#39;s feelings and needs, they would be respectful and leave them alone if said woman was not interested.  Real men treat women with respect, care about their feelings, and wouldn&#39;t have sex with a woman without her consent.  But for men with misogynistic attitudes and masculine superiority, it often becomes all about power and domination over the &#39;lesser&#39; sex, as if it&#39;s all about them.   For many, rape is an aggressive culmination of this type of behavior, and until society figures out how to reverse this type of behavior, it&#39;s never going to stop.  That&#39;s why when these type of people get drunk, their attitude towards women is fully realized, as their inhibition telling them what they&#39;re doing is illegal and wrong goes out the window.  It&#39;s not the alcohol, it&#39;s their attitude unleashed.  Brock Turner didn&#39;t have the slightest bit of respect for that woman, and still doesn&#39;t.  Blaming everyone and everything else but himself doesn&#39;t fix anything.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s wrong for men to believe that women are at fault, or that their feelings don&#39;t matter.  For some, like Brock Turner&#39;s Dad, it&#39;s his son who has to live with all the suffering and embarrassment, not thinking for one second about the victim, or that the fact that his son committed a felony crime by raping an unconscious woman.  What might seem to be &#39;20 minutes&#39; is never forgotten by the victim; they have to live with that forever.  But with people like Dan Turner, a slap on the wrist is all that rapists need because it&#39;s &#39;just one mistake&#39;.  If only the victim got a slap on the wrist.  But she didn&#39;t.  She was raped.  Maybe if he thought about her feelings, he might&#39;ve second guessed the things he said.  Because it&#39;s not &#39;just one mistake,&#39; it&#39;s a crime.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;The legal system is supposed to help the victims.  But sometimes, they turn a blind eye, often times blaming the victim, or assuming felony rape is not worthy of such a long sentence because the perpetrator is supposed to be an outstanding citizen (when he&#39;s clearly not for raping a woman).  The Judge who sentenced Brock Turner to 6 months in prison spent his time talking about not wanting to ruin his life.  It&#39;s not about his life.  It&#39;s not about his future.  It&#39;s about justice for the woman.  The Judge deserves to be fired for his lenient sentence.  It&#39;s as if a felony didn&#39;t happen.  Aren&#39;t felonies supposed to land you at least one year in prison?  Again, had the judge listened to what the woman went through, he would&#39;ve seen things differently, rather than believing the perpetrator was the actual victim.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;The sad truth is that our society bashes women to some level; whether it&#39;s a Presidential candidate calling women fat pigs, dogs, slobs, disgusting animals, bimbos and bleeding out of &#39;you know where,&#39; a judge who ignores a woman&#39;s plea for justice, focusing on protecting the rapist himself, or those who call women sluts every time they have too much to drink and have sex but don&#39;t make such remarks about men.  This problem is much bigger than Brock Turner.  It happens everywhere, college universities, businesses, you name it.  Women need to be heard, to speak up and fight back.  This brave woman let the world know how she felt, and her words are nothing short of powerful and honest.  Having just read what she had to write, all I can say is thank you for standing up and speaking out.  We need more people as brave as her, as heroic as the two men who stopped the rape, and less people like the rapist who pretends to care but blames everyone but himself.  It&#39;s time we stop focusing on the bad people and focus on the good ones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/social/2016/06/09/rape-a-nasty-side-effect-of-societys-mistreatment-of-women</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/social/2016/06/09/rape-a-nasty-side-effect-of-societys-mistreatment-of-women</guid>
        
        
        <category>social</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Muhammad Ali, the Greatest</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; On Friday night, late in the evening, I found out that Muhammad Ali, the legendary boxer, had passed away at the age of 74.  Though I&#39;m not a boxing fan and I don&#39;t know any boxing fans, there was always one boxer that everyone knew about, Mr. Muhammad Ali.  Though some would argue that Mike Tyson is equally famous, he was known for the wrong reasons.  But Muhammad Ali is not only the greatest, as he frequently claimed, but he was the most important athlete of the 20th Century in any sport.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/ali.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Muhammad Ali&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Float like a butterfly, sting like a bee.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was only seventeen years prior in 1947 that Jackie Robinson broke the color barrier in the biggest sport at the time, baseball, becoming an American hero at a time when blacks were still segregated in some parts of the country.  Back then, African-Americans were just starting to participate in professional sports with the white majority.  The Civil Rights act didn&#39;t pass until 1965, so at a time when the African American community needed a powerful voice, in entered Muhammad Ali, who first became popular in 1964 after an upset of Heavyweight Champion of the time, Sonny Liston.  But unlike the African American athletes of the past, Muhammad Ali, then known by his birth name Cassius Clay, was not afraid of anyone.  He said what he felt, and was confident in what he said, the type of swagger that was missing from the African American community in sports at the time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the former Cassius Clay changed his name to Muhammad Ali and converted to Islam shortly after beating Sonny Liston, he did not care what others thought of him, he did what he felt was right for him, and wasn&#39;t afraid to let people know.  He stood up for those afraid to speak out their minds and did so with such an incredible sense of confidence and proudness.  For many, Muhammad Ali was the voice of a community just starting to gain basic rights they previously didn&#39;t have, as the Civil Rights act passed the following year.  Obviously, there were men like Martin Luther King Jr. and Malcolm X, but Ali, being a sports figure, didn&#39;t have to do the things he did, which made his voice different from those whose main objective in life was to fight for African American rights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/ali3.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Muhammad Ali&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Muhammad Ali: The Champ&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Muhammad Ali was the greatest boxer at the time, and still is seen today as the greatest by many; the skill set he displayed pushed him to the top.  But his fearlessness outside the boxing ring made him the legendary figure he is known for today.  With the Vietnam War brewing, Ali was drafted to fight in the war.  But Ali stood his ground, proclaiming he objected to serving, citing his religious beliefs.  He stood up for what he truly believed in, sacrificing everything while fighting charges for draft evasion.  There were plenty of people who despised him for not answering the draft call, claiming him &#39;un-American&#39; for not serving his country when they needed him, but Ali, in his own words, &#39;had no reason to fight the Viet-cong.&#39;  While many athletes, even those today are too afraid to suffer the consequences for standing up to causes, Ali did not flinch, and though he wasn&#39;t able to fight from 1968-1971 as he fought the charges, he did so believing in what he believed in, while losing his championship titles in the process.  Most athletes wouldn&#39;t sacrifice the money lost and reputation suffered for taking a stand but Ali wasn&#39;t afraid of this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ali returned to the ring in 1971, and although he wasn&#39;t as youthful as before, he still had the skill to be the champ, despite the younger blood out to get him.  Though he lost a big fight to Joe Frazier, a boxer whom would become Ali&#39;s biggest rival, people still loved Ali&#39;s attitude and skill, rooting for him to be the champ once again.  He became worldwide known in the process, with two of his biggest fights in his career happening overseas.  First was the &#39;Rumble in the Jungle&#39; against George Foreman in 1975 in what was known as Kinshasa, Zaire.  While there, he embraced the culture of those in the former Zaire, becoming a hero in the process.  He defeated then champion George Foreman in what was considered the biggest fight at the time, as many considered George Foreman the hardest hitting boxer around.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/ali4.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Muhammad Ali&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Ali, Bomaye!  Ali, Bomaye!&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;The other big fight took place the following year in his third and final fight against Joe Frazier, arguably his biggest rival.  Smokin&#39; Joe Frazier beat him the first match, but Ali beat him the second match.  As such, they agreed to fight on more time, in Manila, Philippines, in a fight known as &#39;The Thrilla in Manila.&#39;  Ali, the master trash talker, got into Frazier&#39;s head with his jaunts, and Ali won the match.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Ali was not the same fighter after that, as his age started to show and in part to all the hits he took, began showing signs of Parkinson&#39;s disease, which he was officially diagnosed with in 1984, after his retirement in 1981.  But despite all of this, Ali was still beloved by many and an inspiration to those not willing to speak up.  He fought for his beliefs, had a strong sense of religion without judging others for theirs, and knew exactly how to entertain people.  Many of those who needed a voice got an empowering voice from Ali.  It&#39;s no wonder that he carried the torch for us in the 1996 Olympics in Atlanta; no one else deserved such a higher honor in our Olympics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/ali2.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Muhammad Ali&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;killa and a thrilla and a chilla, when I get that gorilla in Manila.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;In a time where Muslims are often chastised for those who commit acts of terrorism, Muhammad Ali stood up for real Islam, proclaiming the radical terrorists as inauthentic and not true believers of Islam.  Perhaps the most famous Muslim living, Muhammad Ali continued to profess his beliefs in Islam, even as some people attacked Islam and associating Islam with terrorism.  Ali knew better and spoke the truth, unapologetic and unafraid to do so.  So while some people may treat good Muslims bad, there was Ali standing up for the millions of Muslims who needed a strong voice.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;So when I heard Muhammad Ali has passed away, I was sad like many.  He was the greatest boxer, but even more important, the greatest sports humanitarian of his time.  As I&#39;ve seen many times, from 9/11 to the Boston Marathon Bombing, sports, more than anything, can bond people together like nothing else, heal people in a time of need and make people proud of their country.  Muhammad Ali, more than any athlete, embodied that notion, never wavering on his beliefs, speaking up for those who didn&#39;t have a voice while achieving greatness within his sport.  So while other famous athletes like Michael Jordan or Tiger Woods wouldn&#39;t speak up on social issues to preserve their financial and personal reputation, Ali was more than eager to speak his mind when he felt was right.  That, more than anything, made Ali the Greatest.  R.I.P. to a real legend in every sense of the word.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/2016/06/06/muhammad-ali-the-greatest</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/2016/06/06/muhammad-ali-the-greatest</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tech Giants - The Real Viruses</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; On Wednesday, my sister Jenn complained to me that her laptop with Windows 7 automatically updated to Windows 10, without giving her a choice.  It made her angry, she refused to set it up for hours, and after a day of using it, Jenn lost internet access completely.  Not surprisingly, Jenn was pissed by the whole endeavor, in an extremely grumpy mood that not even myself could snap her out of.  Thankfully, Jenn found a way to revert her laptop to Windows 7 thanks to the wonders of instant data via the internet, and getting her Windows 7 back, Jenn was happy again as she should be.  But it&#39;s the principle that matters: Tech companies shouldn&#39;t be allowed to force programs onto your computers.  It goes against the very fiber of the American consumer industry, like a virus out to harm your computer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/microsoft.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Microsoft Screen of Death&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;I call Screen of Death on Microsoft&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;I recently bought a new laptop a few weeks ago running Windows 10, and I enjoy it.  A better OS than Windows 8, which was despised by most people, trying too hard to move to the tablet based technology without weaning people off of the classic laptop/desktop setting of Windows 7.  Windows 10 is a good mix of this.  But despite Microsoft&#39;s intent, they can&#39;t force programs onto a user&#39;s computer.  Some people enjoy Windows 7 and aren&#39;t ready to move on to Windows 10.  People should be able to upgrade as they see fit.  For me, I still use Microsoft Office 97, even though I know Microsoft Office 2010 is better, I just don&#39;t want to pay for it.  And I still use my copy of Adobe Photoshop 7.0 that I received from someone whom I consider to be the worst human being I&#39;ve ever met, but I&#39;m capable of making my own choices.  They still work for me, so why should I fork out money for something new.  Microsoft and Adobe shouldn&#39;t force me without choice to install a program without my input, especially when money is involved.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Plenty of people make programs that have adverse affects on their computers, they call them viruses.  There&#39;s little difference between forcing someone to update to Windows 10 when they&#39;re in the middle of a big project and a virus that steals your information.  No matter who created the software, unwanted software is a virus.  It can have unintended consequences no matter the source of said virus and regardless of the intent.  Yet the tech giants insist that they have the ability to trick people into downloading their unwanted programs, sometimes without the option of saying no.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/apple-music.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Apple Music&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;I&#39;m not going to take a Chance on Apple Music (no pun intended)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Back in 2014, myself and millions upon millions of iTunes users found themselves with songs from a new U2 album, Songs of Innocence, that I neither asked for or knew existed.  Like many of those users, I don&#39;t like U2, never wanted nor never asked for a crappy U2 album.  You wouldn&#39;t want anyone to give you a program you don&#39;t want, why would you want Apple to download an album onto your iTunes without your permission.  Some less tech-savvy people may not be aware of how to remove said programs (or songs) and it&#39;s unfair to the consumer who doesn&#39;t want your crappy program without the option of saying ‘No&#39;.  If I want to buy the crappy U2 album, it&#39;s my choice, not Apple&#39;s.  Just like it&#39;s not my choice, nor anyone&#39;s to have a Trojan horse installed onto my computer.&lt;p&gt;

	&lt;p&gt;So please Microsoft, while we are aware you want everyone to use Windows 10, it&#39;s not realistic that everyone will want it.  People like Windows 7 and their desktops/laptops may be better suitable with it than Windows 10.  This is especially true when in the middle of a big problem.  And to Apple, I wouldn&#39;t listen to U2&#39;s Songs of Innocence album even if Apple put a gun to my head forcing me to listen to it.  I have a right to choose. And while we&#39;re talking about Apple, stop trying to trick people into your Apple Music streaming service.  Streaming music for a fee each month is a stupid idea.  It works with movie streaming like Netflix since movies require a screen to watch, but music can be enjoyed everywhere and people have the right to listen to their music without a valid internet connection.  It&#39;s especially stupid when rappers like Chance the Rapper claim his new mixtape Coloring Book is free but require you to pay a subscription fee each month to listen to it without any other options to listen to it.  #LAME!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/technology/2016/06/03/tech-giants-the-real-viruses</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/technology/2016/06/03/tech-giants-the-real-viruses</guid>
        
        
        <category>technology</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NBA Finals Preview</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; The NBA Finals have arrived, featuring as I expected, a rematch of last year&#39;s Finals, Golden State vs. Cleveland.  Last year, Cleveland, despite missing Kyrie Irving and Kevin Love, played their hardest, gave Golden State a legitimate scare before Golden State was able to win their first championship in 40 years.  Things have changed slightly this year, with the aforementioned Irving and Love healthy this time around, while Golden State, with not much change, finished with an NBA record 73 wins in the regular season.  So who wins the rematch?  Here are my thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/green.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Draymond Green&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Draymond Green, the cog that makes the wheel so special&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Golden State has the same core from last year, but improved their offensive output considerably to a record 73 wins.  Steph Curry and Klay Thompson are capable of hitting a barrage of three pointers at any time, while Draymond Green took the leap from stud to All-Star, a matchup nightmare for any team, Cleveland included.  Golden State is not perfect by any means, needing to overcome a 3-1 deficit to beat Oklahoma City in the Western Conference Finals, but at their best, Golden State is difficult to stop.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Cleveland, on the other hand, has looked unstoppable as of recent, albeit with a weaker group of opponents.  Tyronn Lue, who took over the head coaching position from fired David Blatt, has implemented a more up-tempo game and Cleveland has clearly flourished under this style of play.  Their offensive game somewhat matches Golden State’s with their shooting capabilities.  Mid season acquisition Channing Frye has been hitting threes; his presence may be Cleveland’s wild card.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/lebron.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;LeBron James&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Still the same old LeBron James&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Defensively, Golden State still has last year’s Finals MVP Andre Iguodala to guard LeBron James.  I would imagine Iguodala will start in the Finals since his addition to the starting lineup last year propelled Golden State to the MVP.  Draymond Green was defensive player runner up and will likely guard Kevin Love, whose range likely makes it easier for LeBron and others to attack the rim.  Cleveland on the flip side has LeBron leading the way defensively, while Tristan Thompson will be responsible for cleaning up the boards.  I expect this series will be decided by small ball, rendering Andrew Bogut useless.  Does Timofey Mozgov even play much time anymore?  I’m not sure he even does.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;One thing that could tip the series is Draymond Green’s technical foul watch.  With six already in the postseason, one more will trigger a one-game suspension.  He must try to keep his emotions down, which is not easy for anyone with his tenacious style of play.  He struggled a bit against Oklahoma City, and needs to play his best, as he’s the ultimate X-Factor and arguably the heart of the team, the player that makes Golden State truly out of this world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/thompson.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Klay Thompson&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;If Klay Thompson is hitting his shots, the Warriors will win&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Both teams live by the three and die by the three.  Ultimately, this is what the series will come down to.  Curry and Thompson are the top two shooters in the game right now, finishing 1-2 in the regular season in three-pointers made.  Cleveland has players that can stretch the floor out and hit threes as well, Irving, Love, J.R. Smith and Frye are capable of getting hot from the three-point line.  Whichever team can defensively play the best will ultimately win the NBA Championship.  While Cleveland will give Golden State everything they got, I expect a hard fought series going to the Warriors in Seven Games.  For Finals MVP, I’ll go out on a limb and predict Klay Thompson as Finals MVP.  He saved the Warriors in Game 6 against Oklahoma City and arguably more difficult to stop since Cleveland will focus more on stopping Steph Curry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/basketball/2016/06/02/nba-finals-preview</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/basketball/2016/06/02/nba-finals-preview</guid>
        
        
        <category>basketball</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Steven Adams - A Debate on Whether Exoticness equals Attractiveness</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/steven-adams.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Steven Adams&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;The man with the hair: Steven Adams&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;After watching seven games of the Golden State-Oklahoma City series, I have come to the conclusion that no matter how talented you are, you need a signature look to gain attention from the common-man.  Sure, Kevin Durant is quite talented, he shoots well and is one of the most feared offensive players in the league, but while I was watching this series, it was Steven Adams and his long hair, long mustache and tattoos that got all my attention, as well as an interesting back-and-forth between my Mom, her boyfriend, my sister and I on whether Adams is good-looking or not.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/steven-adams-3.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Steven Adams&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;As a youngster, he looked handsome&lt;/h4&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Naturally, people are drawn to those that look unlike anyone else.  I was always like that growing up; playing one of my favorite games as a youth in Street Fighter, I always choose Blanka and his green-skinned / orange-hair savage-like looks over the conventional karate master Ryu, who seemed bland and boring to me.  I was always drawn to the different looking characters because they were exotic, unique, out of the blue.  And with Steven Adams, there&#39;s definitely something about him that stands out, which otherwise wouldn&#39;t happen if he kept his youthful look when he was first drafted.  But is Steven Adams really attractive, or just exotic?&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/adam-morrison.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Adam Morrison&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Before Steven Adams, there was Adam Morrison.&lt;/h4&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;		
	&lt;p&gt;To some, Steven Adams looks hideous, and though there are some men who look good with long hair, Steven Adams looks unkempt with the beard and mustache when he plays.  I first thought of him looking like (former NBAer) Adam Morrison on crack.  He had the long hair and mustache, but Morrison wasn&#39;t the wild-child that Steven Adams was.  Morrison&#39;s looks were more goofy, while Adam&#39;s looks come off as more fitting.  But playing basketball, it&#39;s not about looking handsome on the court.  Players play hard, they sweat and will do anything to get the ball.  It&#39;s not like being a model on the catwalk.  Would Steven Adams look good on a catwalk as opposed to the hardwood floor?&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/steven-adams-2.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Steven Adams&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Steven Adams looks better in official pictures because he&#39;s supposed to.&lt;/h4&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;		
	&lt;p&gt;His looks personify his performance, so chances are, if Steven Adams wanted to pull that look off on the catwalk, he easily could.  The hair is pulled into a ponytail when he plays, making him look like a warrior of sorts.  But he tends to let his hair loose when he&#39;s on the bench, so he can make the look more attractive when needed.  Not to mention he looks happier taking official pictures than when he&#39;s on the floor trying to win the game for his team.  A nice looking youngster when he first entered the NBA, the look has evolved in the past three years.  It&#39;s that kind of evolution that has some people interested in him and finding him more attractive than your typical player.  For some, who wants to be a typical Steph Curry when you can be wild and crazy looking Steven Adams.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/chris-andersen.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Chris Andersen&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Birdman: A man of a thousand looks...and they all look hideous!&lt;/h4&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;		
	&lt;p&gt;Some players in the NBA, current or former, have looked exotic and unique but aren&#39;t able to pull their look off well.  James Harden, for example, has the beard, which might look passable if not for the equally weird looking hair style.  To me, he looks like a big hairy mess with an unnatural beard, which covers everything past his nose minus the mouth.  Perhaps if he went bald and contained some of his beard near his mouth he would look better, but instead he&#39;s the man with the big bushy beard.  Then you have players who look bad on purpose for the sake of attention, like Dennis Rodman, whose hair dye, piercings and tattoos are well-documented.  Another player known for his appearance is Chris Andersen, a.k.a. Birdman, whose body is covered by tattoos and varying hair styles that make him look like a tattoo model than a basketball player.  These are examples of NBA players whose looks don&#39;t do them well.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/james-harden.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;James Harden&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;The man with the beard...James Harden.  No thanks.&lt;/h4&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;	
	&lt;p&gt;Yet for Steven Adams, his young looks make his evolution more appealing.  Unlike Chris Andersen, who looked unimpressive when he was young before the hair and tattoo explosion, Steven Adams comes off more of an evolution of his New Zealander roots than someone who merely just wants tattoos all over his body.  Dennis Rodman&#39;s looks made no sense other than being a rebel who wanted to look different, nor did Chris Andersen&#39;s, and James Harden&#39;s looks doesn&#39;t fit his style of play.  But while Steven Adams is not as handsome as Tony Parker, Adams is able to make it work through his roots and playing style.  Adams plays like his looks, and that to me is part of his mystique.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;In all, I would say that exotic looks have the ability to be considered attractive, if done correctly.  It doesn&#39;t necessarily apply to all athletes in the NBA, or in sports in general, but in the case of Steven Adams, it&#39;s no wonder why there&#39;s even a debate on whether he looks good or not.  The simplest test is whether a kid can pull it off, and as in the case of Oklahoma City&#39;s youngest viral fan, Lil&#39; Stache Bro, the answer is hell yeah.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-6&quot;&gt;
		&lt;blockquote class=&quot;instagram-media&quot; data-instgrm-captioned=&quot;&quot; data-instgrm-version=&quot;7&quot; style=&quot; background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:658px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);&quot;&gt;&lt;div style=&quot;padding:8px;&quot;&gt; &lt;div style=&quot; background:#F8F8F8; line-height:0; margin-top:40px; padding:50.0% 0; text-align:center; width:100%;&quot;&gt; &lt;div style=&quot; background:url(data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAACwAAAAsCAMAAAApWqozAAAABGdBTUEAALGPC/xhBQAAAAFzUkdCAK7OHOkAAAAMUExURczMzPf399fX1+bm5mzY9AMAAADiSURBVDjLvZXbEsMgCES5/P8/t9FuRVCRmU73JWlzosgSIIZURCjo/ad+EQJJB4Hv8BFt+IDpQoCx1wjOSBFhh2XssxEIYn3ulI/6MNReE07UIWJEv8UEOWDS88LY97kqyTliJKKtuYBbruAyVh5wOHiXmpi5we58Ek028czwyuQdLKPG1Bkb4NnM+VeAnfHqn1k4+GPT6uGQcvu2h2OVuIf/gWUFyy8OWEpdyZSa3aVCqpVoVvzZZ2VTnn2wU8qzVjDDetO90GSy9mVLqtgYSy231MxrY6I2gGqjrTY0L8fxCxfCBbhWrsYYAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC); display:block; height:44px; margin:0 auto -44px; position:relative; top:-22px; width:44px;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;p style=&quot; margin:8px 0 0 0; padding:0 4px;&quot;&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/p/BFzwDdiCqG4/&quot; style=&quot; color:#000; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none; word-wrap:break-word;&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lil Stache Bro in Thunder Alley.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p style=&quot; color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;&quot;&gt;A photo posted by Oklahoma City Thunder (@okcthunder) on &lt;time style=&quot; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px;&quot; datetime=&quot;2016-05-24T23:34:23+00:00&quot;&gt;May 24, 2016 at 4:34pm PDT&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
	&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; defer=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.instagram.com/en_US/embeds.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-6&quot;&gt;
		&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
			&lt;img src=&quot;/img/jason.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Jason&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
			&lt;h4&gt;Meet my Mom&#39;s Boyfriend&#39;s son Jason.  If a little kid can pull off the look, so can Jason.  I just wanted to show this picture off.&lt;/h4&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/basketball/2016/05/30/steven-adams-a-debate-on-whether-exoticness-equals-attractiveness</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/basketball/2016/05/30/steven-adams-a-debate-on-whether-exoticness-equals-attractiveness</guid>
        
        
        <category>basketball</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>When Keeping it Real Goes Wrong - The Social Media Edition</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Anyone who used to watch Chappelle&#39;s Show back in the day surely remembers the skit, &#39;When Keeping it Real Goes Wrong,&#39; as Dave Chappelle&#39;s comically showed skits of so-called thugs and gangstas in instances when it&#39;s not the best idea to &#39;keep it real.&#39;  But that was 2003, now in the days of social media, viral videos and tweets, it often shows that way too many people &#39;keep it real&#39; when they shouldn&#39;t.  A sad but unfortunate side effect of stupidity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/troy.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Troy Ave&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Troy Ave may think it&#39;s fine to keep it real&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Case in point, the recent shooting at New York&#39;s Irving Plaza before a T.I. show, where Brooklyn rapper Troy Ave, a gangsta rapper who leads the BSB crew, got into a seemingly random argument with allegedly another crew.  A street smart rapper would find a better time to take revenge, definitely not in a public place.  Instead, Troy Ave, losing his cool and keeping it real, started firing shots.  Even worse, he was caught on camera firing shots, a definite no-no for someone who, like a lot of criminals, can&#39;t legally own a gun.  Now everyone who knows what he looks like can watch the grainy video seeing Troy Ave looking for someone, firing shots and leaving the view.  And the worst of it all, Troy Ave&#39;s bodyguard, Banga, was the only fatality.  So while Troy Ave, seemingly on his way to the top, finds himself charged with Attempted Murder, Reckless Endangerment and Criminal Possession of a Weapon, and a fresh wound in the leg for shooting himself.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/troyaveshooting.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Shooting&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;But it can take just seconds to pull up this image of the shooting.&lt;/h4&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;This might have not been a big deal in 2003, but now, it can only take seconds for someone to screw up and have everyone find out.  Troy Ave, whose album Major Without A Deal sold a lousy 2,000 copies in his first week, must&#39;ve thought that street cred is the way to fame, but many rappers have been able to maintain their street cred without acting callously on camera.  So while people now know his name more than before, keeping it real likely has him locked him up behind bars for what fame he has gained.&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;p&gt;But you don&#39;t have to commit violent crimes to &#39;keep it real.&#39;  Just ask Azealia Banks, a female rapper who instead of making music (allegedly her contract won&#39;t let her), makes her rounds by constantly arguing with other rappers, celebrities and all of mankind on Twitter.  Some may think it&#39;s cool to talk trash about others, but there&#39;s a big difference between personal conversations and social media posts, which even deleted within seconds, will last a lifetime.  Azealia Banks, thinking it&#39;s cool to talk trash about others with foul language, has managed to offend almost everyone by &#39;keeping it real.&#39;  Yet strongly homophobic comments about singer Zayn Malik and twitter attacks on 14 year old actress Skai Jackson led to people standing up to her, as Azealia Banks was banned from Twitter for engaging in such foul and harsh language.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;And yet people would constantly mouth off and say the wrong thing back in the days.  But with social media out there, it&#39;s easier to know when people are saying stupid shit.  It&#39;s easier for people to show off and try to &#39;keep it real,&#39; as if they&#39;ll get more fans from it, but has Azealia Banks really accomplished anything?  I still don&#39;t know one song of hers, so whenever I hear about her, it&#39;s for the wrong reasons and not what she&#39;s supposed to be doing with her life.  So has &#39;keeping it real&#39; lead to any album sales?  Not really.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/azealia.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Azealia Banks&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Most people who know Azealia Banks associate her with bad Twitter behavior.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Plenty of people love to keep it real, even with a stunning lack of consequences for doing so.  It&#39;s as if people are totally forgetting about the consequences of their actions.  With social media a constant in our lives now, people are able to keep it real for the whole world to see, even if they don&#39;t intend everyone to see it.  Living in a world where anything that&#39;s shot on camera will make its way to the internet within hours or any tweet you make, no matter how much you regret it, will never go away.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/technology/2016/05/27/when-keeping-it-real-goes-wrong</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/technology/2016/05/27/when-keeping-it-real-goes-wrong</guid>
        
        
        <category>technology</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NBA Conference Finals Preview</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; As the Toronto Raptors defeated the Miami Heat in seven games, the Western and Eastern Conference Finals are now set.  It’s been a crazy ride so far, with surprise endings in some cases, but with four teams left to win the NBA Championship, who will win it all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/lowry.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Kyle Lowry&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;It wasn’t pretty, but Kyle Lowry led Toronto to their first Eastern Conference Finals.  Tough challenges await.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;It’s no surprise that the Golden State Warriors made it back to the Western Conference Finals, but their ride there has been nothing short of expected.  With Steph Curry a little banged up, missing four games, it seemed like Golden State would get challenged by the surprise Portland Trail Blazers.  And for the most part, they were tested, but with each test, Golden State proved to be just a little better, and with Steph Curry returning in Game 4, he saved his best in a thriller, scoring the majority of his points in the second half and overtime after a cold start.  In typical Steph Curry fashion, he put on a show, and while becoming the NBA’s first unanimous MVP ever, proved just how insane his game truly is.  Though Portland played great, the Golden State Warriors showed how elite they are, winning the series 4-1.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Most people, myself included, expected a Golden State-San Antonio matchup.  The Spurs played great during the season, and if not for the Warriors historic success, would have had the best record in the league.  But the Oklahoma City Thunder showed just how dangerous their duo of Kevin Durant and Russell Westbrook (or should it be Russell Westbrook and Kevin Durant) truly are, surprising the Spurs in a well fought series, winning 4-2.  With Russell Westbrook being perhaps the most underrated player in the NBA (someone I think compares favorably to Curry himself and arguably has a better all-around game but people considered not on that level), it’s no wonder the Spurs simply could not stop him, while Kevin Durant played his typical high scoring game.  But it was their defense, with the vastly underrated play of Steven Adams that really pushed them to the next level.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/westbrook.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Russell Westbrook&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Russell Westbrook’s style of play makes him impossible to defend...&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;The Eastern Conference, meanwhile, saw Cleveland easily sweeping the Atlanta Hawks behind some of the most insane three-point shooting outside of Golden State, where the Cavs made 25 threes in one game, a truly mind boggling performance.  Though the Eastern Conference improved from last year, it’s still not as strong as the West, as LeBron James and company are still clearly the best team in the East, sweeping both Detroit and Atlanta.  They’re playing their best ball by far right now, but whether they can beat Golden State or Oklahoma City remains to be seen.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/curry2.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Steph Curry&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;But Steph Curry’s game is even harder to stop.  An elite duel awaits!&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the flipside is the Toronto Raptors, making it to the Eastern Conference Finals for the first time.  They didn’t dominate by any means, losing both Game 1’s at home, but they fought, scratched and clawed their way past Indiana and Miami, with both series going to Game 7.  And though Kyle Lowry and DeMar DeRozan struggled at times, they came up big when their team needed it most, especially Lowry, who remains the heart and soul of the Raptors club.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Eastern Conference Finals looks lopsided to me.  I would be surprised if Toronto won more than one game, and would totally expect Cleveland to pull another sweep.  Perhaps Toronto can pull off the Game 1 upset due to Cleveland’s rust from all the time off, but Cleveland is leaps and bounds above Toronto.  Lowry will keep them close in at least one of their home games, but not enough consistency from DeRozan spells trouble for Toronto.  Miami would have had a better shot of winning against Cleveland, but injuries to Hassan Whiteside (not to mention Chris Bosh not available for the series) killed an otherwise outstanding performance from Dwyane Wade, keeping them from advancing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/lebron.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;LeBron James&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;No matter how much you may dislike LeBron James, you know you simply can’t stop him.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Western Conference Finals on paper looks like a better matchup, as a series with Curry, Westbrook, Durant, Klay Thompson and Draymond Green bring plenty of star power.  But while Westbrook and Durant will be hard to stop, the Warriors are on another level with Curry on the court.  There’s not a player like him, and though his shooting is mind-boggling and his offensive game his beyond crazy, it’s his supporting cast that makes them historically great, mainly the play of the impossible-to-defend Draymond Green, whose all-around game gives opponents headaches.  Oklahoma City will put up a good fight like Portland, but Golden State will find its way to victory.  I project Golden State to win the series in 5 games.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A potential repeat of last years Finals would be historically great, just like last year’s series was.  Cleveland played their hearts out last year without Kyrie Irving and Kevin Love.  The way they are playing right now, Cleveland shouldn’t be taken lightly, and they definitely have peaked at the right time.  But the Western Conference is a different beast, and Steph Curry and the Warriors are setting the tone for a new era in the NBA.  It won’t be easy for the Warriors, as long as LeBron is around, but in the end, the Warriors are my choice to cap off their historic season winning the NBA title again.  No one saw this coming five years ago, but Golden State has put together an impossible-to-beat roster without a dominating big man, something only Michael Jordan’s Bulls could pull off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The craziest season perhaps in NBA history is coming to an end, and with an even crazier summer coming, I expect to see some of the most exciting basketball to be played out in the coming weeks.  Still, the NBA Lottery on Tuesday will mean the most personally to me.  Can the Lakers win the lottery?  Will they even get a top pick?  Stay tuned, it’s going to be one heck of a show&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/booker.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Devin Booker&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Only my sis would think of Booger.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;NBA Lottery Notes - May 17, 2016&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a Laker fan, I can rejoice, they get to keep their pick, that is the good news.  Of course, the Lakers finish Number 2 again, except this year that was were they were supposed to be.  The winner of the lottery: the god-awful Philadelphia 76ers, the worst team in the league.  At least the Lakers didn&#39;t have to give them their pick.  The highlight of the night...my sister thought the Phoenix Suns representive at the Lottery had a last name of Booger.  Here&#39;s to you Devin Booker...or should I say, Devin Booger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/basketball/2016/05/15/nba-conference-finals-preview</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/basketball/2016/05/15/nba-conference-finals-preview</guid>
        
        
        <category>basketball</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
