<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adam's Blog</title>
    <description>A blog about whatever is on Adam's mind.</description>
    <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2016 08:08:14 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2016 08:08:14 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Football Week Eight Thoughts</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Week Eight is unofficially Homecoming Week.  For Minnesota, it's their official Homecoming game against Rutgers, their first matchup ever.  For Oregon, it's a painful reminder of how far they've truly fallen against another high powered offensive team in Cal.  That game was played yesterday.  As we reach Week 8, a closer picture starts for determining the four playoff teams.  I'll talk more about that later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/northwestern.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Northwestern&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;It's crazy every one-handed grab will be compared to OBJ.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Oregon faced off against Cal on Friday night mired in a losing streak.  Unfortunately, their defense still sucks tremendously.  On the plus side, Justin Herbert looks legit, bring the Ducks back from a 20 point deficit to force overtime, throwing for six touchdowns.  But his one interception sealed the game in double OT, as Cal won a wild-west shootout 52-49.  Now the Ducks are on their longest losing streak since 1996.  How times have changed.  The Ducks were mired in mediocrity before that yet Rich Brooks remained the coach for 17 years, building a legacy.  But that legacy may have reached its end, as the Ducks are now a different team and have bigger goals in mind.  Mark Helfrich, as good as a man he is, probably needs a miracle to keep his job.  The rest of the Ducks schedule looks daunting: Arizona State, USC, Stanford, Utah and Oregon State, all teams that can run the ball quite well.  Something Oregon clearly can't stop.  Chances are, should Helfrich be fired, they will look outside for a coach.  Perhaps Chip Kelly would come back, as his NFL career has predictably turned out to be disappointing, and his 49ers look terrible.  But we'll see what happens there.  Until then, Duck fans everywhere should start counting down to basketball season.  At least the basketball team looks strong and can play defense.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Minnesota, meanwhile, played its first game against Rutgers.  The good news for them is that Mitch Leidner returned after suffering a concussion two weeks ago against Iowa.  A surprise as he was declared out just two days ago.  Even better news, Rutgers is just plain awful.  The worst team in the Big Ten and probably the worst team of all the major conference teams.  Unfortunately for Minnesota, after a great game in Maryland, their performance against Rutgers was a letdown.  Although they won 34-32, Minnesota needed a last second field goal to win a game that they should've easily won.  They were favored by 17 points and jumped to a 21-3 lead, but Rutgers, who entered the game with just 14 points in the season against Big Ten foes, scored 32 and took the lead late in the fourth quarter.  Again, it was Mitch Leidner and the passing game that struggled.  They'll need to play better next week when they visit Illinois.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;As the playoff race begins, we have a clear top team: Alabama.  They look pretty unstoppable at this point, and appear to be a lock to defend their title.  But anything can happen, as Ohio State was shocked by Penn State, who came back from a 21-7 decifit to win 24-21.  Ohio State is still in the playoff hunt, as a matchup with Michigan still looms with the Big Ten East (and a trip to the Big Ten title game) on the line.  The Big XII needs a miracle to get back in the playoffs, as the only unbeatens team left in the conference are Baylor, currently ranked 9th, and West Virginia, whose currently ranked 12th.  The chances of them running the table are low, so most likely, the Big XII is out.  Washington has a good shot of finishing unbeaten, and is the only Pac-12 team that can bring the conference back after missing the playoffs last season.  The ACC is a bit of a scramble between Clemson and Louisville.  Clemson beat Lousiville in a close matchup, but they still have to face Florida State, who can play spoiler and create a three-way tie between the three, all in the same division of the ACC.  If either Clemson or Washington lose a game, that would open up a spot for both Michigan and Ohio State.  At this point, the following teams are still alive: Alabama, Ohio State, Michigan, Clemson, Texas A&amp;amp;M, Louisville, Nebraska, Baylor, West Virginia, and Florida.  At the end of the day, anything can happen between now and December.  After all, the Chicago Cubs clinched their first World Series appearance since 1945 and are four wins away from their first title since 1908.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Northwestern continues to be the most confusing team in the country.  They lost to Western Michigan, though they are undefeated, so that's a plus for them, and even worse, lost to Illinois State.  But they have rebounded, beating Iowa among other teams.  And much credit to Safety Kyle Queiro, who completed an OBJ like one-handed interception. --- Congrats to the Colorado Buffaloes, who have now won six games this year and clinched a bowl berth.  They could win the Pac-12 South with the talent they have.  Unfortunately, Oregon has replaced them in the gutter for the time being.  Not only did Washington beat both Oregon and Stanford (convincingly), Colorado has as well.  Mike McIntyre definitely belongs in the running for Coach of the Year. --- Utah running back Joseph Williams rushed for 332 yards against UCLA today.  Combined with Arizona State running back Kalen Ballage's seven rushing touchdown (eight overall) against Texas Tech earlier in the season equals two reasons Oregon is not going to get better any time soon.  Yikes!--- The Heisman race this year is Louisville QB Lamar Jackson's to lose.  He struck the Heisman pose today against NC State.  --- Oklahoma and Texas Tech combined for 1,708 yards, setting a new record.  That's a lot of yards.  Seven records were broken in that game. --- With that said, so here are my picks for Top Ten:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alabama&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michigan (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clemson (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Washington (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ohio State (-3)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Louisville&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nebraska (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wisconsin (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Baylor (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Texas A&amp;amp;M (-3)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/10/22/college-football-week-eight-thoughts</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/10/22/college-football-week-eight-thoughts</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Football Week Seven Thoughts</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Week Seven for me is Strange Week.  The Minnesota Golden Gophers make their way to Maryland to play them for the first time since they joined the Big Ten in 2014.  I'm still not used to them and Rutgers being part of the Big Ten.  Maryland should've remained in the ACC and Rutgers looks like complete crap.  Market aside, the Big Ten should've stopped with Nebraska.  But nonetheless, it's the game against the Terrapins.  As for the Ducks, they stand to have their best defensive performance of the season, as they have the week off.  As for the rest of the week, it seems kind of bland, with the exception of Alabama-Tennessee and Ohio State-Wisconsin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/rodney-smith.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Rodney Smith&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Rodney Smith led the way to a win against Maryland&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;The Gophers faced off against Maryland with their first glimpse into the future.  Mitch Leidner was out with a concussion, so backup QB Conor Rhoda gets his first start.  He's a junior so we'll see who the starter is next season, but here's hoping Mitch Leidner will be back for next weeks game, not that they need him against god-awful Rutgers.  As long as they have the Rodney Smith-Shannon Brooks combo at Running Back, Minnesota will be just fine.  And that was true for the Gophers first Big Ten matchup against Maryland.  Their defense shut down Maryland's offense, holding them scoreless through three quarters, and the Gophers mostly kept it on the ground, with their dynamic duo that they've missed since the great Marion Barber III-Laurence Maroney days.  Their defense forced four turnovers against Maryland, including a pick-six by Antoine Winfield Jr. to seal the game.  Minnesota got the win they really needed, 31-10.  Next up, their homecoming game against god-awful Rutgers.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;This week wasn't particularly interesting, and honestly, I wasn't really paying that much attention to it. I had other things to do. --- Tennessee got their butts wooped by Alabama, no surprise there. --- Ohio State beat Wisconsin in overtime.  So much for Wisconsin having a down year, although their wins against LSU and Michigan State look far less impressive than they did at the time.  LSU fired Les Miles and Michigan State is 2-4. --- Clemson barely survived against NC State, as NC State missed a field goal that would've won the game at the end of the fourth quarter.  --- Oregon plays Cal next Friday at Cal.  They'll probably give up a touchdown before the game starts. ---  That's all I got for now, so here are my picks for Top Ten:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alabama&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ohio State&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michigan (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clemson (-1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Washington (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Louisville (-1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Texas A&amp;amp;M&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nebraska (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wisconsin (-1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Baylor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/10/15/college-football-week-seven-thoughts</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/10/15/college-football-week-seven-thoughts</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why I Should Be The Next Starting Quarterback of the Cleveland Browns</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Tim Couch, Ty Detmer, Doug Pederson, Spergon Wynn, Kelly Holcomb, Jeff Garcia, Luke McCown, Trent Dilfer, Charlie Frye, Derek Anderson, Brady Quinn, Ken Dorsey, Bruce Gradkowski, Colt McCoy, Jake Delhomme, Seneca Wallace, Brandon Weeden, Thad Lewis, Jason Campbell, Brian Hoyer, Johnny Manziel, Connor Shaw, Josh McCown, Austin Davis, Robert Griffin III and Cody Kessler.	A list this long would be perfect to describe a proud NFL franchise's Hall of Famers, but no, this is the list of starting quarterbacks for the Cleveland Browns since their franchise was reborn in 1998.  Clearly, the Cleveland Browns are cursed with Quarterbacks.  They're looking for the wrong qualities. Here are the reasons I should be the next starting quarterback of the Cleveland Browns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/browns.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Cleveland Browns&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;This could be your future, Dawg Pound&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;It's true, I'm thirty one years old and have never played football on any level, much less the quarterback position, but the Cleveland Browns should know that the following qualities surpass anyone on the above list.  For starters, I have never thrown an interception in my life, much less thrown an incomplete pass.  Also to note is that the offensive line doesn't have to worry about me getting sacked since I've never been sacked before either.  I'm also proud to say I've never suffered a football injury in my life.  I fractured my wrist in the eighth grade, but that was in my non-throwing arm.  Other than that, I've enjoyed a pain free career and that's something the Cleveland Browns have been lacking.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Cleveland Browns have clearly been terrible at drafting quarterbacks.  All of their first round selections have been complete failures, from their first pick ever, Tim Couch, to the complete and utter disaster known as Johnny Manziel.  They've passed up plenty of quality quarterbacks, including Russell Wilson, Aaron Rodgers, and of course, Tom Brady.  That's why they shouldn't draft a quarterback at all and settle for an unknown quality free agent like myself.  No more bad draft choices.  No more overpaying for quarterbacks past their prime.  No more old veterans at the end of their career.  Just pick me instead; I'm on a different level.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Let's also realize another sad fact, no one wants to be the Cleveland Browns quarterback unless they get overpaid.  I, on the other hand, would be willing to take the minimum so Cleveland can use the other money to better build a team.  They have a good offensive-minded coach in Hue Jackson, now they just need to bring in some better players to surround their quarterback stud.  Cleveland needs to take that jump and not spend too much money for less quality.  Cleveland is cursed for a reason, and there's only one person that could save the Cleveland Browns: LeBron James.  But until he has the time to play football as well as basketball, they will need to take a chance on someone else.  That's why I should become the next starting Quarterback of the Cleveland Browns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/10/10/why-i-should-be-the-next-starting-quarterback-of-the-cleveland-browns</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/10/10/why-i-should-be-the-next-starting-quarterback-of-the-cleveland-browns</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>So He Finally Used the A-Word</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; It took sixteen months, but the Idiot finally used the A-word he never likes to use: &lt;strong&gt;APOLOGIZE&lt;/strong&gt;.  What did it take for him to apologize?  A video mic drop recording of him saying some incredibly vulgar things about women, essentially bragging about hitting on a married woman and getting away with groping women because he’s a star.  He called it 'locker room banter,' I call it 'words a sexual predator would say.'  Now that he's used the A-word, he can now apologize to everyone he’s offended in his life.  Here's an partial list of everyone owed an apology.  He's offended so many people it's hard to keep track.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/stupid-idiot.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Stupid Trump&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Once an Idiot...Always an Idiot&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Barack Obama --- Michelle Obama --- Malia and Sasha Obama --- Hillary Clinton --- Bill Clinton --- Ted Cruz --- John Kasich --- Jeb Bush --- Marco Rubio --- Rand Paul --- Tim Kaine --- Chelsea Clinton --- Carly Fiorina --- John Kerry --- Joe Biden --- Rosie O'Donnell --- Megyn Kelly --- Alicia Machado --- Khizr Khan --- Ghazala Khan --- John McCain --- Serge Kovaleski --- The Central Park Five --- Paul Ryan --- Jeff Flake --- Nancy O'Dell --- Billy Bush --- George W. Bush --- Kareem Abdul-Jabbar --- Mark Cuban --- Every Hispanic in America --- Every Muslim in the world not part of a terrorist group --- The Reagan Family --- Angela Merkel --- Mitt Romney --- Heidi Cruz --- Rafael Cruz --- Ivanka Trump --- Rev. Faith Green Timmons --- South Korea --- Japan --- China --- United Kingdom --- David Cameron --- Sadiq Khan --- Harry Reid --- Elizabeth Warren --- Michael Bloomberg --- Bill de Blasio --- Everyone that got attacked at his rallies by his supporters --- Anthony Weiner --- Robert DeNiro --- Ivana Trump --- The Media --- Mexico --- Bernie Sanders --- Vincente Fox --- Everyone affected by his Bankruptcies --- Every contractor he stifled money out of --- Every African American he refused to rent property to --- Black Lives Matter --- All African Americans in General --- Gonzalo P. Curiel --- Eric Schniederman --- Lindsey Graham --- Pope Francis --- All Victims of PTSD --- Samuel L. Jackson --- Cher --- Mac Miller --- Syed Farook's family --- Everyone living in Jersey City, New Jersey --- General John Allen --- All Syrian Refugees --- The Republican Party --- The Democratic Party --- The United States of America&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Thank you and have a good day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/10/08/so-he-finally-used-the-a-word</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/10/08/so-he-finally-used-the-a-word</guid>
        
        
        <category>politics</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Football Week Six Thoughts</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Week Six for me is Rivalry Week Part 1.  Minnesota hosted Iowa for the Floyd of Rosedale and Oregon hosted Washington, winning twelve in a row against them but looking far worse now than they have at ay time in those twelve years.  As for the the rest of the games, another entertaining variety of match-ups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/floyd-of-rosedale.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Floyd of Rosedale&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;My proudest moment watching the Gophers at the Metrodome, carrying off Floyd of Rosedale&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;I went to four games while I was at the University of Minnesota, and the last game against Iowa was the best game of the bunch.  They beat a rival and won a trophy.  So it went without saying that Minnesota really needed a win against Iowa, to prove their legitimacy as possible Big Ten contenders.  Unfortunately, while their defense looked strong, their offense sputtered and could only muster up 7 points, losing to Iowa 14-7 after an Iowa touchdown late in the fourth quarter put them up ahead for good.  While Minnesota has the running backs, they still lack consistency in the passing game.  A tough loss to swallow, but Iowa's defense is just as good, a good old classic Big Ten Slugfest.  Next week for Minnesota: a road trip to Maryland, Minnesota's first game against Maryland since they joined the Big Ten.  The last (and only) time they've met was in 1977.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float:left&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/img/justin-herbert.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Justin Herbert&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;h4&gt;Webfoots, Ducks, whatever you want to call them, they can't defend.&lt;/h4&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The last time Oregon lost to Washington, I was a freshman at the U of O.  I remember watching the game on TV.  Hard to believe Oregon would end up winning the next twelve games.  But this year, Washington enters the game ranked #5 and statistically with the best defense in the country.  Oregon, on the other hand, couldn't stop a chair from scoring.  Wearing their Webfoots jerseys to honor the ancient days, Oregon made a surprising change at Quarterback starting true freshman Justin Herbert.  For the first time in a long time, Oregon looked completely overmatched and likely to get blown out.  And they were blown out, just as everyone figured, final score 70-21.  And just like that, the streak is over.  Oregon gets a much needed week off, but it doesn't look any easier as they face Davis Webb and the high-flying Cal offense.  It's not going to get any easier for the Ducks and with their defense as horrific as it's looked, this will not turn out well.  This may be the beginning of the end for Mark Helfrich.  I questioned how effective he'd be without Marcus Mariota leading the way and it hasn't been particularly pretty at times.  Oregon fans will be pissed, and should be.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
    		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/notre-dame-nc-state.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Notre Dame vs NC State&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
    		&lt;h4&gt;Thoughts to those affected by Hurricane Matthew, even in Raleigh the rain looks horrific.&lt;/h4&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;It's tough to finish a season undefeated, no matter what conference you play in.  Houston, having beaten (a now overrated) Oklahoma at home, lost to high-scoring Navy 46-40.  Their slim chance to make the Playoffs unfortunately is over.  But they can still make a Big Five bowl game. --- Tennessee might be the most entertaining team in the country.  Every game they've played in this season has seen them make a big comeback, and against Texas A&amp;amp;M they came back from a 28-7 deficit.  Volunteers never say die.  But desite the comeback and leading the game into OT, Texas A&amp;amp;M won 45-38.  Gotta give the Vols credit for fighting back.  --- Who would've thought that when Colorado played USC, that the one ranked team would actually be Colorado.  But USC ended up winning 21-17.  What a shame.  --- Hurricane Matthew had a big impact on some of the games in that area.  It postponed LSU-Florida (which neither team has a shared open game to reschedule it, stay turned), and drenched games in the Carolinas.  I saw the rain on a clip of the Notre Dame-NC State game, it looked nasty.  --- Another nasty hit on Penn State kicker Joey Julius.  I didn't realize he had an eating problem.  For that, I apologize for my previous caption on him.  --- Michigan beat Rutgers 78-0.  Rutgers lost to Ohio State 58-0 last week.  Why are they in the Big Ten again? --- Miami fans started throwing litter all over the field after a penalty call went against them.  Only Miami, right?  ---  With that said, here are my picks for Top Ten:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alabama&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ohio State&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clemson(+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michigan (-1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Louisville&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Washington (+2)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Texas A&amp;amp;M&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wisconsin (NR)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nebraska (NR)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Baylor (NR)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/10/08/college-football-week-six-thoughts</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/10/08/college-football-week-six-thoughts</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sorry Norf Norf Lady</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Recently, I read about a viral video of a Christian woman, a mother of four, who blogged her video reaction upon listening to a rap song she heard on the radio, rapping the song line by line and getting upset over the lyrics.  The song in question, Norf Norf, by Vince Staples, is a typical example of a gangsta rap song.  Not surprisingly, the woman was quite offended that this song would appear on the radio, proclaiming the songs of the old days are better for kids.  Not surprisingly, that is simply not true, and there is far more to the story than what appears on the surface.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/vince-staples.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Vince Staples&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Vince Staples, as featured on his new EP, Prima Donna&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;There are plenty of songs on the radio that have inappropriate lyrics.  Some people may be surprised that plenty songs from way back then are about either slightly to very inappropriate things.  Every Breath you Take, by The Police?  A song about a guy stalking a woman who leaves him breathless.  Purple Haze by Jimi Hendrix?  Like plenty of rock songs from that time, about drugs.  And who could forget all the pop songs from the old days singing about sex (Britney Spears, Christian Aguilera, anybody)?  But of course, it's only a problem for some when a rapper makes music about life in the streets.  There have been plenty of gangsta raps songs on the radio since the days of N.W.A. proclaiming &quot;Fuck Tha Police.&quot;  Vince Staples is certainly no different than any gangsta rapper from Long Beach or anywhere in the world.  To assume that music was more clean back in the days is wrong.  Nothing has really changed for rappers in the ghetto.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;It's hard for many to understand living the street life because they don't live it.  It is disturbing for those who see it from the outside, myself included.  But what people don't ever think about is that most people who live in the streets don't actually want that life.  No one ever stops to think about the people of the ghetto themselves, rather they see them merely as a stereotype.  For people like Vince Staples, and countless of other people growing up in the ghetto, this is the only life they know, their normal.  They don't know anything else.  So when Vince Staples raps about 'running from the police,' that's because it's what he's used to.  It's not glamorizing like people assume, but their reality.  In fact, for some with skills like Vince Staples, it's a way out of that life.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;While it's true that children shouldn't listen to inappropriate lyrics, it's also true that plenty of people don't pay attention to the lyrics of the songs.  Often times, rappers rap so fast that people don't bother to listen or understand the lyrics.  For those, it's all about the beat.  So for those who do listen to the lyrics, they shouldn't be that surprised.  Try listening to rappers like Bone Thugs-N-Harmony and Twista and tell me you can recite their lyrics off the dome.  And with songs like Panda by Desiigner on the radio constantly, who cares about the lyrics?  Does anyone know what the heck he's talking about?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float:left&quot;&gt;
    		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/norf-norf-lady.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Norf Norf lady&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
    		&lt;h4&gt;If you don't like the music, don't listen to it.&lt;/h4&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;When it's all said and done, this woman shouldn't let her children listen to songs like this, but while she's entitled to her own opinion, she shouldn't slander rappers like Vince Staples over the content of their songs.  Their music isn't meant for kids, anyway, so like life in general, it's up to the parents to do their best to keep their kids from listening to this music, not complain about the rappers themselves or demanding such music not be played on the radio.  In this day and age, anyone can pull up Norf Norf or any other rap song on iTunes, youTube or any other website that features music.  It's up to the parents to set the good example.  There are plenty of people whose demographic is more suitable for songs like Norf Norf that enjoy the music, like myself.  But if I don't like a song or get offended by it (which isn't likely), I simply choose to ignore it because I can't decide for someone else whether they should listen to songs or not.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;When asked about it, Vince Staples defended the woman's right to have an opinion, stating that she can make up her own mind, but at the same time, pointing out that she doesn't understand what the song is all about, leading her to be frightened.  And that, in its essence, is what leads so many people to 'freak out.'  They have no idea what it's like to live in the ghetto.  Just as someone in the ghetto has no idea what it's like to be a devout Christian obsessed with all things Jesus.  There's no point for this woman nor anyone else outside to try to comprehend that life, but to me, understanding the struggle itself is what's most important when listening to music in general.  I'll never understand life in the ghetto, but I can certainly listen to a dope rapper and feel his/her struggle and emotion.  That's what makes rappers like Kendrick Lamar so great.  In the meantime, I'll play Norf Norf and try to figure out what the title Norf Norf means.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/music/2016/10/06/sorry-norf-norf-lady</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/music/2016/10/06/sorry-norf-norf-lady</guid>
        
        
        <category>music</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Football Week Five Thoughts</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Week Five has plenty of great matchups, with three top ten conference battles for the first time: Stanford at Washington on Friday, Wisconsin at Michigan and Louisville at Clemson.  Meanwhile, it's the battle for the Governor's Victory Bell for Minnesota as they went to Penn State, while Oregon, after a demoralizing loss last week, head to Washington State, where they hope to avoid last years dysentery affected loss to Washington State&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/joey-julius.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Joey Julius&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;What in the heck did they feed Joey Julius?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;The first game I went to at the University of Minnesota was a matchup against Penn State at the old Metrodome.  A good game aside, though Penn State won 28-27 thanks to a missed PAT from the Gophers.  Ten years later, the two programs have changed dramatically.  Minnesota was mired in bored mediocrity under Glen Mason, while Penn State had legendary coach Joe Paterno on the sideline.  Their program obviously crashed over the Jerry Sandusky scandal, while Minnesota got a burst of energy from Jerry Kill, who laid the foundation for Tracy Claeys.  This game had the signs of a close matchup, and it did not disappoint.  One thing that stands out for Penn State is their ridiculously large placekicker Joey Julius, who looks and tackles like a nose tackle but with kicking ability.  He laid some monster hits in previous games.  But Gopher LB Jaylen Waters delivered a cheap shot on him, getting ejected.  Pretty stupid.  On the flip side, the Gophers have the tallest  player in college football, 6-10 Tight End Nate Wozniak.  Also, I didn't realize Antoine Winfield Jr. was a cornerback, his dad was a great NFL cornerback.  But for the Gophers, their rushing game was a good as advertised, with Rodney Smith and Shannon Brooks as a great 1-2 punch.  But Penn State, with homecourt advantage, squeaked out an overtime victory 29-26.  The Gophers had their chances, but Penn State made some big plays in the second half to end up with the victory.  Chances are, the Gophers would've won that game at home, but they'll need to improve next week as they host the suddenly struggling Iowa Hawkeyes next week at home for the battle of the Floyd of Rosedale.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float:left&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/img/dysentery.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Dysentery&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;h4&gt;The Cougs are right, Oregon has died of Dysentery&lt;/h4&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;As for the Oregon Ducks, it's clear that their defense is completely broken, and their offense can't keep up.  Washington State loves to throw the ball, and they did plenty of that against the Ducks, but what was surprising was that they managed to rush for six touchdowns with 280 yards on the ground.  Oregon clearly can't stop the run, and they're not going to do any better until they figure out a way to do so.  Clearly, Brady Hoke hasn't improved our defense at all, but the Ducks also lack the depth and personnel, so it's unfair to say whether Hoke has failed since he's not even into his first season.  Oregon's in a crisis, it's been a while, but this is not going to be Oregon's year, unless they drastically improve their defense.  Next week they play Washington, who've they haven't lost to in 12 years, but Washington will come into Autzen Stadium as a favorite for the first time in years.  Oregon will need a huge upset to keep that streak alive.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
    		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/nate-wozniak.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Nate Wozniak&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
    		&lt;h4&gt;Nate Wozniak is HUGE!&lt;/h4&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I didn't think if was possible, but the Huckin' Fuskies appear to be legit, they crushed Stanford.  Good lord!  Who'd of thunk that Steve Sarkisian leaving would be the best thing to happen to them.  Not only did they get a great coach in Chris Petersen, but they got rid of a drunk.  How well did he do at USC? --- Baylor should be ashamed of themselves.  Their new head coach Jim Grobe brought rape survivor Brenda Tracy to speak to them, and while she said the players were engaged, an assistant questioned her appearance and made her feel unwanted.  How disgusting!  They barely beat Iowa State 45-42.  That school is messed up, only interesting in winning.  You wonder why Penn State got in the position they did. --- Last week, I mentioned about Les Miles' poor clock management.  The next day, he was fired.  They should've fired him in the offseason when they wanted to.  His act got old pretty quick.  In the interim is Ed Orgeron, whom USC made a big mistake not keeping, hiring Steve Sarkisian instead.  How well did that work out for USC? --- What the heck is going on with Northwestern?  They've lost games to Western Michigan and Illinois State, but managed to beat Iowa.  Pretty perplexing to say the least. --- Five weeks into the season, and two of my picks for the playoffs already have two losses.  Florida State got embarrassed by Louisville and just lost today at home to North Carolina.  That's not national championship material.  Oklahoma's lost twice as well, but on the road to Houston and Ohio State.  They still have a shot, but have to run the table.  Pretty tough. Florida State, on the other hand, has two conference losses already.  They're out.  ---  Tennessee might be the most entertaining team to watch, as they've had to make comebacks in four of their five games this season to win, including three halftime deficits (one against Appalachian State!), and the other game against Ohio was a close one as well.  Against Georgia today, Tennessee completed a hail mary to win the game.  Safe to say, that type of grit will help them in the long run, especially for their next two games: Texas A&amp;amp;M and Alabama.  Those will be tough.  --- Indiana finally beat Michigan State in OT, 24-21.  The Hoosiers have come a long way, and they won with defense, a far cry from their high-scoring/no-defense past.  Props to the Hoosiers.  --- With that said, here are my picks for Top Ten:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alabama&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ohio State&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michigan (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clemson (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Louisville (-2)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Houston (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Texas A&amp;amp;M (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Washington (+2)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tennessee (NR)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Miami (NR)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/10/01/college-football-week-five-thoughts</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/10/01/college-football-week-five-thoughts</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Liar Liar, Pant is on Fire</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; People lie, doesn't matter who you are.  But some people lie more than others.  This year, lying has become the new truth-telling, as the Republican candidate for President, whose name won't be mentioned, lies about, well, basically everything.  This is coming from a man who believes it's okay to lie and does so repeatedly and often as possible.  A man so deluded in himself that he complains a mass conspiracy every time someone tells him what he's saying is lying.  He even claims Ted Cruz as the biggest liar of all time with the nickname Lyin' Ted (to be fair, they are both ridiculous liars). With that said, tonight is the first Presidential debate, and one thing is for certain: this Idiot will frequently lie.  If a drinking game would be made out of it, all participants would die of alcohol poisoning. Here's a live look at lie upon lie upon lie..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/hillary-clinton-donald-trump.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;The debate&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;One's great, one's stupid.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:03 PM - The first Presidential debate is started by moderator Leslie Holt, who announces it's sponspored by a non-partisan committee.  The Idiot previously thought the Democrats controlled it because the Falcons-Saints game is playing.  And here come Hillary in Red, and the Idiot with a blue tie.  Ironic colors for both of them.  Now we get the opening statement about acheiveing prosperity, mainly jobs.  Hillary Clinton first.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:06 PM - Hillary talks first about the economy, and looking at the Idiot, he looks like a grumpy pompous ass while he's listening.  After acknowledging him, he showcases his ugly chin.  He's effin' ugly&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:08 PM - And now for the Idiot.  He talks about stealing jobs, but he's done plenty of this&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:10 PM - Hillary responds by calling the Idiot's economic plan as Trumped Up trickle down (I think), the most extreme ever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:12 PM - The Idiot is talking about his small loan in 1975 of $1,000,000 dollars, which was much more in value than it is today.  With inflation, that's like $10,000,000.  Jenn just told me he's snifling a lot.  Now I noticed it.  He claims Hillary didn't do enough, but it's a too party street.  Hello?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float:left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/hillary-clinton2.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Hillary Clinton&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Hillary Clinton&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:14 PM - The moderator asked him to actually answer the question, which he didn't answer.  Jenn's right, he's snifling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:15 PM - Hillary mentions the Recession as the primary reason for such jobs leaving.  After she mentioned the Idiots desire to profit off the collapse, he said &quot;That's business.&quot;  This is not business, it's being the President.  Idiot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:16 PM - The Idiot said he never said that global warming is a hoax.  It's all over his Twitter page.  Another case of &quot;I didn't say this even though I clearly did.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/donald-trump5.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Donald Trump&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Idiot!&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:18 PM - The Idiot claims Obama's doubled the debt, but we were already in debt.  He asks Hillary why she hasn't come up with any solutions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:19 PM - Hillary has been thinking about it, but not for 30 years she joked.  It's not up all to her by herself.  He interrupts with remarks about NAFTA and then drinks some water.  Whoop dee doo.  What an Idiot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:21 PM - He keeps complaining about NAFTA, talking about devastation.  Hillary mentions him living in his own reality twisting her words.  He keeps interrupting about &quot;Is this Obama's fault?&quot;  He told Hillary he has no plan, but she mentions her plan clear and available in stores and at the airport, called Stronger Together.  He has no plans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:23 PM - He's proud of the biggest tax plan cut since Ronald Reagan.  Reagan raised taxes.  He talks about regulations upon regulations, but regulations make companies play the level field.  He said Bigly two times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float:left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/hillary-clinton4.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Hillary Clinton&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Hillary Clinton&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:24 PM - The Idiot says his things are Facts.  They are clearly not Facts!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:25 PM - The Idiot says she shouldn't announce her plans to fight ISIS and claims she's been fighting ISIS her entire adult life.  Last time I checked, ISIS was founded in 2004.  Hillary is not 35.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:27 PM - The Idiot says 5 trillion dollars can't be brought in due to bureaucratic red tape.  That's likely a lie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:28 PM - The Idiot says &quot;Why not?&quot; as Hillary said she'll likely to be blamed for everything tonight.  Lester Holt told him to let her answer her question.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/donald-trump3.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Donald Trump&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Idiot!&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:29 PM - Hillary talked about the Trump Loophole, a so-called name that his tax cuts would benefit his family.  He keeps interrupting her.  He wants his word even though it's her turn to talk.  What a loser.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:30 PM - The Idiot claims she's all talk and no action.  He claims the worst economical revival since the Depression.  The economy hasn't been as bad since the depression.  Big hole to dump.  The moderator talks about his tax returns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:31 PM - The Idiot claims a routine audit about his taxes.  He talks about his financial statement, but it's not a complete picture.  Release your taxes Idiot, it's clear you're hiding something.  The moderator mentions the IRS won't disallow him.  He complains about all the years under audit, it's because you're a fraud who's been sued so many times.  Now he's talking about her deleted emails, childish threats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:34 PM - Hillary talks about the reasons he won't release his tax returns, and referred to as a Bait and Switch.  Who cares about her emails?  She talked about her emails, but interrupted again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:36 PM - The Idiot claims it was on purpose and illegal.  It was not illegal, just naive.  He claims you learn more about financial disclosures than tax returns.  But you don't get your tax rates.  Stupid!  He talks about knowing about money, but he filed for Chapter 11 Bankruptcy 6 times.  He claims our country in a mess and called us a third world country.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:39 PM - Hillary wants to talk about his business and all the people he's stiffed for money.  His response: he didn't do a good job.  You still have to pay regardless of whether you like it or not.  It's called a contract.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:41 PM - The Idiot talks about words.  But that's all he is...words.  No action.  He said he paid the contractors but said he didn't paid them earlier.  He sniffles his nose again.  Now he talks about about making something under budget.  Sure, and I wear a bra.  The Moderator says we're really behind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float:left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/donald-trump4.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Donald Trump&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Idiot!&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:44 PM - Now we're on to race issues.  Hillary's up first, talking about the tragedies in Tulsa and Charlotte.  Again, actual ideas about the criminal justice system and trust within the community, with both minoriites and the police.  It does need to be a mutual decision.  And yes, gun violence is a big factor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:46 PM - Now the Idiot talks about Law and Order.  He talks about a large support of policemen.  He talks about African Americans and Hispanics living in hell, with 'thousands' of shootings in Chicago this year.  Again, he has no idea to stop this.  He blames Obama for all of this violence and wants racist Stop and Frisk policies.  He has no ideas to stop this.  Stop and Frisk was declared unconstitutional because of racist tendencies, but the Idiot claims the judge is biased.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float:left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/hillary-clinton1.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Hillary Clinton&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Hillary Clinton&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:49 PM - The Idiot doesn't get it.  He keeps talking about Obama's presidency.  But violence is always been bad, it didn't start in 2009.  And he wants Stop and Frisk so cops can profile Blacks and Hispanics.  We need law and order without racial profiling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:51 PM - Hillary mentions how the Idiot has such a grim view of the inner cities.  She talks about having actual ideas, while all he can say is &quot;Law and Order.&quot;  All words.  If you're too dangerous to fly, you're too dangerous to buy a gun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:54 PM - Hillary talks about how everyone is implicitly racially biased.  Well said, it's not just a police issue.  We need officers retrained.  She mentioned mental health, which is always overlooked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:55 PM - The Idiot claims the NRA are good people.  They are corrupt and only interested in gun.  Now he mentioned the term super-predator which she said years ago.  He claims stop and frisk brought murders down in NYC from 2,000 to 500.  That's bogus, and it had little impact.  She responds that crime is still down in NYC, he interrupts that it's not.  The Idiot's stupid.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:58 PM - The Idiot claims Democrats are abusing African Americans for votes.  Republicans are trying to keep them from voting with voting right restrictions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/donald-trump2.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Donald Trump&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Idiot!&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:59 PM - Hillary got applause for saying she's preparing to be President.  Now he's asked about Obama's birthplace.  He's wasting his time talking about Hillary's role.  He doesn't want to talk about it.  She had nothing to do with that.  The moderator mentions he continued to claim he wasn't from Hawaii.  By the way, Obama did produce his birth certificate before he became President.  The Idiot is so stupid.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:02 PM - Hillary wisely points that the birther lie was racist, and tells the truth about what really happened.  It was how he started his career.  She talks about his lawsuits from the 70's about his racist behavior.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float:left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/hillary-clinton3.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Hillary Clinton&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Hillary Clinton&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:05 PM - The Idiot is again lying about the Birther claim.  Hillary's team had nothing to start the Birther theory.  He's lying again.  Another section begins, security issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:06 PM - Once again, Hillary talks about two types of cyber criminals, including the Russian hacks of our countries organizations.  She's mentioned the Idiot's praise of Vladimir Putin.  He scoffs as if he doesn't praise Vladimir Putin.  She says it's one of their prime methods.  She mentions his asking for Putin to hack into her emails while he shakes his head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/donald-trump1.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Donald Trump&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Idiot!&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:09 PM - Now the Idiot talks about more endorsements from Admirals and Navymen.  Sure...  And he talks about the political hacks running, probably because they support Hillary Clinton.  He's not answering the question, he's talking about the hacked emails themselves about Bernie Senders.  And ISIS is learning lots of internet stuff, including his words against Islam.  Once again, he's blaming the government for everything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:11 PM - More talking from Hillary about a plan to defeat ISIS, and obviously, she isn't going into the specifics, like the Idiot claims it.  And she knows we need to go after Baghdadi, the leader.  The moderator mentions the American citizens committing terrorist attacks.   American citizens.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:13 PM - The Idiot mentions Obama and Hillary creating ISIS.  Wrong.  He claims they created ISIS.  Wrong.  He talks about the oil we didn't take.  That's illegal.  He claims he never supported the Iraq War.  Wrong!  The Idiot said it's wrong that he supported the Iraq war, three times.  She mentioned Bush's agreement to leave Iraq.  Not Obama.  Bush.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/hillary-clinton6.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Hillary CLinton&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Hillary Clinton&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:16 PM - Hillary talks about allies, mentioning how the Idiot frequently insults Muslims.  He's so stupid.  Idiot!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:17 PM - The Idiot talks about the Middle East is a total mess.  It's always been a mess.  He claims it's common sense that NATO needs to pay off.  He still isn't answering the question about home-grown terror or even mentioned it.  ISIS was formed in 2004, not in 2012.  Hello?  He wants to take them out quickly.  It's not an easy task.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:19 PM - He again denies he supported the war in Iraq.  He claims the record is not right, that he's always right.  He said, &quot;Yeah sure&quot; to Howard Stern.  Sean Hannity is a hack.  He told him his views after Howard Stern.  He's complaining about the media.  He's lying again.  The moderator mentions he's making mere judgments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:24 PM - Hillary's talking with experience, mentioning actual policies and getting things done.  The Idiot, not so much.  He's so stupid.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:26 PM - The Idiot says Obama is her president.  He says global warming is not the greatest threat.  He's the president of the United States.  And with NATO, he only cares about getting paid.  He's so stupid.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:31 PM - I'm getting worn out by this debate.  At least Hillary is smart enough to bring some intelligence to the conversation.  The Idiot keeps talking about her creating ISIS.  They didn't create ISIS.  He wants to help allies, but wants them to pay up.  He keeps talking about his business ability.  This is the Presidential election.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:33 PM - Now he's taking about Hillary's stamina.  He's arguing with the moderator over wording.  This has nothing to do with stamina.  Pretty sexist.  She mentions all her experience.  He claims it's bad experience.  We didn't give Iran 150 million dollars for nothing.  Stupid.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/hillary-clinton5.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Hillary CLinton&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Hillary Clinton&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:36 PM - The Idiot claims no one feels sorry for the things he said about Rosie O'Donnell.  He claims her ads are 'not nice' and 'not true.'  He's talking about the polls.  At last, the final statements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:37 PM - Hillary says the election is about us, to vote, not about them.  Same question for the Idiot, who talks about deporting people becoming citizens with some nonsense.  Finally, the debate's over.  Next up, the debates on October 9.  Thank god it's over.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/09/26/liar-liar-pant-is-on-fire</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/09/26/liar-liar-pant-is-on-fire</guid>
        
        
        <category>politics</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Football Week Four Thoughts</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Week Four is a reminder to most that non-conference games are over and the major part of the season begins.  For me, this week can be dubbed the 'State of Colorado' week, as Minnesota faced off against Colorado State, while Oregon hosted Colorado.  An interesting coincidence but nonetheless a good week of football.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/quack.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Quack&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Darren Carrington putting new meaning to quacking like a duck after a touchdown&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Last year, Minnesota needed overtime to win at Colorado State, as Mitch Leidner led the Golden Gophers to a fourth quarter comeback before ultimately winning the game.  This time around, Minnesota led most of the game and were able to hold off Colorado State, with a 31-24 win, to finish their non-conference schedule 3-0.  Shannon Brooks, the team's leading rusher last year made his season debut after missing the first two games with a foot injury.  The Gophers were able to rush the ball for 243 yards in total, with all four touchdowns on the ground.  Their running game, plus a tough defense, makes the Gophers a tough out for their conference foes.  Also to note, Tai'yon Devers now has three tackles this year, all sacks causing fumbles that the Gophers recovered.  He knocked the crap out of Colorado State QB Collin Hill, knocking his helmet off in the process.  Making the most of his work to say the least.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Now that the non-conference schedule is over, Minnesota must make improvements in their passing game in order to contend.  They've made strides but need consistency from Leidner and the wide receivers.  The Big Ten West appears to be wide open, with last year's champ Iowa not playing as well as advertised.  They didn't look particularly good against Rutgers, winning 14-7.  Wisconsin and Nebraska look better than projected, with wins between LSU, Michigan State and Oregon between the two teams.  Minnesota realistically needs to win two out of those three matchups to contend, and with Nebraska and Wisconsin on the road, that task becomes tougher.  In the meantime, they need to win their first road game of the season (and first conference game) against Penn State, where the Governors Victory Bell is on the line.  A winnable game by all means but Beaver Stadium is a tough place to play, and Minnesota's only won two games there, the last win in 2003)&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
        		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/EMU-protest.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;EMU&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
        		&lt;h4&gt;Eastern Michigan protesters after the game.&lt;/h4&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;    
    &lt;p&gt;Some things are more important than football, and that was clear in last night's game between Eastern Michigan and Wyoming, as protesters, upset with racist graffiti found on campus buildings earlier in the week, took to the field after the game chanting &quot;No Justice, No Peace.&quot;  I feel it's important to speak up about issues, and Eastern Michigan University, which supports the protesters rights, should be applauded for listening.  As long as the message isn't lost in translation and no violence comes as a result, this type of action is approved.  Since Colin Kaepernick stopped standing for the National Anthem, it's become a big topic, and unfortunately, those who don't support his actions don't understand what he (and others who have followed) are actually protesting.  That's another topic which I've previously discussed, but Eastern Michigan should be applauded for the way they've handled the response.  Talking about them just gives me an excuse to mention their town, Ypsilanti, which is up there with Kalamazoo as one of the most interesting city names in Michigan (and the United States in general).  It also means I've mentioned each directional Michigan school in just four weeks; Western Michigan, Central Michigan, and now, Eastern Michigan (in that order).&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Oregon opened its conference schedule against Colorado, who's looked a lot better than in years past, but unfortunately for the Buffaloes, their starting quarterback Sefo Liufau is out with an ankle injury.  On the flip side, Royce Freeman didn't play for the Ducks, but they have plenty of talented running backs behind him; Tony Brooks-James, Kani Benoit and Taj Griffin.  The hype before the game were Oregon's new uniforms, featuring green shirts, white pants and orange socks and shoes, to resemble an actual duck.  Hard to believe they never thought of that all these years but it's a nice and clever look, I enjoyed their jerseys.  As for the game itself, Oregon's defense struggled in the first half to stop Colorado's offense, with backup QB Steven Montez looking like a stud in his first start.  Sefo Who?  The Autzen Stadium crowd, along with every Oregon fan watching, was stunned that Colorado led for most of the first half.  But much like the Buffaloes game last week against Michigan, where they similarly jumped out to a big first half lead, the Ducks came back to take the lead late in the third quarter with two turnovers leading to Oregon touchdowns.  But in the end, Colorado won 41-38 as Dakota Prukop threw his first interception of the year at the worst time to seal the loss for Oregon.  Safe to say, their defense is completely broken, as I feared would be the case.  This one will sting, but congrats to Colorado for finally getting a quality Pac-12 conference win, unfortunately it came against the Ducks.  Next up, a road trip to Washington State.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/smokey.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;smokey&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Tennessee's Smokey uniforms.  Good or Bad?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Former Baylor President Kenneth Starr said today that former coach Art Briles was treatly unfairly in regards to Baylor's sexual assault scandal.  Regardless of whether that's true or not, Kenneth Starr treated Bill Clinton unfairly for prosecuting the sham Monica Lewinsky scandal which had no effect on the United States, yet felt it was the single most important issue in our country leading to an obviously politically motivated impeachment.  Shame on you, Kenneth Starr --- Tennessee wore their smokey gray uniforms against Florida.  I'm not quite sure if I like them or not, they stand as a complete contrast to their bright orange jerseys.  As for the game, they rallied from a 21-3 deficit to beat Florida 38-28.  Maybe they're better than I thought.  Not Top Ten good, but we'll see.  I've never had any issues with the Tennessee Volunteers, plus I have some family nearby, so I'll give them credit. --- LSU was this close to beating Auburn, with a miracle touchdown, but they didn't get the play off in time.  Classic Les Miles, always poor with clock management.  I can only chuckle. --- With that said, here are my picks for Top Ten:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alabama&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ohio State&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Louisville&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michigan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clemson&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stanford&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Houston&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Texas A&amp;amp;M (NR)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wisconsin (NR)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Washington (-1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/09/25/college-football-week-four</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/09/25/college-football-week-four</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Who Killed JonBenét?</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Twenty years ago, the night after Christmas, six year old JonBenét Ramsey was found murdered in her home, in what has become a bizarre and fascinating case, from the rambling ransom note to the suspicion on the family, there are many odd things about the case that makes it unusual.  Yet after 20 years, no one really knows what happened.  Recently, a new investigator team, with new technology, reanalyzed the evidence and discussed their findings on a CBS special.  So with that all said, who killed JonBenét Ramsey?  Here are all my possible theories, complete with their likelihood of it happening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/jonbenet-ramsey.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;JonBenét&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;JonBenét Ramsey&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;John Mark Karr killed her.  He confessed to the crime, but no evidence linked him to it.  The likelihood that he killed her:  0%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Burke Ramsey accidentally killed her.  Burke Ramsey, now 29, recently talked to Dr. Phil about the case, and he came across as socially awkward.  And despite the parents claim he was asleep at the time they called 911, a young voice was heard on the phone after Patsy thought she hung up the phone (she didn't) with updated technology, possibly saying “What did you find?”  I doubt a nine year old would intentionally kill his little sister, but if he was awake, why didn't they make that claim to begin with when he could’ve been awake without committing a crime?  In order for this theory to be true, someone needed to cover the crime, which his parents would have every reason to do.  Clearly, the ransom note was not written by Burke.  But at the same time, he apparently had a temper and hit her on the head with a golf club when she was four.  But that's not indicative of a killer; he was too young to understand.  They also found two dots on her back that might have matched train tracks, which he could’ve used, but doesn’t necessarily mean he did use them.  Also found at the scene was a bowl of pineapple and tea with Burke’s fingerprints, which becomes significant because JonBenét had undigested pineapple in her intestine when they found her.  It’s possible Burke hit her in the head with the flashlight over a pineapple squabble; the flashlight head perfectly fit the skull fracture they found, but it’s not the only reason to accidentally kill someone and anyone could’ve used it.  The likelihood of Burke killing her accidentally: 35%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Patsy Ramsey killed her.  Two theories tie in to this scenario.  One: she got in a fit of rage, and two: she was mad at her husband and wanted him to pay for it.  The police had her submit five writing samples as they suspected she wrote the ransom note due to similar handwriting and found her fingerprints on the pad and pen.  The new investigators analyzed the note and believe a woman wrote it based on the language.  Her 911 call was incredibly off, as her apparent grief seemed fake, especially with the conversation overheard accidentally showed her incredibly calm.  And her and John refused to talk to the police for a while, not to mention the fact they had friends over while the crime scene was being investigated.  That in itself is a sign of trying to destroy evidence.  Something was never right with Patsy, and while it’s true she pushed JonBenét with all the pageantry stuff, it is possible she snapped from various reasons, whether it was jealousy or perfectionism.   The likelihood of Patsy killing her: 40%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/burke-ramsey.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Burke&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Burke Ramsey&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;li&gt;John Ramsey killed her.  John Ramsey acted weird, running straight for the basement when the police told him they needed to search the house top to bottom.  And he planned to leave shortly after they found JonBenét deceased.  That seems a bit odd, but wouldn't explain the ransom note that made him the target.  At the very least, he was involved in the so-called cover-up.  The likelihood he killed her: 5%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Patsy Ramsey hired someone to kill her.  The DNA found on JonBenét’s body did not match her immediate family.  That ruled them out as official suspects, but that doesn't mean they weren't involved in her death.  Assuming Patsy wrote the note, she could have had someone enter the house to kill JonBenét, but if money was the object, why wasn't she actually kidnapped?  Perhaps a struggle ensued and the hired killer took things too far by striking her while Patsy wrote the ransom note.  On the other hand, the broken glass theory seemed unlikely, someone probably would've heard it and cobwebs were found intact, as the window was allegedly broken by John months prior.  There was no break-in, so someone else who may have entered the house had to have been let in.  It makes no sense for them to enter through the basement window based on the evidence.  Patsy is the most likely to do this.  The lack of footprints outside in the snow is harder to get explain under this theory, but everything else potentially works.  The probability of Patsy hiring someone to kill her: 15%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;John Ramsey hired someone to kill her.  It’s highly unlikely that this is a possibility as John Ramsey had little motive to kill JonBenét, but you never know, he could've had a double life and seeked an escape, but that would require killing the whole family.  The likelihood of John hiring someone to kill her: 2%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A complete stranger killed her.  There are plenty of sexual predators out there, and one of them could've easily slipped in the door and committed the crime.  Of course, without no forced entry, the only way this is possible is if the door was unlocked.  Otherwise, there would've been evidence of a break-in.  But anything is possible.  There are plenty of people that would have had an unhealthy lust for her since she was in beauty pageants all prettied up.  But why write a ransom note inside with the exact amount of John’s bonus?  Who knew that number besides the family itself.  And since the ransom note suggests a cover-up, why cover up a complete stranger.  The likelihood of a complete stranger killing her: 10%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/patsy-ramsey.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Patsy&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Patsy Ramsey&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are a lot of things to consider when making the determination as to who killed JonBenét.  There was no break-in or footprints (they found one but not conclusive), which highly suggests the killer was already in the house.  Though it’s possible a stranger found a key and entered the house without a break-in, it doesn't completely explain the ransom note.  A true ransom note wouldn't have been written as long nor on pad of paper found in the house.  Even more damaging to the legitimacy of the ransom note was that JonBenét was found dead in the basement.  That's not a kidnapping.  This further suggests that her killer was one of her family members.  But which member was it?  Burke, Patsy or John?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s little evidence to conclude that John Ramsey was the killer.  The ransom note was targeted at him and didn't sound like he wrote it.  He appears to be a family loving businessman and nothing else.  The motive isn't there.  That just leaves Patsy and Burke as the two most likely perpetrators.  Both had the ability to kill JonBenét, whether intentional or not.   There’s certainly a reason to believe a cover up occurred, as a grand jury voted to indict John and Patsy for charges related to her murder, but ultimately the DA declined to press charges.  But who had more of a motive to have a crime covered up?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are plenty of reasons to believe Burke was the killer.  He acted bizarre over the whole ordeal, and his parents apparently lied about him being asleep at the time they called 911.  They spent their lives protecting him and wanting him to have a normal life.  Plus with a tendency to have a temper, it was possible to hit her in a rage.  It would perfectly explain the ransom note as a means to bring attention away from him.  But at the same time, any awkwardness shown in his psychiatry visits doesn’t necessarily suggest that said awkwardness was due to killing her.  Maybe he witnessed the attack that left JonBenét Ramsey dead, and the reason the parents said he was asleep was to keep him from testifying.  That is also possible. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To me, the most likely suspect is Patsy Ramsey.  The way she acted during the 911 call was not what you'd expect from someone who lost a child.  She sounded too calm and likely would've shown a tad more emotion if it was Burke rather than herself.  She pushed JonBenét hard with the pageantry and perhaps got jealous of the attention she received and snapped.  She invited friends over while police were investigating the crime scene and wouldn't speak to the police, speaking to CNN first.  Even then, the way she spoke of JonBenét after she died struck me as someone who killed her, rather than someone protecting her son who killed her.  She said things like “I loved that child,” which lacks empathy to me.  John Ramsey was a loving husband and would’ve easily protected his wife if said attack was not intentional.  There certainly are problems with this theory, but it makes more sense than Burke being the killer.  Sure, Burke was weird, and still is weird, but he could've always been like that.  He appeared to be jealous of the attention JonBenét got, but that didn’t mean he actually killed her.  Plus, he was nine years old.  He would’ve never been criminally charged with her death, as he was too young.  But Patsy would’ve faced murder/manslaughter charges if she was in fact the killer.  She would’ve face prison time and that would’ve destroyed the family fabric.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/john-ramsey.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;John&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;John Ramsey&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One thing for certain is that the family never wanted this case solved.  They used their money and influence to keep the investigation grounded, and did everything else to wipe out and destroy evidence.  Had the police officers and FBI had not messed up the initial investigation, chances are, the crime would’ve been solved 20 years ago.  In this essence, all three Ramsey’s were involved in her death and only have themselves to blame.  Protecting themselves at the expense of JonBenét is sad.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/entertainment/2016/09/24/who-killed-jonbenet</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/entertainment/2016/09/24/who-killed-jonbenet</guid>
        
        
        <category>entertainment</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
