<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adam's Blog</title>
    <description>A blog about whatever is on Adam's mind.</description>
    <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 17:15:14 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 17:15:14 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Football Week One Thoughts</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Thank god football's back.  It's refreshing to take interest in something besides politics and this ridiculous election.  Week One is under wraps, and though only a handful of games carry any value, it's only the beginning.  Here's my thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/taiyon-devers.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Tai'yon Devers&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Tai'yon Devers with two sacks, both fumbles recovered by the Gophers&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Gophers played a tough game against Oregon State, managing to hold onto a 30-23 win despite some sluggishness in the passing game and three ejections from targeting.  Rodney Smith did a good job running and Mitch Leidner showcased his gutsy running on key downs.  Oregon State looked decent and are heading in the right direction, but still a young team, and it showed.  The first game of the season, obviously, but the Gophers will need to play better to take the next step.  Either way, the Gophers won the battle of the 'Rodents,' the only two Major FBS teams with rodent mascots.  Next up, FCS Indiana State.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also playing Thursday night was my pick as most overrated team in the Top 10, Tennessee, who went above and beyond to prove their overrated-ness, just barely beating Appalachian State in OT, 20-13, exactly nine years to the day that the Mountaineers of Appalachian State pulled off their historic massive upset of Michigan.  Safe to say, Tennessee is not there quite yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Saturday, my pick for most underrated team, Houston, played against Oklahoma in a battle of Top 15 teams.  The biggest game in Houston’s history, the Cougars surprised virtually everyone outside Houston by beating Oklahoma.  I'd figured Houston would play well, but exceeded expectations.  The game turned when Houston Auburned Oklahoma with a end-zone to end-zone missed field goal into a touchdown, reminiscent of Auburn’s famous play three years ago against Alabama.  Houston blew the game open after that.  Very impressive effort by Houston, whose Peach Bowl win against Florida State is a game of the past according to the team.  Great philosophy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/royce-freeman.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Royce Freeman&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Royce Freeman was his usual self.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Oregon Ducks began their season against UC Davis, and of course, Oregon won 53-28.  Nothing too spectacular to say, except it was nice to see Pharaoh Brown back after his horrific injury.  Dakota Prukop played as well as one would expect against an FCS team.  On the flip side, their jerseys weren't that great to me, not sure why their jerseys are gray for this game, but they go through so many combos we’ll probably never see it again.  And for the first time in 17 years, Autzen Stadium did not sell out their seats.  Next up, Virginia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for the rest of the games, here are my thoughts.  Once again, USC proved how consistently overrated they are, as defending champs Alabama completely rolled over them 52-6.  Never expected the lousy Trojans to win this game, but a good team would've kept it close.  USC on the other hand, just plain sucked. --- Navy had to pull a quarterback out of the stands to fill in after starter Tago Smith got injured.  Enjoy your fifteen minutes of fame, backup from the stands Malcolm Perry.  Georgia Tech barely beat Boston College in a game played in Dublin, Ireland.  If only Notre Dame had played against Georgia Tech, it would've been the perfect Irish matchup.  But please, no car bombs. --- Virginia, whom Oregon plays next week, lost to FCS power Richmond 37-20.  So much for having two legit Power 5 non-conference teams on the schedule.  At least there's Nebraska. --- Speaking of Nebraska, it was very sweet for them to bring out ten players during their first punt to honor Sam Foltz, who died in a car wreck in July.  Classy act.  Not classy was the scumbag who robbed his brother’s house while this was happening.  This scumbag, who was arrested today, but not identified as of yet, should become the most hated person in Nebraska. --- Northwestern lost to Western Michigan 22-21, which makes me wonder if the recently departed journalist John Saunders (R.I.P.), who went to Western Michigan, lifted them spiritually.  John Saunders was one of my favorites, he will be missed. --- Washington State again proved how unpredictable they are by losing to Eastern Washington 45-42.  They looked fairly good last year despite a loss to Portland State.  They follow up this year with a loss to another FCS team.  What in the hell is Mike Leach smoking?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/houston.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Houston&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Houston turned the game in their favorite with this missed field goal returned for a touchdown.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Week One doesn’t say a lot about the National Championship, but it’s safe to say that Oklahoma won’t win it like I predicted.  By no means does this mean they won’t make it to the playoffs, they can still win out the rest of their games and win the Big XII, but their defense isn’t as great as I thought.  I need to do some better research next time.  Of course, Houston, with its marquee win, has a chance to run the table and make the Playoffs itself.  They still have Louisville to play late in the regular season as a good non-conference game, but they have the talent to go undefeated in the American Athletic Conference and crash the Power 5 Playoff Party.  With that, here are my picks for Top Ten:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alabama&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clemson&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Florida State&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ohio State&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michigan State&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Houston&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stanford&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oklahoma&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;LSU&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michigan State&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/09/06/college-football-week-one</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/09/06/college-football-week-one</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kaepernicking 2.0 - The Protest Edition</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Last Friday, during a preseason game against the Green Bay Packers, Quarterback Colin Kaepernick refused to stand for the National Anthem, taking the opportunity to protest racial oppression in the United States, and plans to continue his protest until 'real change' progresses.  Reaction has not surprisingly been mixed, with some praising him for taking a stand while others are criticizing him for it.  Kaepernick is not the first athlete to use his status to protest civil rights, nor will he be the last, but the question remains, will his refusal to stand actually bring any change?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/kaepernick.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Colin Kaepernick&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Colin Kaepernick&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Sports, more than anything, can bring people together, something we saw after 9/11 and the Boston Marathon attacks.  So in that regard, perhaps sports can help solve our human rights issues.  But we've seen this happen before with little success.  The biggest success was having Jackie Robinson break the color barrier in baseball.  Another success was Jesse Owens winning multiple gold medals in the 1936 Olympics in Nazi Germany.  But other athlete protests have done nothing but made said athletes merely a symbol of protests.  Tommie Smith and John Carlos with the Black Power salute at the 1968 Olympics were courageous to do so, but that's what they're best known for.  Former NBA player Mahmoud Abdul-Rauf refused to stand for the National Anthem during the 1996 for similar reasons as Colin Kaepernick, but his career was never the same after that.  Same thing with Craig Hodges, whose NBA career was all but over after he handed a note to President George H.W. Bush at the White House protesting the treatment of minorities.  For many of the previous examples, these athletes were not notable enough, and thus, didn't have the ability to reach the masses like Michael Jordan, who famously never championed any political causes during his playing career.  The only notable athlete to protest and spread awareness for causes was the late Muhammad Ali, who sacrificed everything to avoid fighting in the Vietnam War.  In that regard, Colin Kaepernick has a steep hill to climb.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;But while things may not have been effective in the past, things are different in 2016.  Social media is rampant and people hear about things in an instant.  Celebrities make their thoughts more public (for better or worse) through Twitter.  We live in a society more aware of racist undertones and more willing to call others out for it.  So maybe now is the time for real progress.  But Colin Kaepernick's career has been on a downhill for the past few years since his miracle run to the Super Bowl.  The fact to the matter is is that no one noticed Kaepernick's refusal to stand for the National Anthem the first two games since he was injured.  One person alone, unfortunately, can not make a difference, whether it's myself, Colin Kaepernick or President Obama.  Kaepernick has a right to stand (or not stand for in his case) for what he believes in, but let's be honest, his actions won't change anything.  Speaking up is a step in the right direction, but collaboration goes further.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float:left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/salute.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Black Power Salute&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Tommie Smith and John Carlos (center and right) with the Black Power Salute&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;As long as the broken system pits us against one another, our society will never change.  As it is, Kaepernick still lives in a world that pits people against each other.  In his case, it's the African Americans against Law Enforcement, and whether Kaepernick is pitting people against each other is his intention, it's clear that Law Enforcement doesn't approve of his actions.  The San Francisco Police Department called his actions &quot;embarrassing&quot; and &quot;disrespectful.&quot;  Standing (or not standing) in protest does little to bridge the gap between said groups necessary to bring real change.  Real change requires everyone on the same page and protest together.  Unfortunately, there's no trust between the two, and that's the biggest challenge.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;Though some question Kaepernick's actions, no one should question his intentions or his passion for speaking up.  It may not be the best way to call for change, but perhaps making a provocative stand, in this day and age, can at least get people talking.  As it is, a lot of people have been talking about it.  Earlier in the year, NBA stars LeBron James, Carmelo Anthony, Dwyane Wade, Chris Paul spoke about racial justice at the ESPY awards, and though it was good for them to speak up, it didn't quite grab the attention that Kaepernick clearly has with his profound statement.  In that regard, going bold can be effective in getting people to talk, which sometimes is half the battle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/2016/08/30/kaepernicking</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/2016/08/30/kaepernicking</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>If It Sounds Like A Racist...</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last week, the Governor of Maine, Paul LePage, known for being an obnoxious blubber mouth, bluntly stated that 90% plus of all drug dealers arrested in Maine are &quot;Black and Hispanic,&quot; a statement which many found to be abhorrently racist.  After all, this is the same Governor who earlier in the year proclaimed that drug dealers &quot;are guys with the name D-Money, Smoothie, Shifty; these types of guys, they come from Connecticut and New York, they come up here, they sell their heroin, they go back home. Incidentally, half the time they impregnate a young, white girl before they leave, which is a real sad thing because then we have another issue we have to deal with down the road.&quot;  Clearly, these types of comments, focusing on skin color, are profoundly racist in nature, lumping blacks with drugs and street-names.  Yet Paul LePage, angry that Democratic State Rep. Drew Gattine allegedly called him racist, left him a vulgar voicemail demanding proof of his 'racism,' using multiple swear words against him, including cocksucker, and told him, &quot;I am after you,&quot; amongst other things.  It would be one thing to say something once, but people like Paul LePage have repeatedly made racist comments.  So what do incidents like this say about racism in our society?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/lobster.gif&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Maine Lobsters&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Sadly, Lobsters are more capable of running Maine than Governor Paul LePage&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Earlier in the year, rapper Macklemore released a song called &quot;White Privilege II,&quot; where he rapped &quot;It seems like we're more concerned with being called racist / Than we actually are with racism,&quot; and this definitely seems to be true here and in many cases.  Someone like Paul LePage doesn't seem to realize that this comments are racist or could be construed as racist, yet is immediately offended as being called a racist, focusing on self-image rather than society as a whole.  People like this knows what racism is and how to define it, but ultimately, they all ignore their own inherent racism.  Racism has been around forever, and in some shape or form will always exist, but for some, it's not an issue until someone calls you out for it.  Like it or not, defining someone based off their race or ethnicity is never the right thing to do.  It accomplishes nothing but put unburden some blame on people without cause.  People are complex beings and are not easy to define.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;It seems like we're more concerned with being called racist / Than we actually are with racism.&lt;footer&gt;Macklemore - White Privilege II&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By definition, the word racism is defined as &quot;the belief that all members of each race possess characteristics or abilities specific to that race, especially so as to distinguish it as inferior or superior to another race or races.&quot;  With LePage's comments about drug dealers, you would think that only blacks and Hispanics are capable of being drug dealers, but stereotyping minorities (or anyone in general based on certain characteristics) with negative connotations is racist, as any group of people are capable of being drug dealers.  For this instance, all this accomplishes is makes Blacks and Hispanics scapegoats for a problem that is more complicated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float:left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/lepage.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Paul LePage&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Governor Paul LePage has no clue of what it means to be racist&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Does making racist comments actually solve anything?  Here, it obviously ignores that fact that there are plenty of drug dealers that have not been caught.  Statistics have shown that police officers are far more likely to go after African Americans and Hispanics than they are whites, even though whites are more likely to be guilty of something.  It happens in places like Cleveland, Baltimore and Ferguson, and certainly does little fix the real issues.  Solving Maine's drug problem requires complex and intricate thinking, more than just identifying the dealers skin color or ethnicity.  It does nothing to stop the issue, and leads to more racial profiling, overlooking the biggest problem within all of this, the drug abusers themselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Racial profiling is not only wrong but completely immoral.  It basically states: &quot;If you are of a certain color, you're probably going to do something bad, but if you're not that color, you're fine.&quot;  Paul LePage thinks blacks are drug dealers, but plenty of blacks aren't dealing drugs, and yet, they are more likely to be accused of dealing drugs than a white person who actually deals drugs will.  So while plenty of Americans will focus on a person's skin color and their stereotypes to form their opinions about them, it ignores the complexity of human beings.  As a Jewish minority, there are plenty of negative stereotypes associated with my religion that aren't associated with me at all, yet Anti-Semitic people have already formed an opinion of me without actually knowing me that's not true.  It's the same with other groups of people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&quot;blockquote-reverse&quot;&gt;&quot;Mr. Gattine, this is Gov. Paul Richard LePage.  I would like to talk to you about your comments about my being a racist, you (obscene term). I want to talk to you. I want you to prove that I'm a racist. I've spent my life helping black people and you little (obscene term), socialist (obscene term). You -- I need you to -- just friggin'. I want you to record this and make it public because I am after you. Thank you.&quot; &lt;footer&gt;Paul LePage leaving a voicemail&lt;/footer&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether someone is actually racist or not is often debatable, but deep down, people can be implicitly racist and not realize or understand it.  These people often can identify someone else as being racist but can't comprehend their own racist thoughts.  Paul LePage certainly sees no wrong in his words, claiming he was just going through a binder full of drug arrests in his state.  But the sad truth is that many people focus on one small detail on human beings to identify everything there is to know about them: color.  There are numerous other qualities that human beings have, from genetics, environmental factors and socioeconomic upbringing, the latter which is often ignored by those who judge solely on skin color.  So while people like LePage focus on color, solving problems requires a more comprehensive research on human beings than just skin color.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/maine.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Maine&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Maine is far too beautiful to have a racist talking Governor in charge.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt; the flipside, we also have people who will say things like &quot;I like these people, I've done this and this for them,&quot; to make the claim that they are not racist.  Paul LePage has no problem stating &quot;he's done all these things to help the African-American community,&quot; but it's basically a cop-out to say things like this.  Once again, it focuses on a person's skin color or ethnicity, rather than their complete personality.  I am more than just Jewish, so really, is anything accomplished by focusing on my religion and not my complete self?  Of course not, but don't tell those whose main goal is to not be referred to as racist?  In the end, that's more important for some than the issue of racism itself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/08/28/if-it-sounds-like-a-racist</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/08/28/if-it-sounds-like-a-racist</guid>
        
        
        <category>politics</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Football Preview 2016</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Next week is the unofficial start of the College Football season, and after a boring summer filled with boring baseball, I'm ready for some football.  Although it officially started 'last night' when Cal played Hawaii halfway around the world in Sydney, Australia, next week is the start for the rest of us. As someone who spent three years at the University of Oregon and one and a half years at the University of Minnesota, I have two teams to follow, and as long as they don't play each other, I don't have to decide.  So here are my thoughts on the upcoming football season.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/leidner.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Mitch Leidner&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Mitch Leidner&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;As previously mentioned, I would hate for Oregon and Minnesota to play each other.  It's a good thing that Minnesota instead chose to open its season against Oregon State.  Not only that, Oregon is too fast for Minnesota.  Oregon State had a disappointing season last year (2-10), but I can't imagine the Beavers being that bad again this season.  With that said, Minnesota is playing at home and has the more steady hand offensively, with Mitch Leidner back at the helm at Quarterback.  Gophers win, 24-14.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;This season, the Big Ten has decided to hold nine conference games, rather than the eight they have previously played.  That means one more conference opponent instead of a crappy non conference opponent. The rest of the Gophers non conference games are against FCS Indiana State and Colorado State.  Colorado State gave them a close game last year, and could very well do the same this year, but I imagine Minnesota will finish 3-0 in the non-conference.  As for their conference games, Minnesota has a far more easier slate of conference games than last year, when Minnesota had one of the toughest schedules imagined.  Rather than playing Michigan and Ohio State, Minnesota instead gets crossover matchups against Penn State, Maryland and Rutgers, who were three of the four worst teams in the Big Ten's East Division.  As it is, Iowa is the only ranked team (#17) on Minnesota's schedule.  The good news for Minnesota, they get Iowa at home.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;So how do the Gophers perform this season?  Should the Gophers get some consistency from Mitch Leidner and their offense, the Big Ten West is wide open for Minnesota to have a chance to steal the Big Ten West from Iowa.  Wisconsin isn't dominate like they have been recently, and perhaps Minnesota can finally win Paul Bunyan's Axe (obviously the most important game of the season).  Nebraska, Northwestern and Penn State are talented enough to match with Minnesota, so winning two of those games (if not all three) is essential.  Shannon Brooks, their leading rusher last year is injured, but should be ready for the Big Ten schedule.  Their passing game showed some signs last year but needs to make the next step in order for Minnesota to contend.  My prediction: Minnesota finishes a respectable 8-4, good for second in the Big Ten West.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/prukop.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Dakota Prukop&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Dakota Prukop&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;    
    &lt;p&gt;As for the Oregon Ducks, who begin the season ranked #24 (AP) and #22 (Coaches Poll), the Ducks will once again have a new quarterback at the helm.  It was just announced yesterday, to little surprise, that FCS transfer, former Montana State QB Dakota Prukop will be the starter, and Justin Herbert, a true freshman from Sheldon High School, coming out of nowhere to supplant expected backup Travis Jonsen as the backup.  Prukop has the smarts and the footwork to be successful, although probably not as good as Vernon Adams was last year, Oregon still has plenty of offensive weapons starting with Heisman contender Royce Freeman, one of the best running backs in the country.  Their offense, assuming they stay healthy, will be fine.  Another thing to note is the return of Pharoah Brown, whose horrific injury two seasons ago nearly cost him his leg.  Any production from him will be welcomed as should he, as he's come a long ways, and was just named starting Tight End once again.  It's their defense that's killed them in the past.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Oregon has never been known for their defense, and it killed them last year blowing a 31-0 lead at the Alamo Bowl.  Though Oregon's usually stayed in house, no one from Oregon could handle the job, as Don Pellum was demoted to Linebackers coach.  In comes Brady Hoke, the former Michigan coach holding a coordinator job for the first time.  Will Oregon's defense improve?  Hard to say with losing their best defensive players from last year (DeForrest Buckner).  They'll need it as Oregon plays plenty of tough games.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Their non-conference schedule isn't anything special, with UC-Davis, Virginia and Nebraska on their plate, the latter game on the road against old nemesis Mike Riley.  Oregon should win all three of those games, heading into a conference schedule with three ranked teams, Washington (inexplicably ranked #14), USC (#20, yuck!) and Stanford (#8, again the toughest game of the year).  Can Oregon win the Pac-12 this year?  Will someone besides Oregon or Stanford win the Pac-12 North?  My hunch tells me Oregon will finish second behind Stanford again.  Oregon beat Stanford last year, but too many questions defensively for them to win the North.  My prediction: Oregon finishes 9-3, good for second in the Pac-12 North&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;As for the rest of the College Football landscape, Alabama and Clemson start the season as they ended it, #1 and #2 respectively.  Oklahoma, making the Playoffs last year as well, is still loaded and ranked #3, while Florida State is ranked #4.  The Big Ten is led by Ohio State and Michigan, and could come down to the two long time rivals.  Stanford is the highest ranked team in the Pac-12, ranked #8 (AP) and #7 (Coaches Poll), with the electrifying Christian McCaffrey at running back.  One team that's ranked too high to start is Tennessee, in the Top Ten in both polls despite their past years of mediocrity.  One team ranked too low (not surprisingly as the best non-major conference team, Notre Dame not included) is Houston (#15, AP and #13, Coaches Poll), who surprised many last year by beating Florida State in the Peach Bowl convincingly, and returning many of their best players.  They begin their season at home against Oklahoma, and though Oklahoma is probably going to win, Houston has plenty of weapons to at least contend with the Sooners (especially at home) and make another BCS Bowl.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/mccaffrey.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Christian McCaffrey&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Christian McCaffrey&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;       
    &lt;p&gt;Some other things that will intrigue me includes all of these things:  How will Baylor perform this year after their controversial summer with the firing of Art Briles for his lack of conduct over their numerous players arrested for various violent crimes?  Two teams I really hate play each other in the first game of the year: Alabama and USC.  Which team is more dispicable right now, the Crimson Tide and their big time success and complaining against Oregon-styled offenses, or the always dislikable USC that always gets ranked no matter how mediocre they really are.  LSU has had a crazy ride with floods affecting the state, particularly Baton Rouge, and the near firing of Les Miles.  How will they perform with all of this going on?  The Pac-12 has lots of talented teams, but since they joined the conference, Colorado has always been at the bottom, slowly creeping their way to respectability.  Is this the year Colorado finally makes the jump from bottom-feeder to respectable?  Lovie Smith, former Super Bowl coach for the Chicago Bears, finds himself as coach of Illinois.  That will be interesting to say the least.  &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Heisman race has two top contenders right now, the aformentioned Christian McCaffrey and Clemson Quarterback DeShaun Watson.  Either one of these two players are talented enough to win the Heisman, but McCaffrey is dangerous no matter where on the field he is.  He's my preseason pick to win the Heisman Trophy.  As for Conference Champions and Playoff teams, here are my picks:  The ACC will once again come down to Clemson and Florida State, the clear two best teams in the conference.  Clemson is obviously talented but my gut tells me Florida State will beat them and win the ACC.  The Big XII has Oklahoma clearly as the best team in the conference, and it's unlikely that will change, as Oklahoma wins the Big XII.  The Big Ten has Ohio State, Michigan and Michigan State as the three best teams in the conference, but with Michigan State losing their leader Connor Cook at Quarterback and Ohio State losing a lot of studs, I pick Michigan to win the Big Ten behind the coaching of the obnoxiously lovable Jim Harbaugh.  The Pac-12 is wide open this year, with Oregon, Stanford, UCLA, Washington and USC all capable of winning the championship, but when it's all said and done, Stanford will repeat.  The SEC is once again ridiculously loaded at the top with Alabama the defending Champion, and they will repeat as SEC Champs again.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Third College Football Playoffs, as I see it, will feature Alabama, Oklahoma, Florida State and Michigan in that order, and when it's all said and done, I pick Oklahoma to win it all, being the most complete team in the nation, a stout defense and an electrifying offense led by Quarterback Baker Mayfield.  This season will be another doozy, that's for sure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/08/27/college-football-preview-2016</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/08/27/college-football-preview-2016</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My New Family Roots</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; For many years, my Mom has been on a quest to find her family roots, never knowing who her biological father was.  Recently, a DNA test found my Mom with 47% European Jewish, 34% Great Britain and 16% other.  I've always wanted to know about my family roots as well, and with my Mom's interest, I was able was able to dig deeper than before to find that her Great-Grandpa's Barnet and Harry were born in the Suwałki area of what was then part of Russia, an area now part of Poland with a portion of its historical area in Lithuania.  So what is Suwałki?  Here is an expose on an area where I have roots.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/Vistytis.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Lake Vištytis&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Lake Vištytis&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Historically speaking, Suwałki was part of Congress Poland, an area of modern-day Poland and Lithuania occupied by Russia.  The area in the 19th Century had a significant Jewish population, with the oldest Synagogue built in 1821.  In 1897, 10% of the Suwałki Governorate, (which had around 589,200 people in total) was Jewish.  The largest town in the area was Suwałki itself, but had other towns with Jewish residents, including Vištytis, which appears to the be the likely town my Pearlstein family came from, based on its Polish translation Wisztyniec, where evidence pointed to a place called &quot;Wistenez&quot; I pulled from a World War II Registration Card from one of my Great-Great Grandfathers.  So where exactly did my family come from?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Suwałki region has historically been a conflict area between Poland, Lithuania, and somewhat Russia, whose exclave Kaliningrad is also within range of the Suwalki region.  After World War I, when Germany occupied the area,  Poland and Lithuania became independent states, no longer control of Russia, but their borders were contested, as Lithuania, with a majority population in the Suwałki region, claimed part of it as its own, even though it was never theirs historically.  This led to the Polish-Lithuanian War from 1919-1920, which led to a peace treaty giving control of the Suwałki region to Poland. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/LithuaniaRegions.gif&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Lithuania&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;The historical Suwałki region (in yellow) in comparison to Lithuania today&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sadly, all the Jews in the Suwałki region were killed in World War II after Nazi Germany took over Poland and the Suwałki region, desecrating their homes as well as the Jewish Cemetery.  Today, there are no Jews in the area, just an empty cemetery buried with Jews.  Quite sad, like the whole Holocaust itself.  I found an interesting article on the History of Jews in the Suwałki area, which you can read by clicking &lt;a href=&quot;http://kehilalinks.jewishgen.org/suwalki/history.htm&quot;&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for Vištytis, I found this small town in Lithuania, just miles away from the Poland and right on the Russia (Kaliningrad) border.  Sitting along a lake with the same name, Vištytis had a good number of Jews, though many emigrated to Germany, the United States and South Africa starting in the 1850s.  Vištytis was also the subject of Nazi Germany, as an estimated 200-400 Jewish residents (amongst the 1,000 total in town) were all murdered.  Today, a memorial and 'Jewish' tombstone can be found in town to honor the Jews whose lives were lost in World War II.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/suwalki.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Suwalki&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;My Jewish roots can be found within the red circle.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I always wondered where my Jewish family came from.  Growing up, I was told Latvia, which I thought was pretty cool, especially for school assignments about my ancestry since no one else had that area, but seeing the census records for Barnet and Harry, they all stated their births in neighboring Lithuania.  I knew at the time, it was a part of Russia, so either way I knew it was in one of the Baltic states (Lithuania, Latvia and Estonia).  Finding out the specific area yesterday of Suwałki, I thought it was cool that it was in modern day Poland, but with the additional research on a fascinating area, I concluded that it was in fact Lithuania, just very close to Poland.  I never thought to connect those two places next to each other, so reading up on this history is quite interesting, especially when I have history there.  It's also a sad reminder of the Holocaust, to read about it many times is sad, but to know the area my ancestors came from were victims of a horrific time makes me sad and puts a personal touch to it.  Anyway you put it, I'm proud of who I am.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/miscellaneous/2016/08/25/my-new-family-roots</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/miscellaneous/2016/08/25/my-new-family-roots</guid>
        
        
        <category>miscellaneous</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Star Wars - The Whole Shebang So Far</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; For the past seven weekends, I have been watching all the main Star Wars films, from the classic trilogy to the newer prequels, some of which I hadn't seen before, all in Episode order, culminating in the new Star Wars movie, The Force Awakens.  As a kid, I enjoyed the classic Star Wars films, and saw Episode I, which I didn't care for, effectively turning me off of Episode II and III.  Older and wiser, and with a new movie out, I owed it to myself to see the entire series so far from beginning to current.  Without giving away any major plot spoilers that aren't clearly well-known: (&quot;I am your Father,&quot; anyone?), here are my thoughts on all seven films.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/force.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;The Force Awakens&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;The Force Awakens&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Episode I: The Phantom Menace - When I first saw The Phantom Menace years ago, I didn't care for it that much.  I enjoyed playing a racing game based on the movie on my Nintendo 64, which was also one of the best parts of the movie.  But the kid who played Anakin Skywalker was very annoying and Jar Jar Binks was a complete joke.  Seeing it now, I still agree with Anakin being annoying and Jar Jar being a joke.  It shouldn't be that surprising this is the worst movie of the bunch, as the beginning of the story is never the best.  Liam Neeson playing the Jedi master Qui-Gon Jinn seems like a mismatch and Samuel L Jackson as Mace Windu didn't do much for me either.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Episode II: Attack of the Clones - I didn't have any desire to see Attack of the Clones (or Revenge of the Sith) until now, and seeing it for the first time, found the movie to be average and unremarkable.  There was nothing about this film that really stood out, and Anakin Skywalker, now an adult (played by Hayden Christensen) was poorly played.  Christensen comes off as a bit of a pompous ass, and did a poor job.  One bright spot was evil Sith Lord Count Dooku (played by Christopher Lee), along with his fight with Yoda.  Other than that, this film left a lot to be desired.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Episode III: Revenge of the Sith - Easily the best of the first three films, Revenge of the Sith showcases the end of Anakin Skywalker and the beginning of Darth Vader.  Though I personally found the transition to be too quick and brief, it was still thrilling to see the transition, despite the continued bad acting from Hayden Christensen.  Even better was seeing him and Obi-Wan Kenobi fight in the lava, leaving Vader scarred and the subsequent scene of being reconstructed as the classic Darth Vader.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/vader.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Darth Vader&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Who can forget the evil Darth Vader?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Episode IV: A New Hope - The original Star Wars film is an obvious classic, the one that started the franchise and its popularity today.  I saw it plenty of times as a kid, seen it parodied from Spaceballs to Family Guy, and referenced in other TV shows and movies.  But having seen the prequels, now I know the complete story of Darth Vader’s past, along with Yoda, Obi-Wan Kenobi, Palpatine and the others.  It makes Vader slightly more sympathetic, but not right away.  Still, Vader is pure evil.  With classic characters from Luke Skywalker, Han Solo, Princess Leia and Chewbacca being introduced, The New Hope is a classic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Episode V: The Empire Strikes Back - The Empire Strikes Back is the best movie of the series, showcasing the ruthlessness of Darth Vader even more, along with the many plot twists and turns.  Introducing characters like fan-favorite Boba Fett, Lando Calrissian, and Luke’s first interaction with Yoda make this the best of the bunch.  And how could anyone forget the scene when Darth Vader tells Luke that he is his father (Everyone knows that already)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Episode VI: Return of the Jedi - Return of the Jedi wasn't as good as the previous two films, but wraps up the story of Darth Vader nicely.  On the one hand, Jabba the Hutt, the most awesomely grotesque character in Star Wars (possibly the best character ever) appears mightily early in the film (he appeared in a re-release of the original movie, but I won't go into all the re release controversies).  Watching him is a delight.  But they also had the too-cute for their own good Ewoks, which were obviously meant to appeal to the kids.  The ending was good as Darth Vader finally broke free from the dark side to kill Emperor Palpatine to save Luke.  Seeing the prequels made this more understandable.  It was weird to see the re release with the ghost of Hayden Christensen-played Anakin Skywalker though.  He still sucks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/starwars.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Star Wars&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Luke Skywalker, Princess Leia and Han Solo when they were young&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Episode VII: The Force Awakens - All of this brings us to The Force Awakens, the beginning of the final trilogy of Star Wars, which was released last year to lots of fanfare.  I won't spoil any parts of the movie for those interested, but I enjoyed The Force Awakens.  Not as good as the classics but much better than the prequels, The Force Awakens manages to blend the classic characters with new and interesting characters.  New characters like the conscious-filled Finn, the strong and determined Ray and the villanous yet emotional Kylo Ren bring lots of complexity, while the little robot BB-8 is easily cute and lovable like R2-D2 before him.  On a side note, R.I.P. to Kenny Baker, the actor who played R2-D2 who recently passed away.  Classic characters like Han Solo, Chewbacca, Princess Leia and Luke Skywalker are for the most part, what you would expect from the characters aged 30+ years.  Luke Skywalker looks much different than I expected, but that's all I will say about that.  The plot, which I won't go into too much, is also good, although I find the Supreme Leader Snoke to be kind of boring compared to Palpatine, despite his deft-defying appearance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When it's all said and done, it's easy to see why Star Wars has managed to remain popular after all these years, and with a good start for the final trilogy, who knows what will happen with Episodes VIII (due to be released in 2017) and IX (due to be released in 2019).  There's plenty to like about Star Wars (and a few things to dislike, eh hem Jar Jar Binks) and there's no other series out there with the lasting appeal and grace of Star Wars (sorry, Lord of the Rings, I just couldn't get into the series when I watched it).  May the Force be with you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/entertainment/2016/08/23/star-wars-the-whole-shebang-so-far</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/entertainment/2016/08/23/star-wars-the-whole-shebang-so-far</guid>
        
        
        <category>entertainment</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>XXL Freshmen 2016 - My Thoughts</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Every year, XXL magazine, a popular hip-hop magazine, releases its annual 'Freshmen Edition,' highlighting young and promising MCs that XXL believes will become big stars in the game.  Like any 'draft,' some become big stars while others never pan out.  I used to get really excited over these lists, but it peaked in 2010, with dope artists like Freddie Gibbs, J. Cole, Wiz Khalifa, Big Sean, Nipsey Hu$$le and Jay Rock still holding some star power in their own and special way.  Nowadays, the list is a reminder of how much of a decline popular hip-hop is.  I wanted to write this when the list first came out in June, but held off to give myself some time to listen to some of these rappers, none of whom were MC's I loved, and only a few I even had songs from.  So who amongst the 2016 list has any credibility?  Here are my thoughts, starting from top left of their cover.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/xxlfreshmancover2016.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;XXL Freshman 2016&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;If this is the future of Hip-Hop, please help me&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Desiigner, a young MC from Brooklyn who sounds like a duplicate of Future, a popular Atlanta MC who I consider to be complete trash, hit the scene with a viral hit, Panda earlier in the year.  While the song is addicting and has been in my playlist for its beat and flow, the song itself is admittedly stupid, with nonsensical lyrics and a dumb title.  Legacy, Panda, Huh?  He released a song called Timmy Turner which sounded kinda dorky and too sing-songy.  Though he has a co-sign from Kanye West, the question remains as to whether he really becomes the next Future, trap &quot;king&quot;, or Trinidad Jame$, one-hit wonder (whose song &quot;All Gold Everything&quot; landed him a big deal with Def Jam but got dropped shortly after).  Either way, his career will forever be defined by Panda.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;Dave East, standing tall and proud at the top of the cover, is this years choice for what I like to call the &quot;Underground Pick,&quot; the type of rapper that's strictly for the streets.  Dave East, reppin East Harlem, New York, isn't likely to appear on any mainstream radio stations soon, but will get his attention from those strictly from the underground.  Dave East is no exception to this rule, a raw street rapper that scored a record deal with Nas' Mass Appeal Records.  Dave East, though needing some polish, is one of the standout members on this list, though I wouldn't call any of these rappers can't miss.  East has some potential, with great tracks like the Nas assisted &quot;Forbes List&quot; and &quot;KD.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;Denzel Curry, with the dreadlocks, is nothing special to me.  Unlike some of the rappers on this list, he actually raps, which is a positive, but he is just average to me, which being from the Miami area, isn't totally surprising.  I like the song &quot;Zenith&quot; with Joey Bada$$ and he doesn't do a particularly bad job on the track, but I mainly like Joey Bada$$.  His name makes me think of Denzel Washington and Steph Curry, that's probably the best thing he has going for him, but his style isn't particularly special, though there are far worse artists on the list.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;Lil Yachty, otherwise known as the dude with the ugly red beads in his hair, was chosen as the &quot;People's Champ.&quot;  Frankly, I have no clue why anyone would listen to this guy.  He mostly sings like crap and has no talent whatsoever.  And why is this guy obsessed with boats?  It's guys like Lil Yachty that make rap so awful sometimes.  I try to keep an open mind, but this guy is just a bad singing loser with little rapping.  It's also dumb for an Atlanta rapper to rap about how cold Minnesota is (don't listen to his song &quot;Minnesota,&quot; it's awful).&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;Lil Dicky, the goofy looking white rapper of the bunch, reppin' the Philadelphia area, is exactly that, a goofy white rapper.  Starting off as a comedian but unsuccessful with that career, he turned to rapping to express he comedic chops, and for the most part, it works for him, as he rhymes about silly things but doesn't take himself too serious.  Songs like &quot;Professional Rapper&quot; showcase him trying to fill a niche as a funny-guy rapper rapping back and forth with Snoop Dogg, making the song quite interesting.  He also has the creative means with videos like his early viral hit &quot;Ex-Boyfriend,&quot; where he raps about how huge his girlfriend's ex's package is.  Lil Dicky might be silly but he's smart enough to know he's silly.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;Lil Uzi Vert, another rapper with the name Lil, and like Lil Yachty, with ugly braids, his more purple.  Also from Philadelphia, but with a far stupider name than Lil Dicky.  What does Uzi Vert even mean?  Another sing-songy rapper with dumb lyrics and no real talent, although his hit song &quot;Money Longer&quot; at least has a nice beat and is catchy enough to listen to.  Otherwise, who cares.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;G Herbo, previously known as Lil Herb, is an authentic Chicago street rapper that's part of the rising genre of the so-called Chi-Raq Drill music.  G Herbo's name is kind of lame, ironically I liked Lil Herb better (despite the plethora of 'Lil' rappers), but there are far worse rappers then him on this list.  Though a far cry from the past legends, G Herbo is better than the previous Drill rappers that have appeared on this list (i.e. Chief Keef, Lil Bibby, Lil Durk) and has some potential.  I heard him on Common's song &quot;The Neighborhood&quot; a few years back and liked what he brought to the song, he probably should've made this list in 2014 instead of friend Lil Bibby.  But better late than never.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;Anderson .Paak came out of nowhere last year to make not one, not two, (we know the game), but six appearances on Dr. Dre's final album, Compton, where Anderson .Paak's unique singing ability and occasional raps made him a hot commodity, eventually landing a deal with Dr. Dre's Aftermath Records.  Reppin' Oxnard, California, Anderson .Paak further proved his talents with his major label debut &quot;Malibu,&quot; which along with multiple guest appearances here and there make him a bright star in the future.  But primarily an R&amp;amp;B singer, does he really belong on this list, or is this a sign of things to come with the decline of rapping and more singing based raps as many past and present Freshmen have shown.  Either way, with some of the garbage on this list, it's somewhat ironic that Anderson .Paak finds himself as one of the more talented members of this list.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;21 Savage, the crazy looking guy with the cross tattoo on his forehead, was someone I never heard of prior to this list coming out.  With a few rappers rejecting a spot on the list (Tory Lanez, Bryson Tiller, Post Malone), it seems likely to me 21 Savage made the list as an alternate.  Listening to him, I can confirm that, as he's nothing special.  He sounds gruff but does nothing with it.  Just another typical lame Atlanta rapper with no lyrics.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;Kodak Black, whose hair style is indescribable and god awful, makes me think of the scene from &quot;The Nutty Professor&quot; when the comic Reggie (played by Dave Chappelle) has his hat taken off only to reveal a hideous haircut.  Perhaps Kodak Black should have worn a hat, because he is not only untalented as a rapper, but incredibly ugly to boot with that bizarre haircut.  Even worse, he had to audacity to make a mixtape called &quot;Lil B.I.G. Pac,&quot; complete with a rip off of The Notorious B.I.G.'s  classic &quot;Ready to Die&quot; album cover but with him and his ugly hairdo as the baby.  It's a shame Biggie and Pac aren't alive to see such awful rappers make a mockery out of them and wipe them off the map.  Why anyone thinks this kid is talented is beyond me, he sounds pretty lame to me, but this Pompano Beach, Florida based rapper, currently in jail for a variety of charges, is an obvious example of why quality rap is harder to find and appreciate these days.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;It's times like these that make me appreciate the older rap even more, and even some of the rap I grew up listening to that wasn't so pleasant.  Some of those MC's may have been bad, but at least they are listenable and actually rap.  Many of these new kids being promoted as popular now barely rap and blur the line between rapping and singing.  It really is unfortunate, especially when far better younger MC's are being left off this list time and time again, case in point Mick Jenkins, a young MC from Chicago who has some very thoughtful lyrics relating things to water.  With the quality of rap declining, it's probably better for someone like Mick Jenkins NOT to be on this list.  On the whole, I would say on this list, that Dave East, G Herbo, Lil Dicky and Anderson .Paak are passable, Denzel Curry is okay, Lil Uzi Vert and Desiigner are one-hit wonders, 21 Savage is not good, and Kodak Black and Lil Yachty are awful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/music/2016/08/22/xxl-freshmen-thoughts</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/music/2016/08/22/xxl-freshmen-thoughts</guid>
        
        
        <category>music</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Top 11 Road Trips for 111,111 Miles</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float:left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/111111.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Palouse Falls&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;111,111 Miles&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Today I reached 111,111 miles on my lovely Barracuda, my first and so far only car that I've had for a little over 11 years.  It seemed like just yesterday that I got my first car, as Dad drove me back home from Eugene to spend the weekend at home, only to see a nice 2005 silver Honda Accord DX sitting in the driveway with a big bow on it.  Little did I know that the car was there waiting for me to enjoy it.  For those who don't know the story of its name, the first song I played in the car was Heart's hit song, Barracuda. I've had many wonderful trips with my Barracuda, from the Oregon Coast to Memphis, from Seattle to Chicagoland, 22 states in all.  I've had a lifetime of adventures with Barracuda, from the highs to the lows (though never more than a little scratch).  In honor of my wonderful times on the road, here is a countdown of my Top 11 Road Trips for 111,111 miles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/palouse.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Palouse Falls&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Palouse Falls&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11. Walla Walla: March 18, 2016 - March 19, 2016:&lt;/strong&gt;  Having just starting a full time job at Seterus, I spent my first day off heading to Walla Walla, Washington, where I planned to spend the night in the town and explore the area.  After reaching Walla Walla, I enjoyed a nice little walk around its charming downtown, before crashing for the night.  The following day, after driving through the odd yet photogenic Palouse Hills, stopping in Waitsburg, I reached the highlight of my trip: Palouse Falls, the official waterfall of the State of Washington, which was quite amazing to me.  I then went back home after a nice long day, with a brief stop at Grandma's for dinner (albeit a very late dinner) and some nice Apple Pie (see editors note below)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/painted-hills.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Painted Hills&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Painted Hills&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;    
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10. John Day Fossil Beds: May 20, 2009:&lt;/strong&gt; Though it was only a day trip while I spent a few days in Central Oregon with my Mom, attending a conference in Redmond, I managed to go out to the most stunningly unique place in all of Oregon (perhaps the United States) at the Painted Hills of the John Day Fossil Beds National Monument.  Stuck in the middle of nowhere past Pruneville (sorry... Prineville), with virtually no life in between, the Painted Hills are a reminder of just how special our planet is.  Walking around the Painted Hills and up through the paths is something I will never forget.  I also made it to the Sheep Rock Unit of the John Day Fossil Beds National Monument, which also had plenty of amazing views.  I even found myself a very unique souvenir in the middle of nowhere, but I've already said too much, hehehe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/crater.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Crater Lake&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Crater Lake&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;    
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9. Southern Oregon: September 6, 2014 - September 7, 2014:&lt;/strong&gt; Despite being 4 1/2 hours away from home (and 2 1/2 away from Eugene while I was at the U of O), I never took the drive down to Southern Oregon until two years ago.  Not quite the Willamette Valley but a far cry from everything east of the Cascades, Southern Oregon has its own little charm.  From Shakesphere USA, a.k.a. Ashland, to the charming western town of Jacksonville, there's fun things to see that's unique to Oregon in its own ways.  Though a fire left the weather odd the first day, it cleared up the second day as I made my way to Crater Lake National Park.  Though not my first time there, I really took the time to appreciate Crater Lake this time around and was extremely impressed.  Stops along the way back at Watson and Toketee Falls highlighted my trip, reminding me why Oregon has some of the best waterfalls around.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/smith-rock.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Smith Rock&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Smith Rock&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;       
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8. Smith Rock: May 15, 2009:&lt;/strong&gt; Though just a day trip, my first time at Smith Rock felt like I was there forever, as I went on the hike of my lifetime, starting from the bottom of Smith Rock, reaching the top along Misery Ridge Trail, before heading back down and looping around the River Trail.  There has been no trail I've completed more daunting, more exhilirating nor more utterly insane than Smith Rock.  But believe me, it was worth it, seeing Smith Rock from the top of the trail, being up close with Monkey Face, and perfect views of the Cascades and beyond.  By the time I was done, I was just about exhausted, with the drive home ahead of me.  But if there's any hike I'll remember, it's that one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/sioux-falls.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Sioux Falls&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Sioux Falls&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;        
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7. Sioux Falls: June 4, 2007 - June 5, 2007:&lt;/strong&gt; Heading to Minnesota, Dad and I passed Sioux Falls but didn't see much of the town.  All the excitement that day was from the sudden rainstorm that completely washed away from front bumber full of bugs.  But just 4 hours away from Minneapolis, I thought it would be fun to see what Sioux Falls had to offer.  The centerpiece of the city, the falls for which the city is named after was a great place to visit, with the Big Sioux River flowing through each section, more twists and turns.  There wasn't much to see otherwise, but being in South Dakota also meant 75 mph speed limit, which meant I could really rip it without a worry, reaching briefly up to 90 mph when I knew no cops were around.  After seeing the Mitchell Corn Palace (which I heard about when Dad and I spent the night there), I went back into Minnesota and stopped at the peacefully beautiful Pipestone National Monument, perfectly green and seeing some nice Native American history along the way.  Brief stops in New Ulm and Mankato, Minnesota rounded up a nice trip to see some different parts of Minnesota.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/menominee.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Menominee Pier Light&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Menominee Pier Light&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;     
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6. Green Bay: December 19, 2006 - December 20, 2006:&lt;/strong&gt; My first major trip once I arrived in Minnesota was going to Green Bay, home of the Packers.  Green Bay isn't the most exciting city out there, but there were plenty of adventures along the way, including stops in the funny named Wausau, the northern wooded areas of Wisconsin, mainly the town of Rhinelander and its lovely mythical Hodag, and even the Upper Peninsula of Michigan, where I stopped in the towns of Iron Mountain and Menominee, the latter home of one of my favorite pictures ever of the Menominee Pier Lighthouse.  As for Green Bay itself, I saw Lambeau Field (nice stadium, better than the old Metrodome which thankfully got replaced), the bay itself and the Fox River.  In all, a nice first overnight trip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/reno.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Reno&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Reno&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;      
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Reno: July 18, 2016 - July 21, 2016:&lt;/strong&gt;  Coming in at Number 5 is the trip I took last month, a multi-day extravaganza to Reno, full of fun and excitement.  From driving through California the first day to reach Reno was plenty of fun, seeing Mt. Shasta and stopping amongst its favorite towns (especially Weed), and the amazingly beautiful Burney Falls.  With the main part of Reno right at my fingertips at Circus Circus Reno, seeing the big hotels, the Reno Arch and more.  The second day of my trip brought me to the stunningly blue Lake Tahoe, which after a stop at Carson City, was a breathtaking experience on both sides of the border, along with Stateline right at the border.  The third day of my fun trip saw me walking around Reno, since I needed a break from driving, seeing more of the fun city.  Finally, when it was all said and done, I headed towards home, seeing the Lava Beds National Monument and its historical glory, along with Klamath Falls (whoopdee do!) and Salt Creek Falls (wow!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/st-louis.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;St. Louis&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;St. Louis&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;      
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. St. Louis-Memphis: May 17, 2007 - May 21, 2007:&lt;/strong&gt;  Driving down to St. Louis and Memphis was a lot of fun, even though the trip didn't turn out exactly as I hope, but I'm a better person for it.  Starting my way down through Wisconsin, I first stopped in the city of Beloit, before reaching Rockford, Illinois enjoying views of the Rock River before reaching my main destination of the day, Springfield, Illinois, where I saw plenty of Abraham Lincoln related history and government buildings along the way.  I even had a hamburger with fries in it.  Quite interesting.  The following day brought me to the amazing St. Louis, where upon first entering the city, I was immediately amazed by the beautiful and graceful Gateway Arch overlooking the city.  Thankfully I was stuck in traffic to get a beautiful picture of the skyline from a bridge.  Even more amazing was going into the Gateway Arch and riding its odd and unique tram ride to the top, an experience that can only be described as futuristic.  Seeing a few more places in St. Louis along the way, I made my way down to Memphis, but thanks to the Infamous Cape Girardeau Incident, I was stuck before I got there.  After that nightmare, I made it to Memphis the following day, enjoying Graceland, Beale Street and everything in between, along with a nice order of catfish in a fun musical town.  I thought about turning around from Cape Girardeau, but I knew this was my only moment, and so far, I've been right.  Memphis was a blast, but I made my back back home, spending the day in Tennessee, Mississippi (briefly), Arkansas, Missouri, Illinois and Kentucky (briefly), six states in one day.  Amongst my stops were Cairo, the southernmost point of Illinois, where the Mississippi and Ohio River meets, Collinsville, Illinois where the Cahokia Mounds are located (another great Native American related site) and back to St. Louis to see Forest Park, a beautiful place, before spending the night in Bowling Green, Missouri.  The final day of my trip brought me to Hannibal, Missouri (a.k.a. Mark Twainsville U.S.A.), Iowa City to see the Old State Capitol (and not the corn eating Iowa Hawkeyes) and Cedar Rapids, a nice medium sized city for Iowa's sake.  Suffice to say, I covered lots of ground on this trip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/kansas-city.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Kansas City&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Kansas City&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;      
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Kansas City: January 7, 2007 - January 9, 2007:&lt;/strong&gt; My first superlong trip brought me to Kansas City, Missouri.  Waking up early in excitement, I drove down I-35 and enjoyed the sunrise in Iowa.  With no stops along the way (I figured I'd enjoy Des Moines on the way back), I made it to Kansas City, and became impressed with a city that reminded me a lot of Minneapolis.  I spent the day in Kansas City, seeing the views from the Liberty Memorial (unfortunately, I couldn't climb the memorial itself, but didn't have to do so), the Nelson-Atkins Art Museum with the giant Shuttlecocks and plenty more, before enjoying some authentic Kansas City BBQ at Arthur Bryant's.  The next day brought me to St. Joseph, Missouri (briefly stopping in Kansas) to enjoy some of the sights (I even passed through Oregon, Missouri) before reaching Omaha, Nebraska, where I enjoyed the city and some of what it had to offer (despite it being extremely windy).  The final day of my trip brought me back to Des Moines, where I ended up stopping this time around, to see their golden State Capitol and the city itself.  In all, a fantastic trip with no hiccups along the way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/chicago.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Chicago&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Chicago&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;      
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Milwaukee-Chicago: March 10, 2007 - March 12, 2007:&lt;/strong&gt;  Once in a while, you have a day so perfect that it will forever be known as Adam Day (a day to enjoy all things Adam and have fun).  That was was the second day of this trip, in Chicago.  But first, I had to get there.  With more snow on the grouund in Minnesota and Wisconsin, it was far different from my Kansas City trip that had no major snow, so heading to the Wisconsin Dells, I stopped to enjoy its waterparks that were closed for the season, but photogenic nonetheless.  I also got stuck in the snow, but got help out shortly, and continued my trip down to Madison, the state capital surrounded by two big lakes, and oddly formed city but beautiful and unique nonetheless.  After reaching Milwaukee, I enjoyed visiting the city, from its skyline views from Lake Michigan to the absolutely stunning Milwaukee Art Museum that looked out of this world.  I spent the night there, heading down to Chicago the next day, where everything (except for the cost) ended up being perfect.  From Sears Tower (I don't care what they call it now, it's still Sears Tower to me) to the John Hancock Building, I enjoyed views from the highest buildings in the country.  On the ground, I saw Millenium Park with the beautiful Cloud Gate sculpture that can only be described as flawless, and enjoyed great views of the city from the edge of Lake Michigan.  After stopping in Gary, Indiana (for the sake of being in Indiana, and the see the Jackson's childhood home), I returned to Chicago, where I enjoyed great Chicago cuisine not once, but twice at Portillo's, having a Chicago hot dog (definitely not from Nathan's Hot Dogs at the Mall of America) for lunch and an Italian Beef sandwich for dinner, two Chicago specialities.  Once my perfect day in Chicago was over, I returned to Milwaukee for the night, enduring a horrific line pass the toll-gate into Wisconsin, yuck).  The last leg of my trip brought me to multiple Wisconsin cities along Lake Michigan (Manitowoc and Sheboygan) and Lake Winnebago (Fond du Lac, Oshkosh and Appleton), where I saw plenty of nice things along the way, including Lake Winnebago covered in ice.  With that said and done, my trip was over and I headed back home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/rushmore.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Mt. Rushmore&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Mt. Rushmore&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;      
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Moving to Minnesota: August 29, 2006 - September 1, 2006:&lt;/strong&gt;  For all of my fun and exciting trips, there was only one that defined me to make all of this happen, my move to Minnesota, where my new life at the University of Minnesota was waiting for me.  Although my Dad did most of the driving, having a U-Haul attached to the back of my car, travelling across country to start my new life brought plenty of adventures.  The first day of the trip brought me from Portland all the way to Butte, Montana, driving through Spokane, the Idaho Panhandle and Missoula, Montana along the way.  The next day was filled with all the excitement as we made our way through Yellowstone National Park, where we saw geysers, hot springs and of course, plenty of Bison crossing the road, holding us up in the most unique and eventful traffic stop one could possibly imagine.  After leaving Yellowstone, we drove through Wyoming, going up and down every twist and turn of the Bighorn Mountains in a drive that can only be described as cautious.  After reaching the top and seeing nothing but plains, we spent the night in Sheridan, Wyoming, enjoying a restaurant with crap on walls, Sanford's Pub and Grub.  The next leg of the trip brought us to Mt. Rushmore, which can only be described as beautiful.  Surrounded by the Black Hills, Mt. Rushmore was incredible to see, and a place every proud loving American should see if they get the chance.  After that, it was on to driving through the Great Plains, which certainly wasn't very exciting, but plenty of Wall Drug signs on each side of I-90 available, it was necessary to go through, before reaching Mitchell, South Dakota, with my Barracuda covered in dead bug carcass on the front bumper.  Fortunately, a rainstorm in the night washed it all right off, and just five hours away from my new home in Minneapolis, we finally made it, where plenty of adventures awaited me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/barracuda.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Barracuda&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Barracuda&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;     
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Editor's Note: One night while at my Grandma's, she told me we were having Apple Pie for dessert, which I don't like (but would prefer Grandma's Apple Pie over store bought pie).  I gave her an odd expression, either due to confusion of tiredness.  But ever since then, I always ask my Grandma when we will have Apple Pie, well knowing it's not Apple Pie.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/miscellaneous/2016/08/20/top-11-road-trips-for-111111-miles</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/miscellaneous/2016/08/20/top-11-road-trips-for-111111-miles</guid>
        
        
        <category>miscellaneous</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Making A Murderer - Brendan Dassey's Redemption</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; When I watched Netflix's &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/entertainment/2016/01/19/making-a-murderer-my-thoughts-on-the-steven-avery-case&quot;&gt;Making a Murderer&lt;/a&gt; early in January, the biggest puzzling thing about that case was that Steven Avery's nephew Brendan Dassey was convicted of anything at all, much less for the murder of Teresa Halbach based on a clearly coerced confession.  As news hit yesterday that a Federal judge in Milwaukee agreed, overturning the conviction, I can't help but feel relieved that Dassey got some redemption.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/dassey.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Brendan Dassey.&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Light at the end of the tunnel for Brendan Dassey&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Clearly, Brendan Dassey had nothing to do with the murder.  Watching the confession tape, it's clear that Dassey was manipulated by the cops.  Thankfully, the Federal judge in Milwaukee rightfully pointed out that the police who interviewed him made up false promises and Dassey, with a low IQ, seemed eager to tell the cops what they wanted so he could go back home, as the police promised him.  Of course, they lied their asses off, and Dassey was arrested after the false confession.  With all the talk about police corruption around the country, it's not a surprise they would do this.  Even worse, Dassey, just 16 at the time, did not have his mother as was required, as he needed her help with his low IQ.  And of course, his initial defense attorney was not present and seemed too eager to make a deal with the prosecutors in exchange for grilling Steven Avery.  The Federal judge deemed he was excited by the media coverage and did nothing to help his client.  Had police followed protocol, Dassey's mother would have set them straight, but instead, they bullied him and arrested him while he was too mentally disabled to understand what was going on.  The prosecution has 90 days to bring him back to trial, but since his false confession was the only thing that got him convicted, it's unlikely they would do so.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The bigger question remains, how does affect Steven Avery?  It was my opinion that there wasn't enough evidence to convict him.  Most of the evidence was coincidential at best; the blood in the RAV4, the key found at the dresser, and so on.  Not to mention a lack of motive.  His lawyers fought hard and presented an arguable case in my opinion.  But while some have argued that the Manitowoc County police framed him and planted evidence, I still find this kind of ridiculous.  I do believe they were too eager to investigate Steven Avery since he was the last person to be seen with Teresa Halbach.  Just like the initial rape case he wrongfully spent in prison.  They clearly had a bone to pick with Avery and were so focused on him, they ignored the evidence that pointed to the real rapist.  It's possible they planted evidence, but I don't think they killed her.  Someone with a grudge against Avery could've very well killed Halbach.  After all, they never found the body.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;As for Brendan Dassey, the system was rigged against him, as it is for many people falsely accussed and convicted of crimes.  The police were so eager to place him at the scene of the crime that they bullied him into telling them what they wanted to hear to fit their story.  It happens to too many people, targeting those who are vulnerable, mental disabilties amongst them.  How the jury convicted him of all charges; murder, rape and mutilation of a corpse, which Steven Avery wasn't even convicted of all those charges, is quite puzzling.  Different jury aside and different lawyers (not as good as Avery's), the jurors took his false words at face value and didn't consider anything else.  That the was only evidence they had against him, basically.  Now that the conviction has been overthrown, they have nothing against him.  It goes to show how corrupt our legal system and police officers can get.  I've read plenty of stories, more so recently, about mass police corruption in Baltimore, Cleveland and Ferguson, painting a grim picture of officers taking advantage of minorities, and it can certainly happen to anyone the police wants to target.  While it's easy for some to claim &quot;The police is always right,&quot; while claiming &quot;It's wrong to accuse police of acting stupidly,&quot; clearly anyone can be corrupt, including those who serve.  At the end of the day, Brendan Dassey got his redemption and hopefully those police officers would get punished for not following protocol.  There are too many good police officers getting lumped with the bad ones.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;It's good to know that Brendan Dassey got his conviction overturned.  If I were him, I would file a lawsuit against the Manitowoc County police, like Steven Avery did years earlier.  It would also be good for Dassey to move as far away from the county as he reasonably could.  Probably not realistic, but he deserves better, just like Steven Avery.  Now we'll wait to see what happens to him.  Can they prove his innocence?  Will they get better results on the blood in the RAV4?  What about the biased juror?  There are way too many questions left unanswered about Steven Avery's case.  In the meantime, we can rejoice that Brendan Dassey got his redemption for something he clearly had no involvement in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/entertainment/2016/08/13/making-a-murderer-brendan-dasseys-redemption</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/entertainment/2016/08/13/making-a-murderer-brendan-dasseys-redemption</guid>
        
        
        <category>entertainment</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Pledge</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.article span {
	font-size: 1.1em;
	font-weight: bold;
}
@media (max-width: 512px) {
	h3, p, img {
		clear: both;
	}
	.blog-pic {
		max-width: 100%;
	}
	.blog-pic h4 {
		max-width: 100%;	
	}
}
&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Three months from today, on November 8th, the country I call home, the United States of America, will elect a new President. Our country's future is at stake.  On one hand is Hillary Clinton, Former First Lady, Senator of New York and Secretary of State.  On the other hand is Donald Trump, who can simply be described as a Tyrannical Racist Ugly Misogynistic Pig.  I am sick and tired of hearing about this fool.  Everything he says is stupid, childish and filled with hate.  There are a plethora of reasons not to vote for this degenerate, I've managed to find one-hundred reasons, but the reasons don't stop there.  He has zero qualities of a worthy President and even less qualities of a proud American. This is why I am taking a pledge to no longer refer to him by his name and pledge to start calling him simply as The Idiot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Happy &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/CincoDeMayo?src=hash&quot;&gt;#CincoDeMayo&lt;/a&gt;! The best taco bowls are made in Trump Tower Grill. I love Hispanics! &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/ufoTeQd8yA&quot;&gt;https://t.co/ufoTeQd8yA&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/k01Mc6CuDI&quot;&gt;pic.twitter.com/k01Mc6CuDI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Donald J. Trump (@realDonaldTrump) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/728297587418247168&quot;&gt;May 5, 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Claiming to like Hispanics by eating 'their' food is a stupid attempt at getting their support.&lt;/h4&gt;	
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;On Immigration&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Idiot is flat out wrong on immigration.  When the Idiot first entered the race, he managed to set the tone for his whole campaign by saying &lt;span&gt;&quot;When Mexico sends its people, they're not sending their best... They're bringing drugs. They're bringing crime. They're rapists. And some, I assume, are good people.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  This obviously appeals to racist bigots who hate all things Hispanic, but most immigrants are good people and only leads to discrimination against Hispanics in general, no matter their legal status.  He even had the nerve to ask &lt;span&gt;&quot;Well, somebody's doing the raping, Don (Lemon)! I mean somebody's doing it! Who's doing the raping? Who's doing the raping?&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  As if every rapist in the United States is somehow undocumented and from Mexico?  Not true!  The Idiot doesn't have any ideas to fix our broken immigration system other than to say &lt;span&gt;&quot;Mexico's going to pay for the wall.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  Historically speaking, walls have never been effective and anyone wanting to cross the border will find ways to get over the stupid wall.  It's especially stupid to think that Mexico will pay for something they don't want.  Stronger border security is the best way to go.  Not bashing all undocumented immigrants, singling them out for committing crimes when crimes are committed by all races, genders and religions, or building a stupid wall.  The immigration system isn't perfect, but with over 11 million undocumented immigrants, the solution isn't as easy as treating all of them as criminals and deporting them.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;On Terrorism&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Idiot is flat out wrong on terrorism.  Keeping us safe is not as easy as saying &lt;span&gt;&quot;Donald J. Trump is calling for a total and complete shutdown of Muslims entering the United States.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  This does nothing to stop attacks like the ones in Boston, Orlando, Fort Hood and San Bernardino, all committed by Muslim-Americans, many of whom were born in America, and like his attacks on immigrants, unfairly places the blame on foreigners, treating them all as potential criminals rather than people.  An actual strategy to stop Terrorism requires working with our allies to attack Terrorists, rather than declaring war on all of Islam, as the Idiot has clearly done multiple times &lt;span&gt;&quot;I think Islam hates us.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  That only encourages Terrorists like ISIS to continue their fight and justify their message that somehow &quot;The West hates them,&quot; even though that's not true.  They're already using the Idiot's words for propaganda.  This is from someone who didn't think ISIS was even our fight to begin with, &lt;span&gt;&quot;Let Syria and ISIS fight. Why do we care? Let ISIS and Syria fight. And let Russia, they're in Syria already, let them fight ISIS.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  The Idiot's methods for defeating Terrorism include committing war crimes, &lt;span&gt;&quot;The other thing with the terrorists is you have to take out their families, when you get these terrorists, you have to take out their families,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; creating a national registry for Muslims &lt;span&gt;&quot;I would certainly implement that, absolutely,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; singling out refugees as the only ones capable of committing attacks at home with the false idea that &lt;span&gt;&quot;There is 'no system to vet' refugees from the Middle East,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; and using three little words, &lt;span&gt;&quot;In his remarks today, President Obama disgracefully refused to even say the words 'Radical Islam.' For that reason alone, he should step down. If Hillary Clinton, after this attack, still cannot say the two words 'Radical Islam' she should get out of this race for the Presidency.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  Coming from a man who claims &lt;span&gt;&quot;I know more about ISIS than the generals do,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; it's not surprising with his idiotic ideas that he knows nothing about fighting terrorists or the Middle East in general.  Of course, when 49 innocent people were killed by an ISIS supporter in Orlando, all this Idiot could do was take credit for being 'right' about terrorism, even though he was dead wrong &lt;span&gt;&quot;Appreciate the congrats for being right on radical Islamic terrorism, I don't want congrats, I want toughness and vigilance. We must be smart!&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/fake-tweet.png&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Idiot&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;This Idiot thought this was true.  It's not even remotely true.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;On Race Relations&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Idiot is flat out wrong on race relations.  Obama is not responsible for making race relations worse, as the Idiot claims &lt;span&gt;&quot;I'm a unifier, unlike our president now, I'm a unifier&quot;&lt;/span&gt;.  It's people like The Idiot who refuse to accept the fact that we elected an African American President (twice).  It's ridiculous for the Idiot to claim that blacks are responsible for most gun crimes in the country, all while siding with White Supremacists and not being outraged by their support &lt;span&gt;&quot;I don't know anything about David Duke.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;   The Idiot targets blacks, Hispanics, and Muslims, yet with White Supremacists, he retweets their racist, anti-Semitic imagery while running a campaign tailored for their policies, no matter what the Idiot says otherwise.  That's why David Duke is so enthusiastic about The Idiot's campaign.  The Idiot frequently injects racist names when discussing African Americans &lt;span&gt;&quot;Our great African American President hasn't exactly had a positive impact on the thugs who are so happily and openly destroying Baltimore!&quot;&lt;/span&gt; or with Hispanics &lt;span&gt;&quot;The protesters in New Mexico were thugs who were flying the Mexican flag. The rally inside was big and beautiful, but outside, criminals!&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  This divisive attitude has fueled the anger that had led to more shootings and violence throughout the nation.  For someone who claims &lt;span&gt;&quot;I am least racist person there is,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; he has done nothing but attacked African Americans, Hispanics, Muslims, Asians and just about every other minority with bigoted hate-filled spew.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/donald-trump-star.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Idiot&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;The Idiot's campaign is catered for White Supremacists: That's why he always retweets their ideas rather than dismiss them as hate-speech.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;On Guns&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Idiot is flat out wrong on guns.  No one is trying to get rid of the 2nd Amendment, despite the Idiot claims that &lt;span&gt;&quot;Hillary Clinton wants to abolish the Second Amendment.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  Increasing background checks a little is not the mass destruction of gun rights.  It's protected to keep the guns out of the hands from those who don't need them; criminals and terrorists.  These opinions are bought by the NRA, and their corruption and lack of empathy on gun shootings must stop. Having a gun on you doesn't guarantee your survival from an attack, &lt;span&gt;&quot;The bullets were going one way, not the other way. And if they were, if somebody had protection, a few people, not all, a few people had protection we would not have had 130 people dead.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  Too bad those who commit these acts are more prepared and have stronger weapons than a simple handgun for protecting.  Handguns won't stop suicide bombers who want to die, powerful assault weapons designed to kill or trucks driven by maniacs.  Requiring teachers to have guns will make those wanting to shoot up a school go after the teacher first, &lt;span&gt;&quot;Let me tell you, if you had a couple teachers with guns in that room, you would have been a hell of a lot better off.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  We can't live our lives waiting for someone to shoot us, and we shouldn't have to.  It's way too easy for criminals to get a hold of guns, with all the loopholes the NRA wants to leave open.  This Idiot even claims that Hillary Clinton wants to release violent criminals from jail, claiming &lt;span&gt;&quot;This is Hillary Clinton's agenda, too, to release the violent criminals from jail. She wants them all released.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  Too many people have died and nothing is being done about it, yet The Idiot only shows compassion for the victims and their loved ones if the perpetrator is undocumented, Muslim or Black.  All victims of gun violence deserve the same love and attention, regardless of who killed them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;These crimes won&amp;#39;t be happening if I&amp;#39;m elected POTUS. Killer should have never been here. &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/AmericaFirst?src=hash&quot;&gt;#AmericaFirst&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/XDGKaj0ico&quot;&gt;https://t.co/XDGKaj0ico&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Donald J. Trump (@realDonaldTrump) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/748920081942327296&quot;&gt;July 1, 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/donald-trump4.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Idiot&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;This Idiot thinks foreign policy is like running a Miss Universe pageant.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;On The Economy&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Idiot is wrong on the Economy.  How can someone filthy rich &lt;span&gt;&quot;I'm Really Rich!&quot;&lt;/span&gt; understand the plight of the common man?  Giving the rich huge tax breaks won't trickle down the economy.  This Idiot has taken advantage of every rule and loophole to maximize his profit without any regard for anyone but himself, &lt;span&gt;&quot;It's none of your business, you'll see it when I release. But I fight very hard to pay as little tax as possible.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  It's no wonder he refuses to release his taxes.  Take it from someone who's filed Bankruptcy four times &lt;span&gt;&quot;I have never gone bankrupt, by the way&quot;&lt;/span&gt;, all while stifling contractors and taking the money for himself.  This is from someone who hires foreign workers almost exclusively, the same ones he bashes on a regular basis, while thinking it's easy to get jobs back here &lt;span&gt;&quot;We're going to bring businesses back. We're going to have businesses that are now in Mexico come back to New Hampshire and you can tell them to go f*** themselves.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  That's not the economy working for all, that's the economy working for him.  We need someone who understands how to get money for the middle class, not someone who thinks wages are too high &lt;span&gt;&quot;But, taxes too high, wages too high, we're not going to be able to compete against the world. I hate to say it, but we have to leave it the way it is. People have to go out, they have to work really hard and have to get into that upper stratosphere.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  They're not!  And we certainly need someone who will get us out of debt, not someone who loves debt &lt;span&gt;&quot;I'm the king of debt. I love debt,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; or thinks printing more money is a good idea &lt;span&gt;&quot;You never have to default because you print the money.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/Don_Vito_08&quot;&gt;@Don_Vito_08&lt;/a&gt;: &amp;quot;A picture is worth a thousand words&amp;quot; &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump&quot;&gt;@realDonaldTrump&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/LyingTed?src=hash&quot;&gt;#LyingTed&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/NeverCruz?src=hash&quot;&gt;#NeverCruz&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/MELANIATRUMP&quot;&gt;@MELANIATRUMP&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/5bvVEwMVF8&quot;&gt;pic.twitter.com/5bvVEwMVF8&lt;/a&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Donald J. Trump (@realDonaldTrump) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/712850174838771712&quot;&gt;March 24, 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;On Women&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Idiot is flat out wrong on Women.  He calls them names, objectifies them solely on their looks &lt;span&gt;&quot;Look at that face! Would anyone vote for that? Can you imagine that, the face of our next president?,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; proclaims they're playing the 'woman card' to win &lt;span&gt;&quot;The only card she (Hillary Clinton) has to play is the woman's card,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; and makes vulgar jokes about menstruation &lt;span&gt;&quot;You could see there was blood coming out of her eyes. Blood coming out of her wherever,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; and rape &lt;span&gt;&quot;...she got schlonged, she lost, I mean she lost.&quot;&lt;/span&gt; The Idiot thinks women should be punished for abortions, &lt;span&gt;&quot;There has to be some form of punishment.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  When it comes to equal pay, the Idiot claims woman need to work harder to get the same salary as a man when they already do, &lt;span&gt;&quot;You're gonna make the same if you do as good a job.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  The Idiot even selected extreme Anti-Abortionist Mike Pence as his running mate.  Shouldn't expect anything less from a womanizing unfaithful husband who would date his own daughter if he could, &lt;span&gt;&quot;If Ivanka weren't my daughter, perhaps I'd be dating her&quot;&lt;/span&gt; and raped his first wife.  Women are people too, not objects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/donald-trump7.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Idiot&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;This Idiot hates Women.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;On Healthcare&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Idiot is flat out wrong on healthcare.  He has no actual ideas to fix Obamacare, other than to claim that he will &lt;span&gt;&quot;Replace with something terrific.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  That's code for nothing.  Republican's have had years to try to improve Obamacare but have done nothing but want to get rid of it and go back to the way things were.  Get some ideas or don't say anything at all. By the way, the website works, &lt;span&gt;&quot;The $5 billion website for Obamacare - never worked. Still doesn't work.&quot;&lt;/span&gt; It really works.  And vaccines don't cause Autism &lt;span&gt;&quot;We had so many instances [in which] a child had a vaccine, and came back and a week back had a tremendous fever, got very very sick, and now is autistic.&quot;&lt;/span&gt; Anyone who believes that is an idiot, as this has been disproven for years now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;An: Media fell all over themselves criticizing what DonaldTrump &amp;quot;may have insinuated about &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/POTUS&quot;&gt;@POTUS&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;quot; But he&amp;#39;s right: &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/bIIdYtvZYw&quot;&gt;https://t.co/bIIdYtvZYw&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Donald J. Trump (@realDonaldTrump) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/743075154507489280&quot;&gt;June 15, 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;The Idiot claims proof Obama supports ISIS, but this is obviously not true.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;On President Obama&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Idiot is flat out wrong on Obama.  President Obama was born in Hawaii, not Kenya &lt;span&gt;&quot;His grandmother in Kenya said he was born in Kenya and she was there and witnessed the birth, okay?&quot;&lt;/span&gt; and he's a Christian, not Muslim &lt;span&gt;&quot;I wonder if President Obama would have attended the funeral of Justice Scalia if it were held in a Mosque? Very sad that he did not go!&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  This was proven years ago, yet the Idiot still thinks he's a Kenyan-born Muslim and refuses to correct anyone with the truth, even blaming Hillary for the the Birther movement which he is the king of &lt;span&gt;&quot;Just remember, the birther movement was started by Hillary Clinton in 2008. She was all in!&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  The Idiot claims Obama supports terrorism &lt;span&gt;&quot;President Obama claims to know our enemy, and yet he continues to prioritize our enemy over our allies, and for that matter, the American people,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; and has divided America based on color &lt;span&gt;&quot;The irresponsible rhetoric of our President, who has used the pulpit of the presidency to divide us by race and color, has made America a more dangerous environment for everyone.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;   The Idiot claims Obama is the worst President ever &lt;span&gt;&quot;'In politics, and in life, ignorance is not a virtue.' This is a primary reason that President Obama is the worst president in U.S. history!&quot;&lt;/span&gt; None of this is true.  Obama gave the order to kill Osama bin Laden, speaks greatly about people of all races and color and got us out of the Recession.  The Idiot, like every extreme Republican, refuses to believe One Word the President has ever said and will say anything against him (Not one Republican criticized George W. Bush for not stating those three little words but yet it's only an issue with Obama as President).  End of Story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/trump2.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Idiot&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;This Idiot sounds like a spokesperson for Greenhouse-Gas emitting companies&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;On Climate Change&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Idiot is flat out wrong on Climate Change.  No, Global Warming is not a hoax invented by the Chinese &lt;span&gt;&quot;The concept of global warming was created by and for the Chinese in order to make U.S. manufacturing non-competitive.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  97% of all Scientists agree it's real.  And just because it's snowing one place &lt;span&gt;&quot;Snowing in Texas and Louisiana, record setting freezing temperatures throughout the country and beyond. Global warming is an expensive hoax!&quot;&lt;/span&gt; doesn't mean it's snowing on the opposite side of the world.  That's why we have four seasons.  By the way, we haven't heard anything from the Idiot regarding Flint's water problems.  Who really cares about the environment? Not the Idiot wanting support from the very organizations polluting the Earth for profit.  It is a bigger potential concern than Terrorism, it affect everybody, including Terrorists.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/donald-trump6.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Idiot&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;This Idiot expects us to &quot;Believe Me&quot; with numbers.  Ridiculous!&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;On Numbers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Idiot is flat out wrong on Numbers. Pick a number, any number.  If used by Donald Trump, there's a 1000% chance it's not the right number and a complete over exaggeration of the truth.  &lt;span&gt;&quot;Don't believe those phony numbers when you hear 4.9 and 5 percent unemployment. The number's probably 28, 29, as high as 35. In fact, I even heard recently 42 percent.&quot;&lt;/span&gt; The unemployment rate may not show a complete picture, but it's far closer to 5% than 42%.  &lt;span&gt;&quot;I am now hearing it's 30 million, it could be 34 million, which is a much bigger problem.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  Try 11 million undocumented immigrants. &lt;span&gt;&quot;We're the highest taxed nation in the world.&quot;&lt;/span&gt; Not even close. &lt;span&gt;&quot;If you look at what's going on in this country, African-American youth is an example: 59 percent unemployment rate; 59 percent.&quot;&lt;/span&gt; Try 19 percent. &lt;span&gt;&quot;We have 93 million people out of work. They look for jobs, they give up, and all of a sudden, statistically, they're considered employed.&quot;&lt;/span&gt; Closer to 21 million, and no, they're not considered employed. Not even close. &lt;span&gt;&quot;He's gonna tax you people at 90 percent.&quot;&lt;/span&gt; Bernie Sanders wouldn't do that.  When the Idiot mentions a number, do yourself a favor, don't believe it, you can't believe a word he says.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/donald-trump2.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Idiot&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;This Idiot thinks Russia is a better country than the United States.  WRONG!&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;On Leadership Qualties&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Idiot is flat out wrong on Leadership qualities.  Being a great leader is willing to work others.  The Idiot on the other hand thinks dictators like Vladimir Putin &lt;span&gt;&quot;I will tell you in terms of leadership he is getting an 'A,' and our president is not doing so well,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; and Kim Jong Un &lt;span&gt;&quot;It's incredible. He wiped out the uncle, he wiped out this one, that one. I mean this guy doesn't play games. And we can't play games with him,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; are great leaders.  He calls Obama weak and criticizes his allies &lt;span&gt;&quot;He's (Vladimir Putin) making mincemeat out of our president,&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  while praising Saddam Hussein for killing terrorists &lt;span&gt;&quot;He was a bad guy -- really bad guy. But you know what? He did well? He killed terrorists. He did that so good. They didn't read them the rights. They didn't talk. They were terrorists. Over.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;.  Too bad Saddam Hussein was a well-known sponsor of terrorism and protected groups that aligned with him.  These are not great leadership qualities.  Leaders have empathy for others, while the Idiot hasn't shown empathy for anyone but himself.  That type of leadership is more for dictators.  A foreshadowing of what life would be if this Idiot was elected President.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/donald-trump-mocks-disabled-reporter.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Idiot&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;This is what The Idiot looks like when he makes fun of someone's disability&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;On Character&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Idiot is flat out wrong on Character.  This Idiot has no redeeming characteristics.  Instead, this Idiot acts like a five year old when arguing with others &lt;span&gt;&quot;He started it. I didn't start it.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;, makes up stupid childish nicknames &lt;span&gt;&quot;Lyin' Ted Cruz denied that he had anything to do with the G.Q. model photo post of Melania. That's why we call him Lyin' Ted!&quot;&lt;/span&gt; makes childish threats out of spite &lt;span&gt;&quot;The wall just got 10 feet taller, believe me,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; makes jokes about his genitalia &lt;span&gt;&quot;And, he (Marco Rubio) referred to my hands if they're small, something else is small,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; claims to have seen videos that don't exist &lt;span&gt;&quot;And I watched in Jersey City, N.J., where thousands and thousands of people were cheering as that building was coming down. Thousands of people were cheering,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; repeats ridiculously false conspiracy theories &lt;span&gt;&quot;His (Ted Cruz's) father was with Lee Harvey Oswald prior to Oswald being, you know, shot. I mean the whole thing is ridiculous. What is this, right, prior to his being shot? And nobody even brings it up,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; mocks POW's &lt;span&gt;&quot;He's (John McCain) not a war hero -- he's a war hero because he was captured. I like people that weren't captured.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;, stereotypes people based solely on their name &lt;span&gt;&quot;Take a look. I mean, you look at the names, you look at what's happened. You tell me,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; makes fun of someone's disability &lt;span&gt;&quot;Now, the poor guy, you've got to see this guy: 'Uhh, I don't know what I said. Uhh, I don't remember,' he's going like 'I don't remember. Maybe that's what I said'&quot;&lt;/span&gt; promotes violence at his rallies &lt;span&gt;&quot;Knock the crap out of them, would you? Seriously. OK? Just knock the hell -- I promise you, I will pay for the legal fees. I promise, I promise,&quot;&lt;/span&gt;, threatens violence at other people's rallies &lt;span&gt;&quot;Bernie Sanders is lying when he says his disruptors aren't told to go to my events. Be careful Bernie, or my supporters will go to yours!&quot;&lt;/span&gt;, claims he wouldn't lose supporters if he shot someone &lt;span&gt;&quot;I could stand in the middle of 5th Avenue and shoot somebody, and I wouldn't lose voters,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; claims an American born judge is out to get him solely on his ethnicity &lt;span&gt;&quot;I have a judge who is a hater of Donald Trump, a hater. He's a hater, we believe, Mexican, which is great.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;, verbally attacks a Muslim woman in grief of losing her son in the Iraq War for not speaking &lt;span&gt;&quot;If you look at his wife, she was standing there. She had nothing to say. She probably, maybe she wasn't allowed to have anything to say. You tell me,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; diminishes the value of a life lost in war &lt;span&gt;&quot;I've made a lot of sacrifices. I work very, very hard. I've created thousands and thousands of jobs, tens of thousands of jobs, built great structures,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; all while claiming to be the victim every time someone says something negative about him &lt;span&gt;&quot;I was viciously attacked by Mr. Khan at the Democratic Convention. Am I not allowed to respond? Hillary voted for the Iraq war, not me!&quot;&lt;/span&gt; This Idiot has no redeeming qualities on character and can't take the slightest criticism without scorching the Earth every time someone goes after him.  The First Amendment is for all Americans, not just for The Idiot and his followers.  No person would ever act this way to others, let alone a President to his country.  This Idiot will believe anything that's on the Internet &lt;span&gt;&quot;I don't know, all I know is what's on the internet,&quot;&lt;/span&gt;, even if it's clearly not true...&lt;span&gt;&quot;USSS did an excellent job stopping the maniac running to the stage. He has ties to ISIS. Should be in jail!  &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/tkzbHg7wyD&quot;&gt;https://t.co/tkzbHg7wyD&lt;/a&gt;?ssr=true&quot;&lt;/span&gt; unless it's about him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/donald-trump3.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Idiot&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;This Idiot hates America, he'd be glad to take everything from us just to enrich himself.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;On America&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Idiot is flat out wrong on America.  We're not on fire, crime isn't rising, refugees aren't coming in to attack us, immigrants aren't taking all of our jobs, and not everything is Obama and Hillary Clinton's fault, despite the Idiot's claim that &lt;span&gt;&quot;It's(The Obama Administration) failed them at every level.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  This Idiot made a rambling speech at the RNC about how bad things are, how he alone can fix everything as fast as snapping your fingers, &lt;span&gt;&quot;Nobody knows the system better than me, which is why I alone can fix it,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; all while accusing Democrats of destroying the very fabric of this nation.  Last time I checked, the Economy is better than it was in 2008, people have more rights, more access to healthcare and believe it or not, more safe than in 2008.  America is not perfect, but it's not a war zone &lt;span&gt;&quot;There are places in America that are among the most dangerous in the world. You go to places like Oakland. Or Ferguson. The crime numbers are worse. Seriously.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;, and insulting our Armed forces &lt;span&gt;&quot;Our military is a disaster,&quot;&lt;/span&gt;, our Generals &lt;span&gt;He's (General John Allen) a failed general,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; and American citizens &lt;span&gt;&quot;I Love the Poorly Educated,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; is as un-American as you can get.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/donald-trump1.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Idiot&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;This Idiot is UGLY&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;On Honesty&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Idiot is flat out wrong on honesty.  He's a con-artist and a fraud, plain and simple.  He stole millions of dollars from people through his sham of a University while pretending it wasn't true &lt;span&gt;&quot;We (Trump University) have an 'A' from the Better Business Bureau,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; told people he'd love for a housing bubble to occur to reap the benefits, &lt;span&gt;&quot;I sort of hope that happens because then people like me would go in and buy,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; and refused to pay contractors for work they did on his crappy Bankrupted buildings.  The Idiot pretends to be an outsider &lt;span&gt;&quot;I'm self-funding my own campaign,&quot;&lt;/span&gt; but his opinions can be bought, &lt;span&gt;&quot;I, on the other hand, received the early and strong endorsement of the National Rifle Association.&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  The Idiot even thinks he's attractive despite his ridiculous hair and ugly looking chin, &lt;span&gt;&quot;It is very hard for them to attack me on looks, because I am so good looking.&quot;&lt;/span&gt; He helped the USFL win a landmark $1 from a lawsuit against the NFL, terrorized renters on his properties in the 80s to force them out, and continues to hire employees as cheap as he can to pocket the extra dough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;In Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When it's all said and done, this Idiot is the worst Presidential nominee in the history of the United States.  He is a historically awful, pathetic, stupid, bigoted, racist, tyrannical, misogynist, narcissistic, greedy, selfish, untrustworthy piece of shit.  I'm tired of hearing about him.  I'm tired of his stupid games.  I'm tired of everything about him.  He has completely destroyed the Republican Party as we know it, for better or for worse.  Electing him President will start a World War, crash our Economy into a complete Depression, make all of us extremely unsafe, and worst of all, make America look like a complete f**in' joke.  America is better than this.  I hope you all join me and boycott his name and start calling him The Idiot.  We must do everything we can to make sure he doesn't take over the United States.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/08/08/my-pledge</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/08/08/my-pledge</guid>
        
        
        <category>politics</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
