<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adam's Blog</title>
    <description>A blog about whatever is on Adam's mind.</description>
    <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 07:15:32 -0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 07:15:32 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Football Week Ten Thoughts</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; It's 'I Hate USC' week as the Oregon Ducks head down to SoCal for the first time since 2012.  I really hate USC, and I make it no secret, but you can read all about that &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2015/11/21/usc-my-anti-christ&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.  But there are more important things than bashing all things USC.  The Gophers played Purdue and with the official playoff rankings out, the chase really begins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/western-michigan.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Western Michigan&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Western Michigan QB Zach Terrell&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;The Gophers hosted Purdue, a team that's been at the bottom of the pole the past few years but has nothing to lose.  Their style of play, more pass-heavy than the traditional Big Ten team makes Purdue a potentially sneaky team.  And in the first half, Purdue kept it close, taking the lead just before the half after a dumb interception from Mitch Leidner.  But the second half was a different story, as Rodney Smith led the way on the ground and the Gophers defense took over, winning 44-31.  Shannon Brooks was injured and not much is known why, or for how long.  They need him back to complement Rodney Smith, as the schedule gets tougher for the last three games: Nebraska, Northwestern and rival Wisconsin.  The Gophers have won four straight and have surpassed their win total last year, but the meat of their schedule is now.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;That leads into the game against the Cheaters.  Of course, Oregon hasn't been themselves this year and their defense is young and broken.  But perhaps an upset is in the books.  Unfortunately, that was not the case as the Cheaters won 45-20.  Not much to say here, but we can solace in the fact that the Cheaters are still overrated and unworthy of the hype.  They were blown out by Alabama, blown out by Stanford, and most importantly, lost a close game to Utah, the latter which will probably keep them out of the Pac-12 title game.  So the Cheaters are still an overrated piece of crap.  Next up for Oregon, the only other dominant team in the Pac-12 North up until this year; Stanford.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The official College Football Playoff Rankings have begun, and surprise surprise, Texas A&amp;amp;M finds itself ranked ahead of Washington.  First ranking aside, another sign of SEC-bias.  But obviously, it's the final ranking that matters.  But they won't be ranked fourth in the next poll, they lost to Mississippi State, losing their QB Trevor Knight in the process.  That's what we call a big jinx.  Also of note is Clemson jumping ahead of Michigan.  With wins against Louisville and Florida State, Clemson has definitely had a tougher schedule to this point.  As Baylor, Texas A&amp;amp;M and Nebraska lost, we can eliminate them.  That leaves the following teams: Alabama, Michigan, Clemson, Washington, Ohio State, Louisville, Auburn, Wisconsin and Oklahoma.  The final three teams have been added to the list but the former six are the best shots at this point.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/sf27.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Sam Foltz&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Proof that kindness in humanity still exists, courtesy of Ohio State.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;    
    &lt;p&gt;Baylor was completely obliterated against TCU.  Thank god, I've never liked Baylor and their imitation high speed offense.  And unlike Oregon, who made two national title games this decade, Baylor couldn't win the big game. Goodbye Baylor.  --- Washington State is now ranked and won big against Arizona, 69-7.  Who knows how high they'd be ranked if not for their loss to Eastern Washington.  But much kudos to them.  And they're still unbeaten in conference play.  If they keep up the pace, they could finally get the ESPN GameDay crew to come to Pullman, as the Apple Cup is at Pullman this year. --- I've always enjoyed the smaller schools, so I got my eye on Western Michigan, as the only unbeaten team left amongst the non-major conference schools.  They are clearly the second best team in the state of Michigan, as Michigan State lost again to Illinois.  How did the Spartans fall so far off the face of the planet?  But Western Michigan, who beat Northwestern in the first game of the season and beat Illinois as well, two more Big Ten opponents than Michigan State has beaten, has a shot to finish unbeaten.  We'll see what happens. --- Hearing about the death of Nebraska punter Sam Foltz and all the tributes their opponents have given them reminds me of how great humanity can be.  Mike Riley is absolutely the right coach for Nebraska and despite his mistakes in the past, is man enough to admit his errors and make things right. It should be noted that this was the only nice thing Ohio State did against Nebraska; they blew them out of the water, 62-3. --- With that said, so here are my picks for Top Ten:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alabama&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michigan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clemson&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Washington&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ohio State&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Louisville&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wisconsin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Auburn (NR)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Penn State (NR)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oklahoma (NR)&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/11/05/college-football-week-ten-thoughts</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/11/05/college-football-week-ten-thoughts</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>One week in the Lakers Season - The 2016 Edition</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last year, I wrote about the Lakers season one week into the year, with much chagrin, as the Lakers took a while to win.  This season is a completely different story.  Would I call them a playoff team at this point?  Of course not, but there's a much different vibe this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/img/jordan-clarkson.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Jordan Clarkson&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;h4&gt;Jordan Clarkson's been a big steal for the Lakers&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;I would define the Lakers right now as a group of young ducklings.  Last season, it was all about Kobe's farewell show.  Now, it's more about the chase into seeing which of the young Lakers develops to be the next great one.  That to me is a good reason to watch these Lakers.  I don't have a favorite player, but rather a nice group of players that can mold into my favorite.  Right now, the Lakers are 2-3, having beating two of my least favorite players (and former teammates), James Harden (with Houston) and Dwight Howard (now with Atlanta).  Their win in Atlanta was impressive as road games, especially the last of four straight road games, coming back from a deficit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of my biggest questions of the Lakers drafting D'Angelo Russell last year was the development of equally talented guard Jordan Clarkson.  Fortunately, new coach Luke Walton found the perfect way to utilize him, as the team's sixth man.  Even better, Clarkson has accepted that role with good results so far.  The type of player the Lakers need.  I was surprised when I first learned of this, especially with Nick Young now the starting shooting guard.  There were doubts he'd even make the roster.  But it's easy to say his ex-girlfriend Izzy Azalea (ugh) was killing his career.  At the moment, it's been a good call, and Nick Young has improved, especially on the defensive end.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/img/larry-nance-jr.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Larry Nance Jr.&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;h4&gt;Larry Nance Jr. can dunk!&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tonight the Lakers return home to host the Golden State Warriors, now with Kevin Durant, wearing their throwback 1986-1987 champion Lakers jerseys.  Though the Warriors are obviously the better team right now, the Lakers are at home and Golden State had a hard fought matchup against Durant's former team.  But the Lakers did beat the Warriors in their last regular season game, rather convincingly.  Never say never.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Lakers have a nice future ahead of them.  They've brought in some nice young players: D'Angelo Russell, Jordan Clarkson and Julius Randle.  They have nice veteran leaders in Luol Deng and Lou Williams.  Their bench is filled with energetic players, from the aforementioned Clarkson and Williams to Larry Nance Jr., whose dunking abilities perfectly describes his play.  They're missing a bonafide star, but Russell's in his second year and much improved from his rookie year when he was stuck with Kobe.  Brandon Ingram is a rookie and it will take him time.  We'll see if Randle or Clarkson can become All-Star's.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/basketball/2016/11/04/one-week-into-the-lakers-season-2016</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/basketball/2016/11/04/one-week-into-the-lakers-season-2016</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>basketball</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Football Week Nine Thoughts</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Week Nine featured two decent matchups on my end.  For the Gophers, it was the week to clinch bowl eligibility.  For Oregon, it was another week to end their hideous skid.  How did Week Nine play out?  Read here for my thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/shannon-brooks.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Shannon Brooks&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Shannon Brooks&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Two seasons ago, when Minnesota made its first New Year's Day bowl since 1962, the Gophers were upset by Illinois, a lowlight for that season.  This year, the Gophers needed not to repeat that game.  And thankfully, the banged-up Fighting Illini were no match for the Gophers ground game and their defense shined.  Illinois had two key turnovers in the first half leading to both Minnesota touchdowns as the Gophers easily won 40-17. Illinois was down to their third-string freshman QB Jeff George Jr. (son of infamous NFL QB Jeff George).  Their top receiver, Malik Turner got hurt in the first quarter from an unfortunate hit from safety Duke McGhee, who was ejected for targeting.  With a particular windy day, the Gophers ground game made it easy for them, as the Gophers are now bowl eligible at 6-2.  But the season's not over and they still have a shot at the Big Ten West title, which definitely won't come easy with their last three games against Nebraska, Northwestern and Wisconsin.  Next up, Purdue.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Oregon desparately needed a win against Arizona State, whom Oregon went through drastic measures to keep the Sun Devils from stealing their signs (much like Washington State did against them last week).  Also notable were Arizona States &quot;Desert Chrome&quot; uniforms, which look stylish, much different from their same-color-scheme-as-Minnesota's jerseys.  Thankfully, the Ducks finally won a game, their first Pac-12 win of the season, winning 54-35.  One thing for certain is that Justin Herbert, despite looking like a thirteen year old (he's 18, a true freshman) is legit.  His shocking meteoric rise from afterthought to being the first true freshman to start for the Ducks since Chris Miller in 1983 is quite astonishing considering he wasn't highly recruited, and from nearby Sheldon High School, a hometown kid.  What's not to love about Justin Herbert.  He threw for 489 passing yards today (tying a team record with Bill Musgrave) with 4 touchdowns.  Impressive, especially as a true freshman.  Hopefully, the Ducks will turn around their season now, but it won't be easy.  Next up, the worst school in the country, the University of Spoiled Cheaters.  God I hate them so much!&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Big XII's playoff chances took a huge hit today as West Virginia lost at Oklahoma State.  Their chances were slim to begin with, but at this point, the Big XII is going to need help to get back into the Playoffs.  Even worse was the fact that Baylor lost as well, being upset by Texas in the last minute 35-34.  I'm glad Baylor lost, especially with all the sexual assaults Art Briles ignored as coach, recent reports indicate he failed to report at least one sexual assault case he knew about.  And he claims he didn't deserve to be fired.  Yes he did!  But at this point, Oklahoma is the only unbeaten Big XII team in conference play, but with two non-conference losses against Ohio State and Houston (who lost last week to SMU of all teams), that makes their challenge more daunting.  As I'm obligated to include one Big XII team, I'm not ready to eliminate Baylor from my list.  But it's a long shot.  Nebraska also lost for the first time this season against Wisconsin, who, you can never count out.  With that said, they need to make it to the Big Ten title game to be considered for a playoff berth.  That leaves the following teams: Alabama, Michigan, Clemson, Washington, Ohio State, Texas A&amp;amp;M, Louisville, Nebraska, Baylor, and Florida.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/justin-herbert2.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Justin Herbert&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;The Legend of Justin Herbert continues.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;    
    &lt;p&gt;Washington finally faced a significant test as they visited Utah in a hard fought 31-24 victory, with Washington winning the game on a punt return for a touchdown in the fourth quarter.  If Lamar Jackson doesn't win the Heisman Trophy for some reason, Washington QB Jake Browning should win it.  He's been quite good this season for the Huskies.  I still don't like the Huskies but the Pac-12 needs someone in the Playoffs and they're the only hope at this point.  I'd rather see them in then two SEC teams, to say the least. --- Speaking of Lamar Jackson, Louisville needed a last-minute touchdown from him to beat Virginia, 32-25.  Not the type of performance you want if the Playoffs are their goal. ---  The most disappointing team this season is thankfully not Oregon, but rather their marquee non-conference matchup from last year, Michigan State, who's lost six in a row after starting the season 2-0.  What in the world happened to the Spartans? --- Clearly, no one is benefiting from Northwestern's strange season more than unbeaten Western Michigan.  The Broncos aren't going to play in the Playoffs even if they are unbeaten but they can still make a New Year's Six Bowl.  Fortunately, that task just got easier after Boise State got upset by Wyoming, a 30-28 win by the Cowboys, who won it with a safety in the last minute.  Of course, Western Michigan needs to remain unbeaten and make it in the Top 15 for consideration.  Right now, they're ranked 20th.  I love a good underdog story. --- With that said, so here are my picks for Top Ten:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alabama&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michigan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clemson&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Washington&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ohio State&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Louisville&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wisconsin (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Texas A&amp;amp;M (+2)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nebraska (-2)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Florida (NR)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/10/29/college-football-week-nine-thoughts</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/10/29/college-football-week-nine-thoughts</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Happy Birthday Adam's Blog</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
    a {
        font-weight: bold;
        color: blue;
    }
    a:visited {
        color: purple;
    }
&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Today marks the one year anniversary to my launch of Adam’s Blog.  It's come a long way from its humble roots, going through my major redesign in April.  So to honor my blog, here's a brief history of my blog and how I wound up getting here, along with some of my favorite posts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/happy-birthday.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Happy Birthday&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Happy Birthday!&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started my blog using JSON through my Express backed main website.   Not the best way to do a blog, but still got me through as I continued to fine tune my developing skills.  Eventually, I made the decision to break off from my Express backed main website and used a Jekyll powered blog branching off my website, which gave me much more flexibility in my blog pages themselves.  I officially relaunched blog.bodiewebdesign.com on May 4th.  I had hoped for a smooth launch, but just before I was ready to move over, the breaking news of degenerate &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/05/03/ted-cruz-the-definition-of-pathetic&quot;&gt;Ted Cruz&lt;/a&gt; dropping out of the Presidential race, which I had to put a blog about.  I was working on a blog post on him, which I wanted to release afterwards, but needed to post on that disgusting turd.  And special thanks to my sister Jenn for reminding me of that booger pic to use.  Classic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you'll see from reading my blog, my two favorite subjects are sports, particularly football and basketball, and unfortunately, politics.  This political cycle has been awful, but has given me an opportunity to express my displeasure in &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/01/31/dumb-and-dumber-why-the-top-republican-presidental-candidates-suck-at-math&quot;&gt;Dumb and Dumber&lt;/a&gt;, a.k.a. Donald Trump and Ted Cruz.  Hopefully that stops after the election.  I hate those two passionately.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Upgrading to Jekyll gave me more flexibility in my posts.  One post I'm particularly proud of is my expose on Oklahoma Senator Jim Inhofe’s ridiculous theories on &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/05/08/climate-change-and-snow&quot;&gt;global warming&lt;/a&gt;, as I was able to add a D3 based graph showcasing Snow levels throughout the years to debunk Inhofe's stupid beliefs.  It gave me an opportunity to try a new JavaScript library, which is always fun to do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As for my blogging skills itself, I feel it has helped me expressed myself through different channels.  I admit, it doesn't come easy for me to speak up, but writing my thoughts allows me to be more elegant and graceful than I have been in a long time.  One particular thing I've enjoyed is my live blogging posts.  &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/basketball/2016/04/13/mamba-day-and-everyones-celebrating&quot;&gt;Kobe Bryant's&lt;/a&gt; last game and the &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/basketball/2016/06/23/nba-draft-the-future-is-now&quot;&gt;NBA Draft&lt;/a&gt; were my favorites.  Live blogging the &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/09/26/liar-liar-pant-is-on-fire&quot;&gt;first Presidential debate&lt;/a&gt;, on the other hand, was a letdown for me.  Some things are better to blog than others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Perhaps the most important blog post I made was &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/08/08/my-pledge&quot;&gt;my pledge&lt;/a&gt; from August.  It's been two months and I still haven't verbally used that Idiot's name.  It's important to live in a free country and that Idiot is downright pathetic and unpatriotic.  As you'll see, plenty of posts about him and his awful ways.  I'm proud of the commitment I've made and I'm especially proud to have voted for Hillary Clinton this election.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More than anything, my blog gives me another channel to showcase my creativity.  Some of my posts are &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/06/12/three-little-words&quot;&gt;serious&lt;/a&gt; while others are downright &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/10/10/why-i-should-be-the-next-starting-quarterback-of-the-cleveland-browns&quot;&gt;silly&lt;/a&gt;.  Whatever the case may be, I enjoy my work and am proud of it as well.  Here's to another year of success.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/miscellaneous/2016/10/25/happy-birthday-adams-blog</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/miscellaneous/2016/10/25/happy-birthday-adams-blog</guid>
        
        
        <category>miscellaneous</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NBA Preview</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Tomorrow is the beginning of the 2016-2017 NBA Season.  For me, I will have to adjust to life without Kobe.  Who should be my favorite player?  Should I even have a favorite player?  How will the brand new Lakers look.  Who's going to win the NBA Championship this year?  How will Kevin Durant adjust to being the villain in Golden State.  Here are my thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/dangelo-russell.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;D'Angelo Russell&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;D'Angelo Russell figures to be the top player for the Lakers this year&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;It's going to be hella bizarre to watch the Lakers play knowing that Kobe isn't going to walk throught that door.  Last year they finished with their worst record ever, a far cry from their glory days they've had plenty of.  Byron Scott is no longer coach, not the right fit for the youngsters now playing.  He especially clashed with D'Angelo Russell, who stands to become the Lakers next star.  Will it lead to wins?  Probably not now, but like the Golden State Warriors at the beginning of Steph Curry's career, they will need time to grow and can at least be fun to watch.  Luke Walton is the right coach for the team, but Laker fans need to be patient.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The rest of the NBA has some entertaining stories.  Here are my standings predictions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Western Conference&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol reversed=&quot;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Los Angeles Lakers:  The Lakers are still likely to be the worst team in the stacked Western Conference.  They'll win more games this season, but still don't have the talent to compete with the rest of the West.  D'Angelo Russell should be in the running for most improved player and could easily average 20 points per game, but Brandon Ingram, Julius Randle, Jordan Clarkson and company are still too young to showcase consistency.  Signing Luol Deng was a nice locker room deal, perfect to fill the Andre Iguodala role with Golden State, but it's clear they will need to rebuild young: their biggest signing, after all, was Timofey Mozgov (yikes!)&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Sacramento Kings:  The Kings, are and have always been, a big freakin mess.  DeMarcus Cousins isn't getting any happier by the day and their draft picks, asides from him, have been completely baffling.  The Kings will try to hold on tight to keep him, but at some point, they need to realize they aren't going to win with him, at least until they get some quality players around him.  The owners and management have no clue on how to deal with Cousins.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Denver Nuggets:  Another team without a clue of how to run its team is the Denver Nuggets.  I'm not sure who their best player is.  They have a bunch of young parts, but they don't particularly mesh well together.  Emannuel Mudiay and Jamal Murray are essentially the same type of player, so I'm really uncertain as to the direction Denver is heading.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Phoenix Suns:  The Suns are similar to the Nuggets, but at least have Eric Bledsoe, provided he can actually stay healthy, is a talented point guard.  That question though, is going to hold Phoenix back for quite a while.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;New Orleans Pelicans:  Anthony Davis is obviously a beast, but he hasn't been consistently healthy, nor has he been consistently been surrounded by quality players.  They got rid of the average shooting guard logjam with Eric Gordon leaving, and Jrue Holiday is out for an extended time as his wife recovers from a brain tumor (hope she makes it), but too many questions about the surrounding talent and Anthony Davis's health.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Houston Rockets:  It was great to see Houston give Dwight Howard the ultimate &quot;F' you&quot; move by hiring Mike D'Antoni as their head coach, as the Rockets clearly made a mistake signing him, who was bound to clash with James Harden.  But Mike D'Antoni has no business being in the NBA.  He was a mere gimmick back in the Steve Nash days in Phoenix, and his plans to have James Harden as point guard will be a complete disaster.  Houston is a joke.&lt;/li&gt;  
    &lt;li&gt;Minnesota Timberwolves: The T'Wolves have a bright future ahead of them.  Karl Anthony Towns has potential to be the next great center, and Andrew Wiggins has plenty of talent, but still needs defensive polish.  Enter Tom Thibodeau, a tough and gritty defensive minded coach to put them to shape.  They have some great pieces to work with, and Kris Dunn has the talent to be the great defensive point guard Thibodeau needs, but in this tough conference, they're still a year or two away.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Memphis Grizzlies:  The Grizzles have some fine players, led by Marc Gasol and Zach Randolph, but something feels different this year.  New coach, Zach Randolph apparently will come off the bench.  That seems like an odd move for me.  Plus Marc Gasol is coming back from injury.  Mike Conley is a good player but got way too much money.  A lot of these contracts are ridiculous anyhow.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/karl-anthony-towns.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Karl-Anthony Towns&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Karl-Anthony Towns has the chance to be the next great center&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;      
    &lt;li&gt;Utah Jazz: The Jazz have nice players; Gordon Hayward, Derrick Favors, Ruby Gobert.  But they lack the star to push them over the top in a tough Western Conference.  Health was an issue for them last year.  In the Eastern Conference, they'd be a Playoff team, but not in the tough west.  It definitely helps to have a great defensive front court, but Gobert and the rest missed a lot of time last year.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Dallas Mavericks:  Every time I count them out, they always find a way to win.  Much credit to Dirk Nowitzki, one of the all time greats in this era.  His passion for playing and smarts to surround himself with talent makes him great, but unlike Tim Duncan, the Mavs haven't pull in the right pieces.  Harrison Barnes may not be the player Dirk needs.  But as long as he's around, they'll just sneak in to the playoffs.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Oklahoma City Thunder: Kevin Durant left.  Everyone knows that.  But as long as Russell Westbrook is there to lead the way, Oklahoma City still has a tough team to play.  Acquiring Victor Oladipo for overrated Serge Ibaka could be a steal for the Thunder, and Billy Donovan's toughness will still be around.  They won't be title contenders, but with one more strong piece, they'll be saying 'Kevin Who?'&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Portland Trail Blazers:  The Blazers surprised just about everyone last year, with a great backcourt combo with Damian Lillard and CJ McCollum.  That right there, along with coach Stotts great toughness, will always make Portland tough as long as they stay healthy.  But they lack great size up front to be real title contenders.  Still, Portland is the team no one wants to play.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Los Angeles Clippers:  As long as they have Chris Paul, Blake Griffin and DeAndre Jordan, the Clippers will always be in the race at the top of the Western Conference.  But as long as the ghost of Donald Sterling is still there, the Clippers will find a way to screw it up.  Chris Paul will be a free agent after this season; this could be the last chance for the Clippers to win with the talent they have and the great coach in Doc Rivers.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;San Antonio Spurs:  Tim Duncan retired, but with the best management ever, along with Gregg Popovich still going strong after twenty years, the Spurs have built a great team for this generation as well, led by Kawhi Leonard and LaMarcus Aldridge.  Add in Pau Gasol to replace Duncan and Tony Parker still around, the Spurs aren't going to go away for a long time.  I could envision Gregg Popovich turning into a robot and still coaching.  It wouldn't shock me.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
    		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/kevin-durant.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Kevin Durant&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
    		&lt;h4&gt;Kevin Durant: From Hero to Villain&lt;/h4&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt; 
    &lt;li&gt;Golden State Warriors: How does the best team in the Western Conference, who won 73 games in the regular season but blew a repeat manage to come up with Kevin Durant joining them?  It starts with great management and great timing, as Steph Curry's ridiculously bargain extension a few years ago laid the way to build a great team with Klay Thompson, Draymond Green and now Kevin Durant (along with Andre Iguodala).  Considering everything, they didn't give up that much, and certainly have the talent to win the West again.  They won't win 73, but that's one scary lineup to deal with.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
    &lt;h3&gt;Eastern Conference&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;ol reversed=&quot;&quot;&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Brooklyn Nets: The Nets are likely to be the worst team in the league this year.  Their main survivor from their failed experiment is injured prone Brook Lopez.  The Nets made some disastrous moves to win now and now their ship has completely sunk as a result.  Unfortunately, the only thing worse than having Mikhail Prokhorov as owner is Vladimir Putin.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Philadelphia 76ers: The only thing worse than the Nets win-now experiment was the ridiculously ridiculed Sam Hinkie extreme tanking.  The only difference is that now the 76ers have a potential difference maker in Ben Simmons.  Unfortunately, he's injured right now.  Outside of him, they have a messed up roster with Nerlens Noel, Jahlil Okafor and now healthy Joel Embiid in the front court.  Good luck Brett Brown.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Orlando Magic: The Magic gave up a potential star for Serge Ibaka.  That won't get them anywhere.  They don't have the pieces to get them into the playoffs for a long time, and I'm puzzled as to what the Magic are doing.  Nikola Vucevic is a nice player and perhaps Aaron Gordon will blossom, but despite having Frank Vogel as their coach, Orlando is a mess.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Miami Heat:  The Heat went from the big two to nothing by putting all their chips in with Hassan Whiteside, a talented defensive player, but not a franchise leader and definitely not worth the extra money that could've allowed them to keep the face of their franchise.  Dwyane Wade is gone, and Chris Bosh isn't likely to play with Miami (or anyone) again with persistent blood clots.  Has Pat Riley finally lost it?  Here's hoping.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Milwaukee Bucks: The Bucks have some nice young players, but without Khris Middleton, whose meteoric rise to role player to stud, the Bucks still have holes in their game.  Of course, their experiment to have Giannis Antetokounmpo play the point guard could cause nightmares for opposing teams.  But too many questions on the offensive end to put the Bucks in the playoffs.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Washington Wizards:  The Wizards have a nice backcourt, but John Wall and Bradley Beal recently admitted that their styles clash, and that could be a problem for the Wizards.  They don't have that much surrounding them asides from Marcin Gortat, and now that Scotty Brooks is coaching, who knows how the Wiz will respond.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;New York Knicks: Yes, the Knicks have a case of the Porzinger Fever, and if it still continues, the Knicks have a chance to make some noise, but Derrick Rose, though better than most point guards the Knicks have had, is damaged goods at this point and I don't think Joakim Noah will make much of a difference.  At the end of the day, they'll still be defined by Carmelo Anthony's one dimensional game.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float: left&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/giannis-antetokounmpo.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Giannis Antetokounmpo&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;It's cooler (and easier) to refer to Giannis Antetokounmpo as &quot;The Greek Freak&quot;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;          
                
        &lt;li&gt;Detroit Pistons:  The Pistons have the talents of an average middling team, and not much has changed for them.  They still have Andre Drummond and Reggie Jackson, but not much else has changed besides that.  Detroit's stuck in neutral unless they bring in some better helping parts.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Charlotte Hornets: Kemba Walker played really well last year and could take the jump to become a superstar caliber player, but they'll lose out on the inside presence of Al Jefferson, who left for Indiana.  Ironically, Roy Hibbert has taken his place, the classic stiff.  The talent's still there in the backcourt, but Jefferson was underrated.  They should've offered him more to stay.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Chicago Bulls: The Bulls turned into a complete mess with Fred Hoiberg his first year coaching them, but the shocking signing of Dwyane Wade gives them character, great leadership and the perfect role model for Jimmy Butler.  With that said, I'm not sure how they will work together with Rajon Rondo in the mix as well.  That seems to me to be a bad trio.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Atlanta Hawks: Mike Budenholzer is a great coach, but Dwight Howard will be by far his toughest challenge, as Howard is still too much of a prima donna to handle, and not the player he was when he reached his prime in Orlando.  The Hawks don't have a star, so they can let Howard take the faux credit, but with Al Horford and Jeff Teague gone, Atlanta is bound to decline.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Toronto Raptors: Kyle Lowry and DeMar Derozan are still there, and that alone will get them into the playoffs, but not much else has changed.  They were a tad bit lucky last year, but the talent in the east is getting better, while Toronto remained the same.  That won't get them back to the Eastern Conference finals.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Indiana Pacers:  Paul George is a BEAST, his talent can't be denied, and he came back from the horrific injury even better than before.  Not sure how he did it, but he is one of the better players in the game.  Adding Jeff Teague as point guard and Al Jefferson at center make them a better team.  Still, it's weird to see Nate McMillan as their coach.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/paul-george.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Paul George&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Paul George is a BEAST&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;          
        &lt;li&gt;Boston Celtics: I don't like the Celtics, but Danny Ainge is the best GM around.  His hire of Brad Stevens is the best hire of a first time coach since Gregg Popovich (who's still in San Antonio after twenty years).  Their trade of KG and Paul Pierce gave them a shitload of draft picks at the best time, and their steal of Isaiah Thomas brought them to the next level.  Add Al Horford to the mix, and the Celtics are the best team in the East to knock off LeBron and the Cavs.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Cleveland Cavaliers:  LeBron James has played in the NBA Finals six years in a row.  That alone makes the defending champs the best team in the league.  Kyrie Irving outplayed Steph Curry and is a better all around player.  Until anyone can beat LeBron in the east, they have to be Number 1.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;So who will win the awards, and the title.  Here are my picks:  &lt;strong&gt;Rookie of the Year:&lt;/strong&gt; Ben Simmons.  &lt;strong&gt;Defensive Player of the Year:&lt;/strong&gt; Kawhi Leonard.  &lt;strong&gt;Sixth Man of the Year:&lt;/strong&gt; Andre Iguodala.  &lt;strong&gt;Most Improved Player:&lt;/strong&gt; D'Angelo Russell. &lt;strong&gt;Coach of the Year:&lt;/strong&gt; Brad Stevens. &lt;strong&gt;MVP:&lt;/strong&gt; Russell Westbrook.  &lt;strong&gt;NBA Champions:&lt;/strong&gt; Golden State Warriors over Cleveland Cavaliers. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/basketball/2016/10/24/nba-preview</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/basketball/2016/10/24/nba-preview</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>basketball</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Football Week Eight Thoughts</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Week Eight is unofficially Homecoming Week.  For Minnesota, it's their official Homecoming game against Rutgers, their first matchup ever.  For Oregon, it's a painful reminder of how far they've truly fallen against another high powered offensive team in Cal.  That game was played yesterday.  As we reach Week 8, a closer picture starts for determining the four playoff teams.  I'll talk more about that later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/northwestern.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Northwestern&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;It's crazy every one-handed grab will be compared to OBJ.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Oregon faced off against Cal on Friday night mired in a losing streak.  Unfortunately, their defense still sucks tremendously.  On the plus side, Justin Herbert looks legit, bring the Ducks back from a 20 point deficit to force overtime, throwing for six touchdowns.  But his one interception sealed the game in double OT, as Cal won a wild-west shootout 52-49.  Now the Ducks are on their longest losing streak since 1996.  How times have changed.  The Ducks were mired in mediocrity before that yet Rich Brooks remained the coach for 17 years, building a legacy.  But that legacy may have reached its end, as the Ducks are now a different team and have bigger goals in mind.  Mark Helfrich, as good as a man he is, probably needs a miracle to keep his job.  The rest of the Ducks schedule looks daunting: Arizona State, USC, Stanford, Utah and Oregon State, all teams that can run the ball quite well.  Something Oregon clearly can't stop.  Chances are, should Helfrich be fired, they will look outside for a coach.  Perhaps Chip Kelly would come back, as his NFL career has predictably turned out to be disappointing, and his 49ers look terrible.  But we'll see what happens there.  Until then, Duck fans everywhere should start counting down to basketball season.  At least the basketball team looks strong and can play defense.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Minnesota, meanwhile, played its first game against Rutgers.  The good news for them is that Mitch Leidner returned after suffering a concussion two weeks ago against Iowa.  A surprise as he was declared out just two days ago.  Even better news, Rutgers is just plain awful.  The worst team in the Big Ten and probably the worst team of all the major conference teams.  Unfortunately for Minnesota, after a great game in Maryland, their performance against Rutgers was a letdown.  Although they won 34-32, Minnesota needed a last second field goal to win a game that they should've easily won.  They were favored by 17 points and jumped to a 21-3 lead, but Rutgers, who entered the game with just 14 points in the season against Big Ten foes, scored 32 and took the lead late in the fourth quarter.  Again, it was Mitch Leidner and the passing game that struggled.  They'll need to play better next week when they visit Illinois.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;As the playoff race begins, we have a clear top team: Alabama.  They look pretty unstoppable at this point, and appear to be a lock to defend their title.  But anything can happen, as Ohio State was shocked by Penn State, who came back from a 21-7 decifit to win 24-21.  Ohio State is still in the playoff hunt, as a matchup with Michigan still looms with the Big Ten East (and a trip to the Big Ten title game) on the line.  The Big XII needs a miracle to get back in the playoffs, as the only unbeatens team left in the conference are Baylor, currently ranked 9th, and West Virginia, whose currently ranked 12th.  The chances of them running the table are low, so most likely, the Big XII is out.  Washington has a good shot of finishing unbeaten, and is the only Pac-12 team that can bring the conference back after missing the playoffs last season.  The ACC is a bit of a scramble between Clemson and Louisville.  Clemson beat Lousiville in a close matchup, but they still have to face Florida State, who can play spoiler and create a three-way tie between the three, all in the same division of the ACC.  If either Clemson or Washington lose a game, that would open up a spot for both Michigan and Ohio State.  At this point, the following teams are still alive: Alabama, Ohio State, Michigan, Clemson, Washington, Texas A&amp;amp;M, Louisville, Nebraska, Baylor, West Virginia, and Florida.  At the end of the day, anything can happen between now and December.  After all, the Chicago Cubs clinched their first World Series appearance since 1945 and are four wins away from their first title since 1908.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Northwestern continues to be the most confusing team in the country.  They lost to Western Michigan, though they are undefeated, so that's a plus for them, and even worse, lost to Illinois State.  But they have rebounded, beating Iowa among other teams.  And much credit to Safety Kyle Queiro, who completed an OBJ like one-handed interception. --- Congrats to the Colorado Buffaloes, who have now won six games this year and clinched a bowl berth.  They could win the Pac-12 South with the talent they have.  Unfortunately, Oregon has replaced them in the gutter for the time being.  Not only did Washington beat both Oregon and Stanford (convincingly), Colorado has as well.  Mike McIntyre definitely belongs in the running for Coach of the Year. --- Utah running back Joseph Williams rushed for 332 yards against UCLA today.  Combined with Arizona State running back Kalen Ballage's seven rushing touchdown (eight overall) against Texas Tech earlier in the season equals two reasons Oregon is not going to get better any time soon.  Yikes!--- The Heisman race this year is Louisville QB Lamar Jackson's to lose.  He struck the Heisman pose today against NC State.  --- Oklahoma and Texas Tech combined for 1,708 yards, setting a new record.  That's a lot of yards.  Seven records were broken in that game. --- With that said, so here are my picks for Top Ten:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alabama&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michigan (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clemson (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Washington (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ohio State (-3)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Louisville&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nebraska (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wisconsin (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Baylor (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Texas A&amp;amp;M (-3)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/10/22/college-football-week-eight-thoughts</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/10/22/college-football-week-eight-thoughts</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Football Week Seven Thoughts</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Week Seven for me is Strange Week.  The Minnesota Golden Gophers make their way to Maryland to play them for the first time since they joined the Big Ten in 2014.  I'm still not used to them and Rutgers being part of the Big Ten.  Maryland should've remained in the ACC and Rutgers looks like complete crap.  Market aside, the Big Ten should've stopped with Nebraska.  But nonetheless, it's the game against the Terrapins.  As for the Ducks, they stand to have their best defensive performance of the season, as they have the week off.  As for the rest of the week, it seems kind of bland, with the exception of Alabama-Tennessee and Ohio State-Wisconsin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/rodney-smith.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Rodney Smith&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Rodney Smith led the way to a win against Maryland&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;The Gophers faced off against Maryland with their first glimpse into the future.  Mitch Leidner was out with a concussion, so backup QB Conor Rhoda gets his first start.  He's a junior so we'll see who the starter is next season, but here's hoping Mitch Leidner will be back for next weeks game, not that they need him against god-awful Rutgers.  As long as they have the Rodney Smith-Shannon Brooks combo at Running Back, Minnesota will be just fine.  And that was true for the Gophers first Big Ten matchup against Maryland.  Their defense shut down Maryland's offense, holding them scoreless through three quarters, and the Gophers mostly kept it on the ground, with their dynamic duo that they've missed since the great Marion Barber III-Laurence Maroney days.  Their defense forced four turnovers against Maryland, including a pick-six by Antoine Winfield Jr. to seal the game.  Minnesota got the win they really needed, 31-10.  Next up, their homecoming game against god-awful Rutgers.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;This week wasn't particularly interesting, and honestly, I wasn't really paying that much attention to it. I had other things to do. --- Tennessee got their butts wooped by Alabama, no surprise there. --- Ohio State beat Wisconsin in overtime.  So much for Wisconsin having a down year, although their wins against LSU and Michigan State look far less impressive than they did at the time.  LSU fired Les Miles and Michigan State is 2-4. --- Clemson barely survived against NC State, as NC State missed a field goal that would've won the game at the end of the fourth quarter.  --- Oregon plays Cal next Friday at Cal.  They'll probably give up a touchdown before the game starts. ---  That's all I got for now, so here are my picks for Top Ten:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alabama&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ohio State&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michigan (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clemson (-1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Washington (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Louisville (-1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Texas A&amp;amp;M&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nebraska (+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wisconsin (-1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Baylor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/10/15/college-football-week-seven-thoughts</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/10/15/college-football-week-seven-thoughts</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why I Should Be The Next Starting Quarterback of the Cleveland Browns</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Tim Couch, Ty Detmer, Doug Pederson, Spergon Wynn, Kelly Holcomb, Jeff Garcia, Luke McCown, Trent Dilfer, Charlie Frye, Derek Anderson, Brady Quinn, Ken Dorsey, Bruce Gradkowski, Colt McCoy, Jake Delhomme, Seneca Wallace, Brandon Weeden, Thad Lewis, Jason Campbell, Brian Hoyer, Johnny Manziel, Connor Shaw, Josh McCown, Austin Davis, Robert Griffin III and Cody Kessler.	A list this long would be perfect to describe a proud NFL franchise's Hall of Famers, but no, this is the list of starting quarterbacks for the Cleveland Browns since their franchise was reborn in 1998.  Clearly, the Cleveland Browns are cursed with Quarterbacks.  They're looking for the wrong qualities. Here are the reasons I should be the next starting quarterback of the Cleveland Browns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/browns.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Cleveland Browns&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;This could be your future, Dawg Pound&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;It's true, I'm thirty one years old and have never played football on any level, much less the quarterback position, but the Cleveland Browns should know that the following qualities surpass anyone on the above list.  For starters, I have never thrown an interception in my life, much less thrown an incomplete pass.  Also to note is that the offensive line doesn't have to worry about me getting sacked since I've never been sacked before either.  I'm also proud to say I've never suffered a football injury in my life.  I fractured my wrist in the eighth grade, but that was in my non-throwing arm.  Other than that, I've enjoyed a pain free career and that's something the Cleveland Browns have been lacking.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Cleveland Browns have clearly been terrible at drafting quarterbacks.  All of their first round selections have been complete failures, from their first pick ever, Tim Couch, to the complete and utter disaster known as Johnny Manziel.  They've passed up plenty of quality quarterbacks, including Russell Wilson, Aaron Rodgers, and of course, Tom Brady.  That's why they shouldn't draft a quarterback at all and settle for an unknown quality free agent like myself.  No more bad draft choices.  No more overpaying for quarterbacks past their prime.  No more old veterans at the end of their career.  Just pick me instead; I'm on a different level.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Let's also realize another sad fact, no one wants to be the Cleveland Browns quarterback unless they get overpaid.  I, on the other hand, would be willing to take the minimum so Cleveland can use the other money to better build a team.  They have a good offensive-minded coach in Hue Jackson, now they just need to bring in some better players to surround their quarterback stud.  Cleveland needs to take that jump and not spend too much money for less quality.  Cleveland is cursed for a reason, and there's only one person that could save the Cleveland Browns: LeBron James.  But until he has the time to play football as well as basketball, they will need to take a chance on someone else.  That's why I should become the next starting Quarterback of the Cleveland Browns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/10/10/why-i-should-be-the-next-starting-quarterback-of-the-cleveland-browns</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/10/10/why-i-should-be-the-next-starting-quarterback-of-the-cleveland-browns</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>So He Finally Used the A-Word</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; It took sixteen months, but the Idiot finally used the A-word he never likes to use: &lt;strong&gt;APOLOGIZE&lt;/strong&gt;.  What did it take for him to apologize?  A video mic drop recording of him saying some incredibly vulgar things about women, essentially bragging about hitting on a married woman and getting away with groping women because he’s a star.  He called it 'locker room banter,' I call it 'words a sexual predator would say.'  Now that he's used the A-word, he can now apologize to everyone he’s offended in his life.  Here's an partial list of everyone owed an apology.  He's offended so many people it's hard to keep track.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/stupid-idiot.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Stupid Trump&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;Once an Idiot...Always an Idiot&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Barack Obama --- Michelle Obama --- Malia and Sasha Obama --- Hillary Clinton --- Bill Clinton --- Ted Cruz --- John Kasich --- Jeb Bush --- Marco Rubio --- Rand Paul --- Tim Kaine --- Chelsea Clinton --- Carly Fiorina --- John Kerry --- Joe Biden --- Rosie O'Donnell --- Megyn Kelly --- Alicia Machado --- Khizr Khan --- Ghazala Khan --- John McCain --- Serge Kovaleski --- The Central Park Five --- Paul Ryan --- Jeff Flake --- Nancy O'Dell --- Billy Bush --- George W. Bush --- Kareem Abdul-Jabbar --- Mark Cuban --- Every Hispanic in America --- Every Muslim in the world not part of a terrorist group --- The Reagan Family --- Angela Merkel --- Mitt Romney --- Heidi Cruz --- Rafael Cruz --- Ivanka Trump --- Rev. Faith Green Timmons --- South Korea --- Japan --- China --- United Kingdom --- David Cameron --- Sadiq Khan --- Harry Reid --- Elizabeth Warren --- Michael Bloomberg --- Bill de Blasio --- Everyone that got attacked at his rallies by his supporters --- Anthony Weiner --- Robert DeNiro --- Ivana Trump --- The Media --- Mexico --- Bernie Sanders --- Vincente Fox --- Everyone affected by his Bankruptcies --- Every contractor he stifled money out of --- Every African American he refused to rent property to --- Black Lives Matter --- All African Americans in General --- Gonzalo P. Curiel --- Eric Schniederman --- Lindsey Graham --- Pope Francis --- All Victims of PTSD --- Samuel L. Jackson --- Cher --- Mac Miller --- Syed Farook's family --- Everyone living in Jersey City, New Jersey --- General John Allen --- All Syrian Refugees --- The Republican Party --- The Democratic Party --- The United States of America&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Thank you and have a good day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/10/08/so-he-finally-used-the-a-word</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/politics/2016/10/08/so-he-finally-used-the-a-word</guid>
        
        
        <category>politics</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Football Week Six Thoughts</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;article&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Week Six for me is Rivalry Week Part 1.  Minnesota hosted Iowa for the Floyd of Rosedale and Oregon hosted Washington, winning twelve in a row against them but looking far worse now than they have at ay time in those twelve years.  As for the the rest of the games, another entertaining variety of match-ups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/floyd-of-rosedale.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Floyd of Rosedale&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;h4&gt;My proudest moment watching the Gophers at the Metrodome, carrying off Floyd of Rosedale&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;I went to four games while I was at the University of Minnesota, and the last game against Iowa was the best game of the bunch.  They beat a rival and won a trophy.  So it went without saying that Minnesota really needed a win against Iowa, to prove their legitimacy as possible Big Ten contenders.  Unfortunately, while their defense looked strong, their offense sputtered and could only muster up 7 points, losing to Iowa 14-7 after an Iowa touchdown late in the fourth quarter put them up ahead for good.  While Minnesota has the running backs, they still lack consistency in the passing game.  A tough loss to swallow, but Iowa's defense is just as good, a good old classic Big Ten Slugfest.  Next week for Minnesota: a road trip to Maryland, Minnesota's first game against Maryland since they joined the Big Ten.  The last (and only) time they've met was in 1977.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot; style=&quot;float:left&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/img/justin-herbert.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Justin Herbert&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;h4&gt;Webfoots, Ducks, whatever you want to call them, they can't defend.&lt;/h4&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The last time Oregon lost to Washington, I was a freshman at the U of O.  I remember watching the game on TV.  Hard to believe Oregon would end up winning the next twelve games.  But this year, Washington enters the game ranked #5 and statistically with the best defense in the country.  Oregon, on the other hand, couldn't stop a chair from scoring.  Wearing their Webfoots jerseys to honor the ancient days, Oregon made a surprising change at Quarterback starting true freshman Justin Herbert.  For the first time in a long time, Oregon looked completely overmatched and likely to get blown out.  And they were blown out, just as everyone figured, final score 70-21.  And just like that, the streak is over.  Oregon gets a much needed week off, but it doesn't look any easier as they face Davis Webb and the high-flying Cal offense.  It's not going to get any easier for the Ducks and with their defense as horrific as it's looked, this will not turn out well.  This may be the beginning of the end for Mark Helfrich.  I questioned how effective he'd be without Marcus Mariota leading the way and it hasn't been particularly pretty at times.  Oregon fans will be pissed, and should be.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;blog-pic&quot;&gt;
    		&lt;img src=&quot;/img/notre-dame-nc-state.jpg&quot; data-toggle=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;Notre Dame vs NC State&quot; class=&quot;image block img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
    		&lt;h4&gt;Thoughts to those affected by Hurricane Matthew, even in Raleigh the rain looks horrific.&lt;/h4&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;It's tough to finish a season undefeated, no matter what conference you play in.  Houston, having beaten (a now overrated) Oklahoma at home, lost to high-scoring Navy 46-40.  Their slim chance to make the Playoffs unfortunately is over.  But they can still make a Big Five bowl game. --- Tennessee might be the most entertaining team in the country.  Every game they've played in this season has seen them make a big comeback, and against Texas A&amp;amp;M they came back from a 28-7 deficit.  Volunteers never say die.  But desite the comeback and leading the game into OT, Texas A&amp;amp;M won 45-38.  Gotta give the Vols credit for fighting back.  --- Who would've thought that when Colorado played USC, that the one ranked team would actually be Colorado.  But USC ended up winning 21-17.  What a shame.  --- Hurricane Matthew had a big impact on some of the games in that area.  It postponed LSU-Florida (which neither team has a shared open game to reschedule it, stay turned), and drenched games in the Carolinas.  I saw the rain on a clip of the Notre Dame-NC State game, it looked nasty.  --- Another nasty hit on Penn State kicker Joey Julius.  I didn't realize he had an eating problem.  For that, I apologize for my previous caption on him.  --- Michigan beat Rutgers 78-0.  Rutgers lost to Ohio State 58-0 last week.  Why are they in the Big Ten again? --- Miami fans started throwing litter all over the field after a penalty call went against them.  Only Miami, right?  ---  With that said, here are my picks for Top Ten:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alabama&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ohio State&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clemson(+1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michigan (-1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Louisville&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Washington (+2)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Texas A&amp;amp;M&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wisconsin (NR)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nebraska (NR)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Baylor (NR)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/10/08/college-football-week-six-thoughts</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.bodiewebdesign.com/blog/sports/football/2016/10/08/college-football-week-six-thoughts</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports</category>
        
        <category>football</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
